<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you need to capture a target in a building, one of the most effective techniques is known as the &quot;Hammer and Anvil.&quot; First, your team surrounds the structure, sealing off all exits; then you enter from all points at once, quickly and quietly. The goal is to find your target fast enough to avoid a stand-off or a fire-fight. It&apos;s hard to interrogate your target if he&apos;s dealing with a gun-shot wound. Of course it&apos;s even harder if he&apos;s dead. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re abducted at gun-point, it&apos;s best to approach it like a blind date: you want to be an active listener, you want to stay positive and you want to make a connection. The more you humanize yourself in the eyes of your captor, the harder it will be for them to pull the trigger. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re marked for death in prison, you&apos;re always anticipating the next fight. The earlier you spot a potential adversary, the better you can defend yourself. Unfortunately, that&apos;s not always enough. If you realize you have multiple attackers coming at you with a coordinated assault, just defending yourself won&apos;t work. The only move is to attack. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a reason spies try to stick to the speed limit in operations. When the stakes are high enough, a simple speeding ticket can be a life or death matter for you; or, for the police officer who&apos;s just trying to do his job. </li>
<li>As any crisis negotiator knows, only about one in five hostages survives a rescue attempt. If you&apos;re the hostage, you&apos;d like to improve those odds, which means figuring out where your rescue is coming from and getting yourself out of the line of fire. Of course, if your captor is every bit as trained as you are, even the slightest attempt to adjust your position might be noticed. </li>
<li>The standard M-112 demolition charge contains 1.25 pounds of C-4. When the charge is detonated, the explosive is converted into compressed gas and the shock-wave rips through anything within 16 feet; which means that if five of those charges are in your back-pack, anyone within a city block is in your blast radius too. </li>
<li>Air-boats are built light with the least material possible, which is great if you want to skim quickly across the water; but, it&apos;s problematic in a gunfight when you don&apos;t have anything to hide behind. You want to make sure you fire first, and last. Of course, there&apos;s no need to hide when you&apos;ve been chasing a decoy.</li>
<li>They&apos;re certain fights you can&apos;t hope to win, your only goal is to not lose too badly. Surviving a beating from multiple attackers is about avoiding the worst blows. You protect your head, do your best to stay on your feet and most of all you, hope for a miracle.</li></ul>
