<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">There&apos;s a long tradition of using doubles in espionage. They&apos;re mostly used by dictators who want to confuse would-be assassins. But they have other, less common uses. Like framing someone for a crime they didn&apos;t commit.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When confronting an armed enemy, the big question is what weapons they&apos;re bringing to the fight. Trick your enemy into bringing the wrong weapon, and you&apos;ve got the advantage. If someone thinks they&apos;re taking fire from a sniper for example, they&apos;ll choose something long range with a long barrel. Which won&apos;t do you much good in close combat.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For a spy, one of the most useful contacts in the criminal underworld is the small-time drug dealer. Their work demands that they stay informed about their rivals, their suppliers, the police, and any other bad guys who might be operating in their area.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The key to robbing an armed transport is to stop the vehicle without putting the guards on the defensive. Shooting a tire can cause a blowout without arousing suspicion, but it takes a gifted sniper to hit a target moving 40 miles per hour.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Staging a scene is one of the most important deception techniques in espionage. You&apos;re telling a story. Arranging evidence for someone to discover so they&apos;ll believe what you want them to believe. If it works, there&apos;s nothing like it. If it doesn&apos;t work, well, it&apos;s good to be nearby with a sniper rifle.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For a spy, there&apos;s no greater victory than successfully inserting an asset into a hostile organization. Of course, it&apos;s a little hard to celebrate that victory when the hostile organization is a bunch of trigger-happy drug dealers, and the asset is your best friend.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The first moments of an infiltration are crucially important. That&apos;s when your establishing yourself. What you know about them, what they know about you, and most importantly, how useful you&apos;re going to be. If the target decides you&apos;re useful, you&apos;re in. If they decide you&apos;re not useful, you&apos;re usually dead.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Establishing a cover as a drug addict isn&apos;t glamorous, but it has its advantages. People don&apos;t expect addicts to be rational, so they don&apos;t question their motives. Nothing explains an unwanted intrusion, quite like the impression that you&apos;re high as a kite.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Not all of the intelligence spies use is stolen, or even secret. When the information you need involves a lot of data, like searching for a single face in the population of Miami, what you really need is access to the right database. Which is usually behind the counter at the closest government agency.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The most advanced computer is worse at identifying faces than a newborn baby. Unless a photo is taken straight on under direct lighting, facial-recognition software is nearly worthless. Fortunately, driver&apos;s licence photos are taken straight on under direct lighting for exactly that reason. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Navigation systems combine data from traffic helicopters, police scanners, and road sensors to estimate the driving time along your route. But compiling all that data creates a time lag. There&apos;s still no quicker way to get across town, than being guided by somebody who has access to real-time satellite imagery.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For a spy, sneaking into the middle of a gun battle to pull someone out is one of the less popular assignments. It&apos;s mostly about timing. Go in too early, and you have both sides shooting at you. Go in too late, and, well, you&apos;re too late. 
</p>
</xml>
