<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Spies make great neighbors. They&apos;re polite, they keep the lawn trimmed, and they never crank the music at night. They don&apos;t stand out because they don&apos;t want to be found. So if you&apos;re hunting for a covert operative, and all you&apos;ve got to go on are the names of a few dozen suspects, you&apos;re out of luck unless you know where to look. </li>
<li>The garbage someone leaves on the curb can often tell you more than a face-to-face conversation. Shredded documents in the trash used to be a strong indicator that someone had a secret. But nowadays, everybody and their mother shreds bills to prevent identity theft.</li>
<li>Laundry bluing is a synthetic dye that dry cleaners use by the thimble and covert operatives go through by the bottle. It blots out secrets and works like a poor man&apos;s dye pack; staining anyone who digs through your trash. </li>
<li>Work long enough in covert ops and you&apos;re bound to be offered some pretty nasty assignments. When a bad job comes along, you have two choices and neither is very appealing. You can pass and watch the op go down or you can take the job and make sure the op gets blown.</li>
<li>Covert operatives try to avoid assuming other people&apos;s identities whenever possible. There&apos;s just too many pitfalls when you&apos;re dealing with someone your new identity has corresponded with. What have they said? What have they been told? What have they agreed to? Of course, it helps if the person you&apos;re deceiving is terrified of the person you&apos;re pretending to be. </li>
<li>When a pro plans an ambush, they capitalize on the element of surprise. They attack aggressively so their opponent has to react from a place of weakness. An amateur, on the other hand, is more likely to take a defensive posture which means they are the one acting from a place of weakness. </li>
<li>Cell phone jammers emit radio waves at the same frequency as commercial cell phones. They&apos;re useful when you really wanna make sure someone stays out of touch. </li>
<li>It doesn&apos;t matter if you&apos;re trying to take out a moped or a dump truck. Every vehicle has three areas of vulnerability: The driver, the engine and the tires. A can of paint across the windshield could blind the driver. A 50-millimeter cannon could kill the engine. But neither will guarantee the truck won&apos;t swerve into oncoming traffic. But if you force a vehicle&apos;s front tires off the road, you drastically diminish its maneuverability. That way, it can&apos;t swerve. Of course, getting a dump truck&apos;s tires off the ground is even more difficult than it sounds and a hell of a lot more dangerous. </li>
<li>Staging a fake death and a believable emergency response is almost impossible on a budget. One lone ambulance isn&apos;t going to sell it. So unless you happen to have a fleet of fire and rescue vehicles, uniforms and a dozen actors you trust, you really do have to call 911. You just have to have called your people first.</li>
<li>Spend a career in covert ops and you&apos;re going to know some bad people. You&apos;ll work with them, you&apos;ll live with them, you might even trust your life to them. But none of that makes them your friend. It can&apos;t. Because one day, you might have to end them. </li>
<li>Black bag missions are often broken into separate parts. Operatives are given discreet tasks to ensure secrecy. They&apos;re like jigsaw pieces and you never know if any of the ones you&apos;re given are from the same puzzle. But if you can get your hands on a corner piece, the part where the puzzle starts to take shape, sometimes you realize all your pieces fit together. </li></ul>
