<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you&apos;re posing as a potential client of a private military company, it doesn&apos;t pay to be subtle. A private army is a very high dollar item and the people who rent them tend to be super rich and not afraid to show it. It&apos;s an expensive cover ID, but if you do it right, it&apos;s worth every penny. You want your target focused less on your credentials and more on the make of your watch and the size of your wallet.</li>
<li>One of the biggest challenges in covert operations, is working with civilian assets. It&apos;s often as much about keeping the asset from falling apart, as it is about gathering intelligence. Kind of like babysitting, only with a gun to your head.</li>
<li>For a spy, deep cover assignments often mean going into enemy territory alone and unarmed. If you want to survive, you better have a support team you can trust watching your back.</li>
<li>Modifications like nitrous oxide injectors and ultra-light carbon fiber body work, are great in movies. But in real life, spies need cars that won&apos;t raise suspicions if they&apos;re searched. The speed, power, and handling you need, better come factory installed; because if the wrong person gets curious it could mean a bullet to the head.</li>
<li>The private military industry is worth 100 billion a year worldwide and growing. It&apos;s secretive, well armed, and almost completely unregulated by international law. Which is great if you need to hire your own private army; but, not so good if you need to steal their classified intelligence. Which means sometimes you have to rely on your powers of persuasion.</li>
<li>The easiest way to open a door with an electric lock is to cut the electricity. Unless your target has a fail-secure door designed to stay locked during a power outage. To get past a fail-secure door, you can try to steal the entry code; but, if you have access to the manufacturers schematics, it&apos;s much easier to wire in a duplicate circuit and trip the lock yourself.</li>
<li>Whether you&apos;re in a market in Syria, or a boutique in Miami, getting supplies to operatives in the field is always dangerous. Often, you have to spot a contact, arrange an excuse to approach, and make a drop – and do it all while looking like you&apos;re just out for a day&apos;s shopping.</li>
<li>They key to successfully bribing someone who resists an initial approach, is research and observation. You need to know as much as you can about your target – his principles, his weaknesses, his dreams. With most by-the-book targets, it&apos;s usually just a matter of making them feel like they&apos;re not being paid to do something wrong, they&apos;re being rewarded for doing something right.</li>
<li>Sabotage is most often used to destroy a target&apos;s vehicles, but not always. Simply damaging an enemies car can be very useful as well, as long as you can get your own team in position to do the repairs.</li>
<li>Getting people to evacuate a building is a lot harder than you might think. Most people don&apos;t pay much attention to fire alarms unless they see flames. Carbon monoxide alarms on the other hand tend to get plenty of attention. People are reluctant to ignore a threat that&apos;s invisible, odorless and deadly. And, best of all, any home with a gas line has a built in delivery system.</li>
<li>Any safe can be cracked with enough time and the right equipment. Even high-end models with security features like glass re-lockers – sheets of glass in the wall that shatter if you try to drill through them. Hit one, and a locking bolt seals the safe permanently. But if you come prepared with a drill point diagram and a good bore-scope, you can bypass the re-locker and find the combination by studying the wheel pack. Then, you just have to hope that your plan to get out of the building goes as well as your plan to get into the safe.</li>
<li>If you need to get out of a zip tie and you can&apos;t cut yourself free, your best option is to find a shim. You can make a shim out of almost anything that&apos;s thin enough and flexible enough to slip into the cable tie and separate the teeth from the ratchet mechanism. Of course, that&apos;s easier said than done if your hands are tied.</li>
<li>Most people know that Carbon Monoxide is a poisonous gas. Inhale too much, and it displaces the oxygen in your blood stream and suffocates you from the inside out. What most people don&apos;t know, is that in a confined space with a vapor-to-air mixture anywhere between twelve and seventy-five percent, it&apos;s also a powerful explosive. </li></ul>
