<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>For spies, the hardest part of operating in the field isn&apos;t combat. When bullets are flying, there&apos;s never really time to think. But in the quiet hours, when you&apos;re alone, thinking is all you can do. Spies don&apos;t make a habit of holding on to keepsakes for the same reason prisoners serving life sentences stop seeing visitors. As much as you might want that connection to your past life, there comes a point when a constant reminder of what you can never have is just too painful. And you can&apos;t have distractions like that when you have to focus on a job.</li>
<li>Operatives working under deep cover spend a lot of time alone. And no matter how hard you&apos;ve trained for it, the isolation never gets easier. Since every meeting you take could compromise the operation and blow your cover, even your case officer has to keep his distance. You only get together when face-to-face contact is worth the risk of getting killed.</li>
<li>One of the problems with taking a mission out of the country, is that you subtract yourself from the lives of the people you love. Because they&apos;re not just going to stop living, important things are going to happen, and you&apos;re going to miss them. But the biggest problem caused by your absence, is that you&apos;re not there when the people you protect, need you the most.</li>
<li>There are many advantages to flying into a country on an unregistered plane. You don&apos;t wait in lines, you don&apos;t check bags, and you don&apos;t leave an incriminating paper trail. The disadvantage is that without a declared flight path, you can&apos;t land at an airport. So the best you can hope for is finding an open field and flying in low. Of course, while flying in low might keep you off the radar of the local authorities, It also means you&apos;re a lot easier to spot from the ground.</li>
<li>A GPS tracker can actively transmit its location from anywhere in the world. Units small enough to hide, however, aren&apos;t usually very precise, which means even though you can follow it everywhere it goes, you won&apos;t be getting much closer than a general area. That&apos;s why it&apos;s a good idea to pair your GPS tracker with a passive radio frequency identification tag. You can be sure that whatever you&apos;re looking for, you&apos;ll find it.</li>
<li>The key to getting through a high-security fence, is understanding how it works. The fence itself is usually divided into sections with a current flowing through. Cut a section, and an alarm goes off, pinpointing the location that&apos;s been tampered with. To compromise one of the sections, you have to match the precise current coming through the fence. Fortunately, electric alarms usually use intermittent pulses rather than a continuous signal, which means you can tap into the system as long as you do it in between pulses. Do it right, no one ever knows you were there.</li>
<li>Modern tracking equipment can help you follow someone without being seen, but once you&apos;ve found his base of operations, you still have to do surveillance the old-fashioned way, which sometimes means waiting.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re undercover, it&apos;s easy to dehumanize a target and see him as nothing more than a monster you&apos;re trying to take down, but sometimes they&apos;ll catch you off guard by showing you how much they care about their cause and even how much they care about you. Those are the moments you wait for as a spy because the closer they are to you, the closer you are to destroying them.</li></ul>
