<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Spies are trained to react immediately when an operation goes bad. Every minute that goes by is another minute your enemy can use to regroup and get stronger. But there are times when you have to remember that denying grief and loss and love can be dangerous too. Because, in the heat of battle you have to know what you&apos;re fighting for. </li>
<li>Most high-rises set up their phone systems floor by floor with switches called with switches called IDF&apos;s. They make maintenance easy and help manage call traffic but they&apos;re also vulnerable. Splice a line into the switch and you can make all the calls you want and no one will ever know you picked up the phone. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re preparing equipment for an unknown tactical situation, more is better. You need a range of weaponry of different sizes and calibers so that you&apos;re ready for anything from close combat to a full on gun battle. Most important of all is body armor. A good lightweight Kevlar vest can be concealed under clothing and will stop stabbing attacks, slashing attacks and almost any round short of a 50-cal. It doesn&apos;t guarantee you&apos;ll survive a surprise attack but it&apos;s a hell of a lot better than nothing. </li>
<li>The tough thing about setting up an ambush in a place of business is that it only works if the business is still running. Usually that means getting the cooperation of some very unhappy business owner, setting your team up someplace out of sight and waiting for the target to arrive. </li>
<li>The first and most important decision when you&apos;re pursuing a target is whether your goal is to capture or to kill. Of course, just because you&apos;ve decided you don&apos;t want the chase to end in bloodshed doesn&apos;t mean your target feels the same way. Once someone uses force the game changes entirely. When you know peaceful capture isn&apos;t an option you have to take the target down immediately, and if you miss the chance you may not get another one. </li>
<li>In any tactical situation where you&apos;re out-numbered and out-gunned it&apos;s essential not to let fear or panic push you into making the first move. In combat, the defender usually has the advantage. Although that can be hard to remember when you have a dozen men with high-caliber weapons on your tail. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a reason bomb makers are fussy about their work spaces. When a stray spark or dropped beaker could end more than just your career, you take every precaution to operate in a safe, stable environment. Of course, when you&apos;re in the field, you don&apos;t always get what you want. So, if you need to build improvised explosives in the back of a moving truck, you keep your head down, you stay focused and you pray that nothing blows up before it&apos;s supposed to. </li></ul>
