<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Spies aren&apos;t much into night clubs. In a career where hearing loss is a serious operational concern, and crowds of strangers have to be constantly monitored, they just don&apos;t seem like much fun.</li>
<li>Training a covert operative takes years and costs a lot of money. In theory, it&apos;s all for the tax payers who paid the bills. In practice, it&apos;s worth a lot on the open market, and when something&apos;s that valuable, there&apos;s always someone trying to sell it.</li>
<li>Spies hate drop-in visits. Any questionable contact has to be reported to superiors, a process that involves hours of paperwork and uncomfortable questions. If you&apos;re a questionable contact, that gives you some leverage. If you know where a spy operates, even a guy running a lowly import/export cover business, you can make someone&apos;s life miserable.</li>
<li>If you wanna stay alive, you have to recognize the signs of a break-in. The most skilled operative in the world won&apos;t last long if he walks into an ambush carrying a box of cereal. When a target is cornered, the best strategy is to flush them into a choke point, where they have two options: surrender, or be shot. Of course, if your target turns out to be 13-years old, carrying a dismantled pistol, it changes the tactical response somewhat.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re undercover, you often fight your emotions. If the operation demands you be a target&apos;s best friend, you do it, no matter what you&apos;re feeling. But there are times emotions can help sell a cover ID. If hitting a guy reinforces your cover, then give it all you got.</li>
<li>99% of controlling someone&apos;s behavior is controlling their environment. All the conversations in the world won&apos;t have the same impact as turning off the right light at the right time. If you want to kill a streetlight without the mess and inconvenience of breaking into the pole with a cutting torch, you need to access the circuit breaker. Connect lines from the breakers to an exposed cell phone wire, and with a quick call, you can short the circuits.  A similar trick can be used to temporarily disable a car. It doesn&apos;t take much to trip a few electronic safety mechanisms, and make a vehicle impossible to start. If you want to make sure you&apos;re the only one making calls, a hundred dollar cell phone jammer will block all signals in a one-block radius.</li>
<li>When you want to create fear, it&apos;s best to keep it simple. The same things people are afraid of as kids scare them when they&apos;re adults.  Fear of the dark, for example. Fear of being alone. And above all, fear of the unknown. </li>
<li>With today&apos;s powerful encryption, it&apos;s usually a waste of time to decipher coded communication. Tap the data stream of even a low-level spy, and you&apos;re going to get incomprehensible garbage. Just because it&apos;s garbage, doesn&apos;t mean it&apos;s worthless though. A network analyzer can tell you how much information someone&apos;s accessing and how encoded it is. If someone starts using heavy-duty crypto and changing their security protocol, you know you touched a nerve. And sometimes, that&apos;s enough to tell you what you need to know.</li>
<li>When you push someone to the point of desperation, there&apos;s always a chance they&apos;ll go looking for help, which could be a problem. Unless you&apos;re the one providing the help.</li>
<li>If you want the appearance of a gunshot without actually dying, you need to create a high-powered burst of blood. A bottle cap, packed with a bit of plastic explosive does the trick nicely. Rig a few remote charges to create the sound of a firearm, and you&apos;ve got everything you need.</li>
<li>Getting a target to do what you want requires a delicate touch. Sometimes, you&apos;re a bully, sometimes you&apos;re a friend. You have to know when to give the target help and comfort, and when to take it away.</li>
<li>When you work as a spy, follow-through is crucial. Even the best executed plan can fall apart. You don&apos;t score if you spike the ball before you&apos;re in the end-zone.</li>
<li>When a plan goes wrong, you have two basic options: the first is to accept failure and abort the mission. That works best when you have the resources and time to remove personnel from the field. When you don&apos;t have resources or time, you&apos;re left with option two: get back in there and salvage the situation any way you can. There&apos;s a long tradition in spy craft of making enemy assets appear unreliable. Make an operative look like a traitor, for example, and if you&apos;re lucky, your enemies take him out for you. Better than making an enemy look disloyal is making him look insane. It takes some doing, but when you pull it off, it&apos;s more devastating than a bullet.</li>
<li>As a spy, you often have to do things you don&apos;t like for people you don&apos;t trust. You don&apos;t always get to choose who you do business with. When the devil, himself, is offering the thing you want most, sometimes you dance with the devil.</li></ul>
