<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In the world of intelligence, if an operative hands you a crossword puzzle, chances are, you just received a coded message. It&apos;s the art of steganography: sending coded messages that don&apos;t look like messages, unless you have the key.</li>
<li>In covert ops, you always want to be the one setting the meeting. When you&apos;re following someone else&apos;s instructions, they set the agenda, they control the security, and they get to make you jump through hoops to remind you they are in charge. </li>
<li>Check fraud is more about technique than high-tech equipment. Get some old checks, a roll of scotch tape, some nail-polish remover, and you&apos;re in business. Nail-polish remover is mostly acetone, which dissolves ink. Get your hands on a check that&apos;s been filled out by the account holder, dissolve everything but the signature, and you&apos;ve got yourself a blank check. Counterfeiters call it &quot;check washing&quot;. </li>
<li>There may be no honor among thieves, but there&apos;s a certain amount of respect. Establishing you&apos;re in the same racket, is a great way to make an introduction. </li>
<li>If you wanna make a friend, solve a problem for them. No problem to solve? Create one. </li>
<li>Relationships are about trust. People trust you when they have something on you. Like, say, the name and address of a mistress in Orlando, or information about a secret gambling habit. It&apos;s all about making them feel secure. </li>
<li>People don&apos;t trust information they get for free. If you wanna sell someone on a lie, you have to make them drag it out of you. It&apos;s effective, but often painful. </li>
<li>Inexperienced operatives abandon a cover ID under pressure; experienced ones just play their roles harder. </li>
<li>Most people think distracting a group of guys is best done by a beautiful woman. The problem with beautiful women is people want them to stick around; which can cause a lot of problems. Obnoxious guys, they just want to get rid of. </li>
<li>Most assassinations involve the firing of a single well-placed bullet. The trick to selling an assassination attempt is to use a lot more fire power... and an explosion or two doesn&apos;t hurt. </li>
<li>Drug cartels have their own internal justice system. It doesn&apos;t involve courts or lawyers or proving guilt beyond a reasonable doubt. If they think you might be a traitor, they&apos;ll kill you just to be on the safe side. </li>
<li>In intelligence, a good adversary lets you think you&apos;re winning. They know the best attack is the one you don&apos;t see coming. So you learn to be vigilant when you think you&apos;ve got the upper hand. Because that&apos;s when they&apos;ll strike. </li>
<li>If you walk in on a corpse and can&apos;t catch your breath, you might be suffering from a panic attack, or someone might be pumping nitrogen gas into the room to displace all the oxygen. It&apos;s not a bad way to kill someone. They suffocate before they&apos;ve realized there&apos;s a problem. It won&apos;t show up on a tox screen, and there&apos;s no trail left behind… unless you know where to look. </li>
<li>There are a lot of disadvantages to being at the scene of a crime, you can get arrested, you can get yourself killed, and no matter how many times you&apos;ve done it, it&apos;s never fun hanging out with a dead body. But the advantage is, there&apos;s no one around to object to a little intelligence gathering. </li></ul>
