<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In any prison contraband is the rule not the exception. Candy, alcohol, even weapons are available at a steep mark-up. But there are still some things that no amount of cash, credits or cigarettes will buy you.</li>
<li>When the CIA plans the capture of a high-value target, no expense is spared. Directional microphones, fiber-optic cameras, taser guns – all the toys come out.</li>
<li>In any covert operation, the closer you get to your goal, the more collateral damage tends to arise. Just because you&apos;re dealing with one situation in a city hundreds of miles away, doesn&apos;t mean that another one won&apos;t show up on your door-step back home.</li>
<li>The motion sensor in a back yard flood light works by measuring infrared heat. When a change is detected it triggers a charge in two electrical leads that turn on the lights. With a little creative re-wiring, that same spark can transform a shotgun shell into a primitive, motion-activated zip-gun.</li>
<li>One of the hardest parts in any take-down operation is waiting for the target to show. There&apos;s nothing to do but wait and watch, knowing that even the smallest mistake can ruin everything.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re on the run the first few hours are when you&apos;re most likely to get caught. Most fugitives are caught quickly because they&apos;re trying so hard to get away that they leave a trail a mile wide. The best plan is usually to hide well and stay out of sight. Of course, it doesn&apos;t matter how well you&apos;re hidden if they have a K-9 unit that can smell you as well as see you. In that case, your best option is usually a decoy. Give the dog something to find and hope their handlers don&apos;t look to close. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re planning an operation to grab a target you want as much manpower on the ground as you can get. You want to make sure you&apos;ve covered every approach, every escape route; because, no matter how much you plan, there are always surprises. </li>
<li>Four thousand years ago, warriors disoriented their enemies by setting fire to bushels of straw soaked in grease and turning them into smoke bombs. Even though today&apos;s soldiers have traded burning crops for Hexachloroethane it doesn&apos;t mean those primitive methods aren&apos;t still effective. </li>
<li>An explosion can kill you in four different ways. There&apos;s the shock wave, the shrapnel, the fire and the oxygen depletion. The best way to survive that deadly combination of factors is to run like hell. If running isn&apos;t an option, your best bet is to create a small, air-tight space from the most flame retardant material you can find. When an explosion is headed your way, it&apos;s hard to argue with an overturned, porcelain bath tub. The brisancy, or shattering force, of a natural gas explosion is nowhere near as powerful as C-4 or RDX. But just because the blast won&apos;t kill you doesn&apos;t mean you want to live through it without proper cover. </li>
<li>As a spy, your job is to avoid detection. But there are times when you&apos;re sure to be discovered and all that&apos;s left is how and when. But that&apos;s not nothing, sometimes how and when gives your friends an awful lot of leverage. </li>
<li>A spies life is spent preparing, learning languages, researching targets, practicing with weapons. You prepare so when the important moments arrive you&apos;re ready. But there are certain moments, human moments, that no amount of training can prepare you for. </li></ul>
