<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Forging an intelligence file is always tricky. Spies are trained to catch even tiny inconsistencies. From outdated type face, to the wrong kind of thermochromatic ink. Even the folder needs to be picture perfect, because the fact is, spies do judge books by their covers.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">An effective booby trap not only needs to look like a good hiding spot, it also needs to leave your enemy incapacitated. A well-placed 50 gallon oil drum should pique your target&apos;s curiosity, and a portable defibrillator packs enough punch to make their heart skip a beat without stopping it entirely. Wire the defibrillator to a convincing decoy, and whoever comes looking will be in for a shock. Connect the camera wirelessly through an internet phone provider, and you&apos;ll be able to keep an eye on your trap from anywhere in the world without having to pay long distance.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Spies spend plenty of time with sociopaths and criminals, but sometimes it&apos;s even more dangerous to hang out with their victims. Letting your emotions get the best of you can threaten the entire operation.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">To create a blank spot in someone&apos;s memory, you need to be equal parts drinking buddy and amateur chemist. First, you need the target to party enough to make your story believable the next day. At the same time, you need to gauge their tolerance so you can combine just the right amount of alcohol with just the right amount of pharmaceutical assistance.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When your surveillance is about to be blown, you have two choices. You can run, or you can stay put and make it look like you have a reason to be there. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">There&apos;s an art to building a listening device that&apos;s meant to be discovered. It&apos;s not enough to make it look like a bug, it needs to have a fatal flaw to make sure someone finds it, like a high-frequency transmitter that causes ear-splitting feedback when placed near other electronics.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Whenever possible, it&apos;s best to avoid charging into a building filled with angry men with guns. If going in is your only option, you choose the best place to stage an ambush, lock and load, and get your enemies to come to you.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Police breaching techniques generally involve removing a door by its hinges or knocking it open with a battering ram. Military breaching techniques are more aggressive; they don&apos;t just try to get by the door, they use it as a weapon.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><strong>Sam </strong>happened to have one “old school” government folder (which they still use in Japan) so he made up an entire set of papers which “tied all the loose ends” and allowed <strong>Jesse </strong>to come to the conclusion that <strong>John Barrett</strong> was the head of the “Cabal” which he had been looking for all these years. And, for the umpteenth time <strong>Fiona </strong>inflicted us all about <em>“let’s talk about what we’re doing to Jesse”</em> M decided to play it straight with Barrett and use the private phone number Vaughn gave him to interrupt Barrett in his conference room and tell him that they had the Bible, wanted jobs and it was here in Miami <em>&quot;whenever you’re ready to talk.&quot;</em> Then he and Jesse set up a video monitored trap for the poor schmuk who Barrett sent to steal it back. Of course, Fiona manipulated M into a lunch meeting with <strong>Madeline </strong>so they both could take a shot at him over POOR, POOR JESSE and how M is HARMING HIM! <em>[see below]</em> So, unbelievably, Madeline threatened M that it had better be over soon! Remember, the fact that Jesse was staying with Madeline was forced on M by Fiona’s self-centered arrogance.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Even though she had been beating on everyone about her leaving M, she had really taken on a client and was going to have Sam help her with the case. A friend of a friend from yoga, <strong>Emily</strong>, was seduced by a scam artist, <strong>Charles Archer</strong>, who took her life’s savings. Charles was the first man she had dated after the death of her husband <strong>Josh </strong>and was swept off her feet. He offered to help her invest her insurance money and used all her account info to clean her out. Now, <em>[surprise, surprise]</em> Jesse began ragging on M about wanting to go physically after Barrett and not liking any of Ms plans. M set up a defibrillator paddle to incapacitate anyone who tried to reach into a barrel for something that looked like the Bible and watched closed circuit video for the commando to come for it.  Sam and Fiona found Charles at the bar spending Emily’s savings with a new “fish on the line.” Fiona described him as <em>“the one man from England with decent teeth.”</em> He only had a couple of DUIs and no discernable bank accounts in the US; but, he had an Interpol file for being a suspected killer. Two women who had complained about him went missing. Because his name was Charles, Fiona thought Sam needed a new cover ID; but, he told her <em>“No… </em><strong>Chuck Finley</strong><em> is forever!”</em> So, <strong>Plan A:</strong> <strong><em>Chuck </em></strong>and <strong><em>Alexis </em></strong>“accidentally” met <strong>Lindsey </strong>and Charles. Fiona said she just flew in from San Francisco and was chartering a yacht when she met Chuck. Fiona took Lindsey to the restroom so Sam could spring a con on Charles pretenting to be a fellow sleazy-womanizer and wanting to run Alexis’ money through Charles&apos; account for a fee.  No deal… so Sam actually had to physically restrain Fiona from “bulletizing” the guy. She told him that if it didn’t work out she would shoot Charles then YOU!
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">On to <strong>Plan B:</strong> They brought <strong>Michael Westen</strong> into it. Sam was going to make Charles think he got drunk and went on a spending spree so he would check his balances and they would be watching when he did. It worked, right up to the point where he was supposed to check his accounts and Fiona and Jesse tailed him to a money-laundering lawyer and were nearly caught until they pretended to be lovers.  Back at the warehouse Jesse ragged on M about the credibility of Sam’s contact and wanted to slip him some false information to test him. M countered<em> [as does every viewer watching this thing], &quot;we know Barrett wants the Bible, how much more testing do we need?!&quot;</em>  The commando, <strong>Colonel Russell</strong>, got zapped and hog-tied until his buddy called for him. Then he was released to take a copy of a page from the Bible directly to Barrett.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Now onward to <strong>Plan C:</strong> they needed to make Charles paranoid enough about his money to need to bring in help from M who would convince him he needed the account numbers to keep his money safe. Emily asked <em>“do you guys have a manual where you get this stuff?”</em> Sam told Charles that a little blue Hyundai was following him everywhere, Fiona and Jesse planted a “not so sneaky bug” in his car – which he found and Sam returned claiming that he had $100k missing from his accounts and said he had a plan to get somebody to go after the thieves. So, with a little embarrassing, Charles agreed to get the account info but his lawyer said that he had already found the leak, Emily, and was sending people to take care of her at that very moment, and a ticket to Rio for him.
</p>
</xml>
