<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Covert operatives have a hard time dating. Even if you find someone who doesn&apos;t mind that you won&apos;t talk about your past, or that you carry a concealed weapon, they usually want more than you&apos;re able to give. </li>
<li>Selling stolen goods is all about discretion. You&apos;ve got to be the kind of person who can keep your mouth shut... the kind of person who never, ever shares the numbers in their little black book. </li>
<li>Even the most careful spy leaves a trail that could get them burned. A patriot making illicit deals for his government looks a lot like a traitor, making black-market sales for his wallet. Somebody upstairs gets the wrong idea, and suddenly you&apos;re burned, and out of a job. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re giving five inches, and a hundred pounds to a well trained opponent, it helps to know the terrain better than he does. </li>
<li>A good cover identity is a team effort. If you want to meet someone, it&apos;s a good idea to play a little hard to get. Put people between yourself and the target. Make them come to you. </li>
<li>Just because someone believes you are who you say you are, doesn&apos;t mean he&apos;ll do what you want him to do. </li>
<li>Clandestine meetings are never fun to arrange. It&apos;s a big part of the job for a covert operative, but it&apos;s never pleasant... It&apos;s not so much the fear of death that bothers you, it&apos;s driving to the meet with a bag over your head. Sometimes they wash the bag, sometimes they don&apos;t. </li>
<li>The thing about security, is that the very things that protect you, can be turned against you by someone who knows what he&apos;s doing. It&apos;s tough to compromise a well thought out security system, but making someone think you can compromise it, well, that&apos;s much easier. Take surveillance cameras, for example, you can disable one by shooting a laser at it and overloading the light-sensitive chip. Cheap, easy, and exactly the sort of thing a sophisticated criminal gang, with lots of resources, would do. Leave around some tell-tale signs of surveillance like cigarette butts, a forgotten camera lens cap, and the more security there is, the more likely they are to think they&apos;ve got a very serious problem. Even the security team itself can be an opportunity. The more employees you have, the more you have to worry about. Deliver some vague threats and a few hundred bucks to a security guard. If he&apos;s honest, he&apos;ll tell his boss, who then wonders who wasn&apos;t so honest. For the cost of a nice dinner, you can get a whole security team canned.</li>
<li>One of the dangers of any kind of psychological warfare, is it can be too effective, and send the target into a paranoid tail-spin. That paranoia can be useful... or deadly.</li>
<li>The key to good security, is good systems, consistency. But those very systems make you predictable. Where will you take your valuables? A bank you trust. How are you going to get there? With armed men in a big SUV. When will you go? When the bank is least crowded. All good procedure; all one hundred percent predictable.</li>
<li>If you know someone&apos;s going to be at a bank at a particular time, it&apos;s not hard to make it look like they&apos;re robbing the bank. Shoot out a few video surveillance cameras. Block off the street with a stolen car, like they&apos;re preparing an escape route. Fire up a spark-gap transmitter to kill the security radios at the bank, and they&apos;ll really look like they know what they&apos;re doing.</li></ul>
