<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Every spy lives in fear of losing himself. When you work undercover, the lines between loyalty and betrayal can become so blurred, so grey, that after a while, you don&apos;t know what you&apos;re fighting for anymore. You end up caught in the middle as your friends become your enemies and your enemies become your friends. Until the time comes when you&apos;re forced to make a choice.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In the field, there&apos;s nothing harder then when you let your team down. Apologies and regrets do no good, you all have to move on and make the best of the situation. It&apos;s crucial to stay focused. To try to keep your mind off the past. But there are times when that&apos;s just not possible.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As an operative, it&apos;s your job to determine how likely a particular plan is to succeed, and if something looks like a suicide mission, to call it off. Of course, that only matters if you care whether you live or die.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">A spy&apos;s ability to operate depends on secrecy. Your anonymity is your greatest weapon. It allows you to operate anywhere, to deceive your enemies, and when it&apos;s all over, to slip back into the shadows. When the world knows your face, your options get a lot more limited. At that point, all you can really do is attack.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Grabbing someone on the move is all about surprise. The goal is to get your target out of his car and into yours before he knows what&apos;s happening. If you have the manpower, it&apos;s best to separate into two teams. One to track the target&apos;s car and one to prepare the ambush.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Small explosive charges won&apos;t penetrate an armored car, but that doesn&apos;t mean they&apos;re useless. If you&apos;re desperate enough, a well-placed charge can come in handy. Since an armored car won&apos;t drive if it&apos;s wheels aren&apos;t on the ground
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When breaking into a building, it&apos;s generally best not to use the door. Any entrance your enemy knows you&apos;d use is too risky. Which means the safest way is often the hardest.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">A spy is never truly done being a spy until he&apos;s dead. It&apos;s part of you. The skills, the secrets, they never go away. And as long as you can be useful to someone, it&apos;s your fate to always be a spy. But if there&apos;s one things spies are bad at, it&apos;s accepting fate.
</p>
</xml>
