<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">On an undercover assignment, there&apos;s no substitute for building trust. It&apos;s not just a matter of getting to know someone superficially. To be really effective, you need to get as close to the target as you can. Both personally, and professionally. It&apos;s never easy. No matter how much training you have, it&apos;s difficult to become someone&apos;s closest friend, knowing that you&apos;re only doing it to steal their deepest secrets. Once you&apos;ve developed a relationship with the target, you can start to use that relationship to get the information you need. If you&apos;re close enough, you can make an interrogation feel like nothing more than innocent questions from a trusted friend. Sometimes it&apos;s not enough to be a target&apos;s friend, however. Sometimes, to accomplish a mission, you have to go further. When you share a target&apos;s bed, when they trust you enough to sleep beside you, it&apos;s a simple thing to get whatever information you need. That information comes with a price, though. Often, the only way to convince someone that you care about them, is to actually start caring about them. And no matter how important the mission is, no matter how much you believe in your cause, it feels like what it is: a complete betrayal of someone&apos;s trust.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As a spy, you get used to the idea that every successful operation comes at a price. Sometimes it&apos;s lives lost, other times it&apos;s cities destroyed or livelihoods ruined. Then there are other costs that are more personal. Less obvious, but the pain is just as real.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">No matter how much you&apos;ve trained, no matter how much you&apos;ve planned, there&apos;s always anxiety in the moments before you capture a target. Most things are simply out of your control. Your operations team may be monitoring the situation, but they&apos;re usually too far away to do much but watch. Your extraction team is there to do one job, and one job only: acquire the targets. Which effectively leaves you alone. At the end of the day, all you can do is smile, play along, and try not to get killed when the shooting starts.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When you&apos;re undercover and running from your own capture team, you have to make it look like you&apos;re trying to escape. But at the same time, you have to create a trail for your friends to find. Cell phones can be tracked, which means if you can keep one close by, it gives your team a shot at finding you. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">With little government oversight and a booming private sector, Mexico has one of the most unregulated airspaces in Latin America. Bad news for safety and air pollution, but good news if you need to conduct a manhunt without the local authorities finding out. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">There&apos;s a reason helicopters are the search vehicles of choice for every law enforcement agency in the world. When you can travel 150 miles an hour on any axis, with 60 miles of visibility, there&apos;s virtually nowhere for your target to hide. The down-side of using a helicopter is that when you&apos;re surrounded by nothing but sky, there&apos;s nowhere for you to hide either. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Since the Vietnam War, helicopters have given technologically superior forces a huge advantage on the battlefield. In almost every situation, your target&apos;s only move is to run and hide. But as everyone from the Viet Cong to the Mujahideen has learned, a helicopter&apos;s main defense is it&apos;s maneuverability. And if they can force you into hovering over a tight space, like a valley between two mountains, or an alley between two buildings, they can make you an easy target.  
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As a spy, you&apos;re supposed to accomplish a mission no matter what it costs. There comes a point, though, where that&apos;s not possible anymore. When you&apos;re pushed to the breaking point, and beyond.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When you&apos;re trying to save someone from an enemy with superior numbers, the challenge is being in two places at the same time. A well-placed directional charge will take out windows, walls, and anyone standing near them. Timed precisely, it can give you the chance to attack both sides of a structure at once. If it works, you take out all the hostiles inside before they can hurt the people you&apos;re trying to save. If it doesn&apos;t, you create one hell of a death trap.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The thing that keeps you going in a deep-cover mission is knowing that you&apos;re fighting for something you believe in. That the people you work for have your back. But when your own side betrays what they claim to stand for, when they&apos;re willing to do things even your enemies wouldn&apos;t dream of, everything starts to fall apart. And when it comes down to that final moment, sometimes you can surprise even yourself.  
</p>
</xml>
