<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In the spy world, often the only things you know about a covert mission are your deployment orders and a list of equipment to bring. Sometimes, that tells you nothing. And sometimes, it can tell a lot. The make of your weapon tells you if you&apos;ll be in open combat, or firing from the shadows. The ammunition you&apos;re bringing can indicate whether you&apos;re there primarily to defend, or to kill. When you&apos;re leaving under cover of darkness, under a false name, you can be sure that whatever the job is, it won&apos;t be pretty.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Whenever possible, spies like to know what they&apos;re getting into before they leave for a mission. When you ship out without orders, you can&apos;t really train or prepare. All you can do is wait and wonder what&apos;s coming.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">No one&apos;s more careful about security than a freelance spy. When you work in intelligence and you don&apos;t have the protection of a government, you have to assume that everyone is a potential enemy. Even your closest friends. A careful operative will have security as good as most military installations. Vehicles will be searched for explosives. And of course, nothing that fires a bullet or sends an electronic signal makes it past the gate. Bottom line: By the time you get inside, the only thing you&apos;ll be armed with is a warm smile.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When you&apos;re in the field, having direct contact with your control officer is supposed to be a last resort. The risk of being seen together is enormous. If something goes wrong, people die. If you&apos;re willing to take that risk, everyone knows it&apos;s serious.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Roadside improvised explosive devices come in many varieties. But they usually share basic features. Once a target vehicle is chosen, an explosive device is planted in the vehicle&apos;s path, and then detonated by remote control as soon as the vehicle is in position. Of course, that assumes that your target isn&apos;t using a signal jammer. The problem with signal jammers is they don&apos;t just make it impossible to remotely trigger a detonator, they also make it impossible to communicate with your team. And when you can&apos;t communicate, bad things usually happen.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When a plan goes wrong in the field, the job is rarely abandoned entirely. The goals of the mission don&apos;t change, the methods do. The problem is back-up plans are usually that for a reason. They tend to be a lot messier and a lot more deadly.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As a spy, you have to get used to deception. Your job is to engage with people, make them your friends, manipulate them. And ultimately, destroy them. It&apos;s one thing to do it to your enemies. You can think of your target in terms that aren&apos;t exactly human, like mission objectives. But when the target is a friend, it doesn&apos;t matter what you tell yourself. It feels like betrayal.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><b>Main</b>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><b>Recurring</b>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><b>Guest</b>
</p>
</xml>
