<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>There aren&apos;t many rules in the spy trade. There are a few &quot;agreements&quot; that most intelligence agencies honor though. Low-level agents get traded, not prosecuted. You don&apos;t shoot foreign operatives if you can avoid it. And you stay away from embassies and consulates. </li>
<li>Consulates are a great place to renew your visa, pay your taxes back home or find foreign spies working under diplomatic cover. Like all bureaucrats, consulate employees live in fear of a pissed off journalist.</li>
<li>Most of the people who work in a consulate are just municipal drones enjoying an overseas post. But the head of security? That guy&apos;s almost always a spy. </li>
<li>One job of a security chief is babysitting the secrets. If one goes missing, it&apos;s a big deal. Even if it&apos;s just transactional data on chemical imports. Steal a few files, no matter how boring, and you&apos;ve got leverage. Play your cards right and you can trade what you&apos;ve got for what you want. </li>
<li>In any covert operation, your first concern is remaining undetected. Whether you&apos;re infiltrating a military base or getting car parts from your mom&apos;s garage without her knowing, staying invisible is tough. And no matter how good you are... sometimes they&apos;re better. </li>
<li>Exploiting an asset is easier when they have a vice: an addiction you can feed. Drugs, money, respect, women. </li>
<li>If you need to get into a secure area, the best approach is to give yourself a good reason to be there. Why sneak past guards when you can just spill a martini? </li>
<li>A hairpin is one of the most versatile tools in a thief&apos;s arsenal. It&apos;s as good as a key most of the time; but not when the lock is a magnetic card reader. </li>
<li>The key to hand-to-hand combat is being able to close the distance between you and your opponent without putting them on their guard. </li>
<li>There are two schools of safe cracking. Some people like to beat the lock, some people like to break the lock. But it doesn&apos;t matter when the safe is sitting wide open. Good counterfeit money is more expensive than you think. If you&apos;re looking to fake money on the cheap, a real bill bound to a stack of filler will do. </li>
<li>Thirty years ago, the CIA would&apos;ve killed for bugs as small as cell phones. They&apos;re the perfect improvised listening device but they burn juice like a Humvee. If there&apos;s no charger handy, an unused USB port will do the trick. </li>
<li>To win a negotiation, you have to show you&apos;re willing to walk away. And the best way to show you&apos;re willing to walk away, is to walk away. </li>
<li>They say a picture&apos;s worth a thousand words. Add in a few hundred that survive the censor&apos;s black pen, suddenly, you&apos;ve really got something. </li></ul>
