<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Whether you&apos;re hunting down extremists in the mountains of Kashmir or tracking arms dealers through the streets of Moscow, the life of a spy takes a toll. So during down times, you work out, eat right, and try to recharge your batteries because you never know what&apos;s waiting for you around the next corner. </li>
<li>Smart criminals have a variety of ways to find out if a meeting is under police surveillance. Some are more subtle than others. Throw a few punches and any cops in the area have to come running. </li>
<li>Behavior in a combat situation is unpredictable. Sometimes trained soldiers go screaming for the hills. Sometimes guys who&apos;ve never fired anything bigger than a cap gun, turn out to have ice in their veins.  </li>
<li>In the field, it&apos;s often your human instincts that jeopardize an operation. Helping people is great, but there are times that impulse can get people killed. Sometimes the right thing to do is let a guy bleed for a while. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re concerned you might be walking into a police stakeout, there are a number of things to look out for: Parked cars or vans, workers that seem unusually preoccupied, and curious kids. No matter where you go in the world, little boys like candy, puppies and cops. </li>
<li>When it comes to cover ID&apos;s, impersonating a bad cop is much better than impersonating a good one. An honest cop follows policies and procedures; from the way he cuts his hair, to the approach he takes when carrying out a traffic stop. Pose as a good cop, and you have to go by the book. Pose as a bad cop, and you can throw out that book and write your own. </li>
<li>In the criminal world, selling yourself as a colleague often means doing something illegal. So while snorting lactose isn&apos;t pleasant- it may put people&apos;s minds at ease. </li>
<li>Interrogation professionals don&apos;t ask questions directly. They hide what they know and don&apos;t know. Amateurs tend to ask for exactly what they want. It&apos;s like playing poker with your cards showing. </li>
<li>When people are desperate for information, they start filling in the blanks, often without realizing it. It&apos;s something fortune tellers rely on. It works pretty much the same way for spies. Although fortune tellers usually don&apos;t get smacked around as much. </li>
<li>Searching for a concealed enemy who could be anywhere is a waste of time. Usually, your best bet is to stay put and give your enemy a reason to come to you. </li>
<li>To tail someone, you need both skill and instinct. You need skill because the driving is tough. You can&apos;t get too close, and you can&apos;t drift too far away. You can&apos;t go too fast or too slow. You need instinct because every turn, every lane change, every bridge, raises the risk of being seen. Anyone can be trained to follow a car but it takes good instincts to know when it&apos;s time to stop following.</li>
<li>When you work with someone long enough, you learn to trust them. When things go bad, that trust is the difference between life and death. Of course, knowing that doesn&apos;t make it less terrifying; to back a play you know nothing about. </li>
<li>Every profession has occupational hazards. Butchers cut themselves, house painters fall off ladders and operatives get asked to help kill their own people.</li>
<li>People underestimate the tactical importance of TV in urban warfare. Guard duty&apos;s boring, and a ball game passes the time better than, say, looking for intruders. More battles have been decided by pennant races than people imagine.</li>
<li>It&apos;s always best to have business arguments unarmed. When tempers are high and everyone&apos;s got a gun, you never know what&apos;s going to set someone off. </li>
<li>When a front door is being watched, your best option often times is just to make a back door. If you don&apos;t mind getting damp, a water saw is a great tool for the job. It will cut through the wall much more quietly than a metal saw and won&apos;t ignite anything flammable that happens to be lying around.</li></ul>
