<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>There&apos;s a fine line between healthy caution, and paranoia. When you&apos;re under stress, your awareness is heightened, making it easier to spot potential dangers. Unfortunately, stress can also make it hard to tell when a danger is real, and when it&apos;s just a figment of your imagination.</li>
<li>When running surveillance, you&apos;re trained to view your targets not as people, but as a list of details in an activity log. When they come home, when they leave, how many calls they make. You have to discipline yourself not to get emotionally involved in the life of the subject. But sometimes the subject makes that impossible. The hardest part about doing surveillance on someone you know, is staying objective. Work can quickly become very personal when everything about the person you&apos;re watching, every look, every gesture, reminds you of the past.</li>
<li>The average hit-rate for a trained marksman firing at a target from 50 feet under ideal conditions is over 99%. Of course, that assumes you can see your target. If you&apos;re under fire and shooting blind, that hit rate drops to about zero.</li>
<li>Being an effective sniper is less about firing your weapon than it is about choosing your location. An ideal sniper perch allows you to estimate range accurately, gauge wind velocity and direction, and keep your weapon stable. The goal is to control as many variables as possible so when your target shows up, all you have to do is pull the trigger. (technically not part of the dialogue, it did appear in the close captioning code in the American broadcast of the show.)</li>
<li>In the field, snipers can spend hours, sometimes even days, waiting to take just one shot. But no matter how diligently you work to stay focused on the task, at some point your mind is going to wander.</li>
<li>Finding someone who&apos;s been abducted is a race against the clock. Each minute that passes increases the area you have to search. If you know the vehicle the kidnapper is driving, the chances of catching them rise significantly. Which is why a smart kidnapper&apos;s first move is to burn his vehicle.</li>
<li>When someone is put in danger as a result of an operation going bad, there are a number of questions that have to be answered. What went wrong? Is there anything you could have done differently? And of course the one question no one wants to ask, is it your fault?</li>
<li>An operative is trained to maintain cover under all circumstances. When the mission requires keeping your identity a secret, you&apos;re supposed to follow orders and stay out of sight. That&apos;s easy when you&apos;re spying on enemies. But it&apos;s a very different thing when you&apos;re spying on friends. When maintaining cover means allowing people you care about to walk right into a death trap, you have a choice to make: risk the operation, or risk your friends&apos; lives.</li>
<li>In a hostage situation, tactical data is usually the most important. Your focus is on details like the building&apos;s entry points and blind spots, your target&apos;s potential escape routes, and your team&apos;s assault capabilities. But sometimes, even more important than your knowledge of the situation, is what you know about the person you are trying to save.</li></ul>
