<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Covert intelligence involves a lot of waiting around. Know what its like being a spy? Like sitting at your dentist&apos;s reception area 24 hours a day. You read magazines, sip coffee, and every so often; someone tries to kill you.</li>
<li>[He&apos;s CIA] What do you say to that? No? Explain that a lot of spies don&apos;t work directly for the CIA? Lot of good that will do.</li>
<li>Sometimes the truth hurts. In these situations, I recommend lying.</li>
<li>In a fight, you have to be careful not to break the little bones in your hand on someone&apos;s face. That&apos;s why I like bathrooms. Lots of hard surfaces. </li>
<li>Southern Nigeria isn&apos;t my favorite place in the world. It&apos;s unstable, it&apos;s corrupt, and the people there eat a lot of terrible smelling preserved fish. I will say this for Nigeria, though: it&apos;s the gun-running capital of Africa. And that makes it a bad place to drive a passenger sedan into a crowded market.</li>
<li>If you&apos;re gonna collapse on a plane, I recommend business class. The seats are bigger if you start convulsing. Although once you pass out, it really doesn&apos;t matter.</li>
<li>Most people would be thrilled to be dumped in Miami. Sadly, I am not most people. Spend a few years as a covert operative and a sunny beach just looks like a vulnerable tactical position with no decent cover. I&apos;ve never found a good way to hide a gun in a bathing suit.</li>
<li>When a spy gets fired, he doesn&apos;t get a call from a lady in HR and a gold watch. They cut him off. They make sure he can never work again. They can&apos;t take away his skills or what&apos;s in his head, so they take away the resources that allow him to function They &quot;burn&quot; him.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re being watched, what you need is contrast. A background that will make the surveillance stand out. An FBI field office is full of guys in their forties. At most South Beach business hotels, it would be tough to tell which middle-aged white guy was watching you. So you stay in the place where everyone is a Jell-O shot away from alcohol poisoning. If you see someone who can walk a straight line, that&apos;s the Fed.</li>
<li>Need to go someplace you&apos;re not wanted? Any uniform store will sell you a messenger outfit, and any messenger can get past a security desk.</li>
<li>With this much money, things get complicated. Change a light bulb in a place like this, and a week later you&apos;re on a speedboat in the Cayman Islands with someone shooting at you.</li>
<li>My mom would&apos;ve been a great NSA communications operative. Drop me in the middle of the Gobi Desert - bury me in a goddamn cave on the moon - and somehow, she&apos;d find a way to call me and ask me for a favor.</li>
<li>I don&apos;t like stealing cars, but sometimes it&apos;s necessary. I have rules, though: I&apos;ll keep it clean, and if I take your car on a workday, I&apos;ll have it back by five.</li>
<li>Figuring out if a car is tailing you is mostly about driving like you&apos;re an idiot. You speed up, slow down, signal one way, turn the other. Of course, ideally, you&apos;re doing this without your mother in the car... Actually, losing a tail isn&apos;t about driving fast. A high-speed pursuit is just gonna land you on the six o&apos;clock news. So you just keep driving like an idiot until the other guy makes a mistake. Again, all this is easier without a passenger yelling at you for missing a decades worth of Thanksgivings.</li>
<li>Sleep through an aerial bombing or two, and noise isn&apos;t an issue. You just need some privacy and a bed. In a pinch, you can lose the bed. But the privacy&apos;s important for projects like this one. With everyone X-raying and chemical testing their mail these days, a box of wire and pipe and batteries sprinkled with chemical fertilizer is a great attention-getter.</li>
<li>Whether you&apos;re a coke dealer, a thief, an arms dealer, or a spy, you need someone to clean your money. Which makes a good money launderer the closest thing you can get to a Yellow Pages for criminals. Even better, a money launderer will always take your phone call. Burn notice or no burn notice.</li>
<li>Doesn&apos;t matter how much training you have. A broken rib is a broken rib.</li>
<li>I never run around in the bushes in a ski mask when I&apos;m breaking in someplace. If somebody catches you, what are you gonna say? You want to look like a legitimate visitor until the very last minute. If you can&apos;t look legit, confused works almost as well. Maybe get a soda from the fridge, or a yogurt. If you&apos;re caught, you just act confused and apologize like crazy for taking the yogurt - nothing could be more innocent.</li>
<li>Cracking an old-school safe is pretty tough, but modern hi-tech security makes it much easier. Thing is, nobody wipes off a fingerprint scanner after they use it. So what&apos;s left on the scanner nine times out of ten is the fingerprint.</li>
<li>Fighting for the little guy is for suckers. We all do it once in a while, but the trick is to get in and out quickly, without getting involved. That&apos;s one trick I never really mastered.</li>
<li>Powerful people don&apos;t like being pushed around. You can never quite predict what they&apos;re going to do. Or have their washed-out special forces security guys do. Point is, blackmail is a little like owning a pit bull; it might protect you, or it might bite your hand off. That&apos;s why it pays to make sure you know what they&apos;re thinking, and that means - eavesdropping.</li>
<li>To build a listening device, you need a crappy phone with a mic that picks up everything. But you want the battery power and circuits of a better phone. It&apos;s a trick you learn when the purchasing office won&apos;t spring for a bug.</li>
<li>Once somebody sends a guy with a gun after you, things are only going to get worse. But like it or not, you&apos;ve got work to do. For a job like getting rid of the drug dealer next door, I&apos;ll take a hardware store over a gun any day. Guns make you stupid. Better to fight your wars with duct tape. Duct tape makes you smart. Every decent punk has a bulletproof door. But people forget walls are just plaster. Hopefully you get him with the first shot. Or the second... Now he&apos;s down and waiting for you to come through the front door. So you don&apos;t come through the front door.</li>
<li>People with happy families don&apos;t become spies. A bad childhood is the perfect background for covert ops. You don&apos;t trust anyone, you&apos;re used to getting smacked around, and you never get homesick.</li>
<li>Thirty years of karate, combat experience on five continents, a rating with every weapon that shoots a bullet or holds an edge; still haven&apos;t found any defense against Mom crying into my shirt. </li>
<li>Airbags save a lot of lives. But they also put you out long enough to get your hands cable-tied to the steering wheel.</li>
<li>When you work solo, it&apos;s about prepping the ground. Home-court advantage counts for a lot. You never know what&apos;s going to happen. You prepare for everything. Most bad guys expect you to just sit there and wait for them, like those are the *rules* or something.</li>
<li>If you&apos;re going to put prints on a gun, sticking it into somebody&apos;s hand isn&apos;t going to do it. Any decent lawyer can explain prints on a gun. But try explaining prints on the inside of the trigger assembly.</li>
<li>As a spy, it doesn&apos;t matter if you&apos;re helping rebel forces fight off a dictator, or giving combat tips to a third-grader. There&apos;s nothing like helping the little guy kick some bully&apos;s ass.</li>
<li>There&apos;s nothing worse for a spook than knowing you&apos;re being played. Someone is pulling strings. Who? Not some intelligence agency bureaucrat in a cubicle. This is someone with more - style. Not FBI either, they&apos;re not this creative and they don&apos;t do surveillance on their own guys. This is someone who knows what he&apos;s doing; someone who wants to send a message: Welcome to Miami.</li></ul>
