<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In any operation, communicating silently is often essential. Chalk marks, an unusual arrangement of objects, anything that stands out from the background will do. A piece of cloth on a window… </li>
<li>A warehouse door is going to be reinforced, but the walls aren&apos;t. And the areas under the windows don&apos;t have load bearing beams. </li>
<li>A good trap doesn&apos;t scare people, it makes them curious. A speeding truck makes people scatter. A slow moving truck on the other hand, makes people want to take a closer look. </li>
<li>For any operative, stashing weapons is second nature after a while. Spies hide guns like squirrels hide acorns. You never know when you&apos;ll need some firepower, or where you&apos;ll be when you need it.</li>
<li>Choosing a cover I.D. on-the-fly is always a challenge. When there&apos;s no time to think, it&apos;s best to go with something simple that keeps your options open. </li>
<li>Freon is available at most computer stores. Buy a can of screen duster, turn it upside-down, and you&apos;ve got it in liquid form. It&apos;s cold enough to crystallize the metal in many commercial locks. A hammer can take care of the rest. </li>
<li>One advantage of working with the same team is that secure communication is simpler. You don&apos;t have to work out a secret code. If you have enough history, the code is in every picture, every memento, every autographed leg cast.</li>
<li>Surveillance is a two-way street. If you know someone&apos;s looking for you, you&apos;ve got an advantage. They follow <i>your </i>lead, go where they <i>think </i>you are.</li>
<li>Who drives armored cars? People who expect gun-fire. Usually people with some fire-power of their own.</li>
<li>In a hostage situation, you have to be cruel to be kind. The more you care, the more leverage they have. Like buying a car, you have to make them think you can walk away.</li>
<li>There are some fights you just can&apos;t win. A force can be so overwhelming that no tactical approach in a fight is going to lead to a victory worth having... When you can&apos;t win in a fight, sometimes you have to settle for making sure that if you lose, everyone loses. It works for nuclear weapons; it works for me.</li>
<li>The sticky bomb was originally developed in World War II for mining tanks. For the homemade variety, tile adhesive works best - sticky, water-proof, and it comes in an easily portable plastic bucket.</li>
<li>A lot of people think the word commando means super-hero, or at least something close to it. In the popular mind, they&apos;re thought of as the ultimate elite soldier, the solution to every problem. The fact is, a commando is just someone trained to fight under a specific set of circumstances. He&apos;s the guy you send in when there are more bad guys than good guys, when surprise is the only advantage you can get in an operation. When it works, commandos seem unstoppable. Those are the operations that make the papers. When it doesn&apos;t work, commandos get killed just as dead as anyone else.</li>
<li>When you work in intelligence, you get used to the idea that some information is worth risking everything for. You sign up for the lifestyle, or the chance to serve your country, or the millions of frequent-flier miles. But finally, it all comes down to putting your ass on the line to learn something.</li></ul>
