<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>You want to blend into a new city, you better be up on local sports.</li>
<li>Covert ops has its perks. You travel, make your own hours and expense most of your meals. The downside? Lots of people want you dead. </li>
<li>If it looks like you&apos;re about to get into a fight that could get you killed, try starting another one. </li>
<li>When booby-trapping your home, it&apos;s important to keep it simple. Make it easy to set up, easy to disable. </li>
<li>One more thing about booby traps. Make sure your friends know not to drop by unannounced. </li>
<li>You can learn good self-defense fighting with students in a class, but great self-defense - that you pick up fighting with your family. </li>
<li>Spies go to bars for the same reason people go to libraries – full of information, if you know how to ask. </li>
<li>The key to a good knife defense is to control the knife hand and strike with everything you&apos;ve got. </li>
<li>Fighting is often about tactical retreats like running away from two knives. It&apos;s also about knowing how to make the body count unacceptable. </li>
<li>Pimps are all about show. High end or low end, they like to stand out. </li>
<li>Compulsive gamblers get a lot of practice seeing people bluff so the good news is they can usually pick up on people&apos;s tells. The bad news is when they&apos;re wrong, the consequences are very expensive. </li>
<li>Any good operative is careful not to leave much behind. Everyone gets careless though, and even the littlest things can turn out to be useful. A receipt, a paperback, room service records. Every bit helps. </li>
<li>A rescue attempt is hard enough when it&apos;s someone who actually wants to be rescued. It doesn&apos;t matter whether it&apos;s a brother with a compulsive gambling problem or a girl who thinks she&apos;s about to launch her modeling career. So you eliminate escape options, keep a low profile, but no matter what you do, you&apos;ll still have someone screaming bloody murder in the back of your car. </li>
<li>Some situations just come down to probabilities – the chance that an assassin with a handgun can hit you at 50 yards, and the number of shots he can get off might have a one-in-five chance of taking a bullet, and maybe a one-in-10 chance of dying. Or a hundred percent chance of getting blown away by a shotgun wired to a door. A ricochet&apos;s usually not deadly, but it sure feels that way. </li>
<li>Any decent criminal will change his plans at mention of the word &quot;cops&quot;. </li>
<li>Spend a lot of time in countries without hospitals, you pick up a few things. </li>
<li>Running an operation, you can&apos;t let personal feelings get in the way. It&apos;s about planning and execution. Not about being angry. Although occasionally you may get a little angry. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a reason family&apos;s always a good source of leverage. Whether it&apos;s a brother that always owes people money, or a brother stuck in the trunk of a car. You can&apos;t really turn your back on them. </li>
<li>The drive home is often a grueling experience for someone you just rescued, especially if they were unaware of their situation. They ask a lot of questions, you fill them in on the answers. And then it dawns on them. The truth. It can be a little overwhelming.</li></ul>
