<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Get your hands on any classified document worth having, chances are it&apos;s going to be redacted, which makes reading it a lot like watching a movie on an airplane. All the juicy parts are missing, but you still get the basic idea. </li>
<li>Jobs in agriculture are a convenient cover; makes it easy to explain your presence in the field and the boardroom; the only downside is, you might have to become an expert on chickpeas.</li>
<li>You can tell a lot about who&apos;s following you by the maneuvers they use. Quick, evasive driving, a casual bailout, feigning car trouble, these are signs you&apos;re dealing with a professional. Smashing into a rickshaw like a crash test dummy, that&apos;s a sign you&apos;re dealing with an amateur, somebody who doesn&apos;t know what he&apos;s doing. That&apos;s when you really got a problem. </li>
<li>Cultivating intelligence assets usually requires some wining and dining. The more connected somebody is, the more they know, the more they feel entitled to a little special treatment. </li>
<li>Smart operatives know how to steer the conversation towards the information they need. Clever assets, on the other hand know how to make the wine-and-dine phase last as long as possible. </li>
<li>Stun guns are a great way to bring down a larger opponent. The only problem is, if you use one on someone who is touching you, you&apos;ll zap yourself too. </li>
<li>A lot of people&apos;s first instinct when they need information out of a captive is to grab a baseball bat or a gun. The fact is, torture is for sadists and thugs. It&apos;s like getting groceries with a flamethrower. It doesn&apos;t work, and it makes a mess. Getting useful information is about creating a new reality for the interrogation subject with no hope of escape or freedom. You control every aspect of their world: how they eat, where they sleep, even whether it&apos;s day or night. When it&apos;s time to ask questions, you want them disoriented, anxious, wondering who you are and what you can do to them. You have to make them understand that their entire future, their hopes, their dreams, and every breath they will ever take from then on, it all depends on one thing: Talking.</li>
<li>It&apos;s unfortunate but true, that no makeup can simulate blood and bruises well enough to stand up to close observation. So if your cover requires looking like you&apos;ve been beaten, you have to get beaten. </li>
<li>It can take a lifetime to convince someone to trust you. It&apos;s much quicker to make them feel like they need you to trust them. </li>
<li>A fight is one of the quickest ways to tell if someone isn&apos;t who they say they are. If you say you&apos;re Russian, but fight like an American, you can consider your cover blown. Which means you&apos;d better know Sambo, the mixed martial art of Russia. Of course, you also have to <i>win</i> the fight. A great cover I.D. doesn&apos;t help much if you&apos;re dead. </li>
<li>A thermal camera is a great tool for scouting. It&apos;ll tell you where the warm bodies are in a building or which rooms are designed to make those bodies invisible.</li>
<li>One issue in dealing with modern criminal gangs, is that their operations are diversified. The heat shielding you hope is hiding a human smuggling operation, could be hiding radio emissions from software pirating computers. </li>
<li>A good interrogator paints a picture of the world outside for a detainee. Whatever he&apos;s holding on to, you take it away. His organization? Crumbling. His friends? Traitors. His precious information? Useless. </li>
<li>Working an information source is a delicate art. Ideally, you can get all the information you need with kind words and free drinks. When drinks and good company aren&apos;t enough, however, a good operative has to apply pressure and that means knowing just what a source loves. </li>
<li>One of the hardest things to do in a fight is to make it look like you&apos;re trying to kill someone without doing permanent damage. They don&apos;t teach any half-moves in combat training. There are moves designed to kill and maim as efficiently as possible. If those are off-limits, one option is opening your fist right before a punch lands. Painful, but the force is distributed. Another showy option is a kick to the shoulder. It might break a rib or two but if you aim right, nobody&apos;s going to the morgue. </li>
<li>In the spy game, you spend a lot of time getting people to betray their own. Most do it for money. Some do it for spite. But the greatest achievement is to get a guy to turn on his own people because he thinks he&apos;s being loyal. </li>
<li>Intelligence gathering isn&apos;t all running around with a gun and a spy camera. When the operation demands it, you get to sit in a hot car with no air-conditioning in downtown Miami. </li></ul>
