<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>A fake identity is known in the spy trade as a &quot;false flag&quot;. Used to be you could make your own documents with a printer and a laminator. These days though, ID&apos;s have magnetic strips, holograms, and infrared water marks. You need a pro. </li>
<li>In some situations, a tactical retreat is your best option... A guy with a gun, is a guy with a gun. You can fight him and risk someone getting shot, or wait for back-up.</li>
<li>Corporations need spies just like governments do. Of course they&apos;re not called spies, they&apos;re called security consultants. They are basically mercenaries with nice suits.</li>
<li>One of the things you learn in training is to avoid situations that cut too close. If you had a rough childhood, a situation with an abusive father and a vulnerable kid is gonna make you angry. That could be motivating. But it can also be dangerous.</li>
<li>Facts are the hallmark of a good false identity. It&apos;s harder to create history, than it is to alter it. Plus, the more truth to your lie, the easier it is to remember. </li>
<li>Just because there are no windows or doors doesn&apos;t mean there are no exits. The thing to look for is an air conditioner unit, that&apos;s where the wall is weakest. Also people watch doors, they don&apos;t watch air conditioners. </li>
<li>A basic rule of covert ops, is let someone else do your dirty work. Let someone else find the guy you want to kill. It&apos;s a great technique, as long as you&apos;re not - the someone else.</li>
<li>Remove the trigger bar spring from a SIG-Sauer P228, and you&apos;ve got a 9mm semi-automatic door stop.</li>
<li>Shoot a propane tank and you&apos;ll just get a big cloud of cold gas. You need an open flame, and real good aim. </li>
<li>Assassination is one percent shooting, ninety-nine percent preparation: anticipating moves, devising approaches, recruiting sources, finding the perfect opportunity so the bullet&apos;s almost an after-thought. Usually that&apos;s when a target&apos;s on the move, when there are too many variables to control them all... There are ways to lessen the risk: an armed escort, taking an unpredictable route to your destination, having back-up in a trail car. But ultimately, as long as the assassin knows where you&apos;re going, they have the upper hand.</li>
<li>It&apos;s impossible to stop a good assassin from finding an opening, and taking the shot. The best you can do is to control where the best opening is, and sometimes, that&apos;s enough. </li></ul>
