<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In prison, there&apos;s no such thing as good attention. It&apos;s better to be a number than to be known because with anonymity comes safety. So whether you&apos;re dealing with a fellow inmate, a guard, or the warden herself; the last thing you want is for your name to be on their mind.</li>
<li>When you&apos;ve been marked for death, hiding is a short term strategy. It might buy you time but it won&apos;t solve your problem. To do that, you need contact. It means exposing yourself to more potential threats, but it also means having the opportunity to find potential allies.</li>
<li>Effective interrogations take many forms but usually include 3 key elements. First, you need a target with the intel you&apos;re after. Then you need an interrogation team. Their job is to secure the target and do whatever it takes to obtain actionable intelligence. But getting useful information doesn&apos;t matter if you can&apos;t move on it, which is why you need a support team in the field. And of course the whole system breaks down if someone kills the target before he can talk.</li>
<li>Personal bodyguards are specifically trained to identify and prioritize potential threats, which means getting their attention is usually as easy as becoming the most immediate threat in the area.</li>
<li>The difference between a drug being called &quot;medicine&quot; or &quot;poison&quot; comes down to one thing: dosage. The recommended amount of prazosin will effectively regulate blood pressure. But taking too much, will trigger side effects that mimic the symptoms of an extreme viral infection. Once they kick in, instead of doubling down, you&apos;ll be falling down.</li>
<li>One of the easiest and most efficient ways to make incendiary devices begins with mixing aluminum powder and plaster of Paris. Once dry, it burns at about 3000 degrees, and can melt solid steel in under a minute. It&apos;s also completely stable, and safe to store until it&apos;s lit. Which is important because nobody should handle a deadly incendiary without a good night&apos;s sleep.</li>
<li>Hiding trackers in accessories is a go-to trick for spies. Jewelry and watches are attractive options but there&apos;s always a risk they&apos;ll clash with the target&apos;s outfit, and get left at home. On the other hand, a tracker that the target believes might save his life, is always in fashion.</li>
<li>Gram staining is a method of testing for the presence of certain types of bacteria. Positive results turn purple, negative results turn pink. If you need a positive result on a gram test, there&apos;s no need to bring in a lethal micro-organism, a little yogurt will do the job. And of course, no matter what color a slide turns, nothing sells scary like a big reaction.</li>
<li>Sabotage is best done in private when no one is around to see it. If you don&apos;t have that luxury, you have to take certain precautions. It&apos;s crucial to conceal the real reason for your movements so people don&apos;t get suspicious. It&apos;s also a good idea to use time delay devices so that when the fun starts, you&apos;ll be nowhere near it.</li>
<li>A successful ambush can end a battle before it ever begins. To pull one off, you need 2 key factors: the element of surprise, and superior positioning. The best staging areas offer a clear view of your target, while providing plenty of cover for you. Of course, it doesn&apos;t matter how good your position is, if you&apos;re the one that gets surprised.</li></ul>
