<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>The vehicle you want when hunting someone down depends on where you are in the chase. If you&apos;re behind your target, you need a set of wheels that&apos;s fast enough to catch up. If you&apos;re ahead and waiting for your target to come to you, you might want to think bigger. </li>
<li>Anti-theft devices, like transponder keys and transmission locks, make newer trucks nearly impossible to steal. Hot-wiring an older truck on the other hand, is still just a matter of shorting the terminals on the starter solenoid; and, of course, dealing with whoever happens to own the truck. </li>
<li>Keeping a large truck stable is basically about keeping your speed low and your turns shallow so the center of gravity doesn&apos;t shift further than the vehicle can handle. On the other hand, speed and sharp turns are exactly what you need, if you want the truck to jack-knife. An abandoned semi-truck will create an effective barricade; but, if you really want to tie up traffic, it helps to give people a reason to keep their distance.  </li>
<li>Hunting for a fugitive in a large area with a lot of cover is less about skill than it is about man-power. It doesn&apos;t matter how good an operative you are, when it comes to a man-hunt, the more people you have on your side the better.  </li>
<li>It&apos;s almost impossible to escape when you&apos;re being handcuffed by pros. They are trained to work in pairs when handcuffing a dangerous suspect. One cuffs the hostile while the other covers them both. Even if you can avoid getting cuffed, it only buys you a second before you get shot. But sometimes a second is all you need.  </li>
<li>Clearing a structure is ideally a team effort. When you&apos;re forced into it alone, you have to take special precautions like using peripheral vision to check angles. But ultimately, no matter how careful you are there&apos;s always one angle that you can&apos;t see when you are alone - the one behind you.  </li>
<li>An ultra-wide band frequency scanner is one of the newer devices in the tool kit of the tactical breaching team. It&apos;s portable, requires little power, and can see through doors well enough to tell you if they&apos;re worth kicking down. </li>
<li>Under the right circumstances stress can make you hyper-aware, alert to every detail. It can also make you paranoid and prone to seeing what you want to see.  </li></ul>
