<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you&apos;re a spy, you learn to live with the idea of people wanting you dead - an old enemy, a dissatisfied employer, a disgruntled asset. Work long enough, and the line to kill you gets pretty long. Still, getting blown up isn&apos;t really something you get used to. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re being hunted, paranoia is inevitable. If you don&apos;t know what to do with it, it turns into cold, directionless fear. With the right training, it turns into hyper-awareness of your surroundings. Not always pleasant, but a lot more useful. </li>
<li>Distinguishing between different kinds of suspicious behavior is crucial for an operative. Someone doing surveillance, for example, looks different than someone who&apos;s trying to commit suicide. </li>
<li>From the first day of training, you&apos;re told not to get emotionally involved in operations. But sometimes it happens, and there&apos;s nothing you can do. </li>
<li>Medical scammers, like pimps, drug dealers or feral dogs, need to protect their territory. They can&apos;t let anyone new operate there, or they&apos;re asking for problems. Like a corporation has a lawyer to handle copyright infringement, a scammer will often have an enforcer to deal with unwanted competition. </li>
<li>As a spy, the best approach is usually to become a target&apos;s friend. Some situations, though, call for a different approach. </li>
<li>Empty commercial buildings are useful when you&apos;re looking for a place to interrogate someone. No one pays much attention to people coming and going, and the floors are typically soundproof. </li>
<li>Securing a room isn&apos;t about walls. A determined captive can kick through plasterboard, but he can&apos;t bite through steel bars, or pry out screws with his fingers. Though it might be fun to watch him try. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a saying in interrogation: &quot;Violence perceived is violence achieved.&quot; You don&apos;t want someone screaming, you want him asking questions. Asking, &quot;What is he doing with that knife?&quot; Asking, &quot;If he&apos;ll do that to himself, what will he do to me?&quot; Mostly, you want him asking, &quot;How do I make this stop?&quot; </li>
<li>Nearly getting killed shakes you up, no matter how much experience you have. Brushes with death are like snowflakes. Each one is unique, and icy cold. </li>
<li>The &quot;Who talks first?&quot; interrogation technique originally involved taking two blindfolded prisoners up in a helicopter and tossing one out to get the other to talk. When a helicopter&apos;s not available, any tall building will do. You really don&apos;t want to kill anyone, of course. The screaming is all you need. </li>
<li>For the truly security conscious, there&apos;s no better meeting place than a pool of water. Even if you manage to hide a bug in your swim trunks, chlorinated water conducts electricity well enough to short out any listening device. </li>
<li>In covert work, you try to make friends with the bad guys. But sometimes you just can&apos;t pull it off. Once it&apos;s clear you&apos;re not going to be friends, you have to resolve the situation as quickly and as cleanly as possible. Sometimes you can&apos;t pull that off either.</li>
<li>Using sound to determine an enemy&apos;s position is one of the oldest techniques in war: whether it&apos;s putting an ear to the ground or bouncing sonar off a submarine. If you can get your enemy on the phone, that opens up new possibilities. Hook up your cell phone to an amplifier and a computer that can analyze sound and you have a powerful weapon if you know how to use it.</li>
<li>Running an operation is like poker. Ideally, you&apos;ve got good cards and you play them well. When your cards are bad, though, you have to know how to bluff.</li>
<li>In modern warfare, a well-positioned microphone can tell you anything from where troops are moving to where a sniper is firing from. The same basic technology will also tell you when an ambulance passes and someone talking on a cell phone.</li>
<li>When you&apos;ve spent enough time as an operative, recovering from a brush with death isn&apos;t about an appointment with the psychiatrist or a week in Hawaii. It&apos;s about having a purpose, whether it&apos;s something to fight or someone to hunt.</li></ul>
