<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">National intelligence agencies and local law enforcement work together more often than you might think. Most metropolitan police stations have an office called a fusion center where classified intel is collected in one place. It’s a great resource if you need information fast. Unfortunately, it does involve breaking into a police station.</span></li>
<li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">Because undercover cops and confidential informants don’t like their pictures taken. Only the public areas of police stations are kept under surveillance. So once you’re past the lobby, the only cameras you have to avoid are the ones taking mug shots.</span></li>
<li><p style="margin-top:0px;color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">Get caught with a lock-pick set in a police station, and you’ve got problems. A pair of cheap sunglasses is less suspicious and just about as effective. Modify them in advance, and you can use the stems as a rake and tension tool. And if you get caught, you’re just a guy with some busted sunglasses.</p></li>
<li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">Police officers uphold the chain of command as sacred. Act like you’re in charge, and someone new to the force won’t dare question your authority.</span></li>
<li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">It’s hard to forgive someone after a betrayal, even if it was for a good cause. There’s nothing more difficult to repair in the field than trust.</span></li>
<li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">Blackmail may be effective at times, but it’s never fun. The problem is that it works best on people that are basically good. If someone’s made a mistake he regrets, it’s easy to make him regret it even more.</span></li>
<li><span style="color:rgb(50,50,50);font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,Verdana,sans-serif;line-height:21.993999481201172px;">Scouting security from a distance is mainly just a matter of observation. You set up in a concealed place and watch incoming vehicles, personnel, and weapons. Getting additional information usually requires a more direct approach.</span></li></ul>
