<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you&apos;re a fugitive, it&apos;s tempting to flee the country and worry about the details later, but it&apos;s also a great way to get caught. Since most countries now require biometric I.D&apos;s, the first step in getting out of town is getting good documents. You can&apos;t just go somewhere new, you need to BE someone new when you get there. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a reason fugitives are so paranoid. When you&apos;re on the run, even the smallest change in your environment can put you on high alert. But then again, sometimes being paranoid pays off. </li>
<li>Even if you evade the FBI, ATF, and DEA, a life of crime is tough to explain to the IRS. That&apos;s why many career criminals have a day job. It gives them a cover I.D., access to equipment, and a real W-2. It also makes them easier to find if they won&apos;t answer your calls. </li>
<li>Counterintelligence, broadly speaking, is the practice of spying on someone who&apos;s spying on you. With a little patience, you can learn a surprising amount about your enemies just by watching their own surveillance teams. It starts with carefully observing who&apos;s at what location, when they&apos;re there, and how often. Once you have a list of possible candidates, you cross-reference with people from other surveillance sites. If anybody shows up more than once, it&apos;s a safe bet it&apos;s not just a coincedence. It&apos;s a lot easier to keep your secrets if you know who&apos;s after them.     </li>
<li>Flashbang grenades may not be deadly, but if one goes off nearby, it can cause temporary blindness and hearing loss. The combination of those effects is enough to stun even the most hardened soldier. But if you can take cover in time to protect your vision, you can still stay in the fight. You may not be able to hear your enemy, but if you can see him well enough to pursue him, then it&apos;s just a matter of not letting the ringing in your ears distract you from taking him down.    </li>
<li>Electroshock torture is a messy business. While most of the damage is internal, the electric arc that&apos;s created can burn anywhere from 2,500 to 5,000 degrees. If you want to look like you&apos;ve been tortured, but aren&apos;t willing to hook yourself up to a car battery, a curling iron can create similar burns without the risk of stopping your heart.  </li>
<li>Surveillance doesn&apos;t always have to be covert to be useful. Sometimes the best way into a target&apos;s life is through the front door. There are advantages to being obvious when the goal is less about information gathering, and more about intimidation. There&apos;s nothing more jarring than realizing that your every move is being watched.</li>
<li>Spies will use whatever they can to get behind enemy lines: stealth, deception, and even capture. A prisoner of war can learn about enemy morale, supply, and location. Of course, the first thing you have to do is convince your enemies you&apos;re worth more alive than dead.</li>
<li>Most intelligence agencies lack the resources to set up safe houses all over the world, which is why they depend on expat civilians to lend their homes or businesses for missions abroad. If you&apos;re a former Syrian intelligence officer, the local Syrian restaurant can make a handy base of operations, and save you a few bucks on lunch. </li>
<li>If you think someone might be following you, the temptation is to drive erratically. It may force the tail to reveal itself, but it also reveals you&apos;re onto them. A better approach is to drive very conservatively. Go below the speed limit and linger at stop signs. You won&apos;t win any fans on the road, but it&apos;ll help you lose your tail. If they think you&apos;re simply an overcautious driver, it&apos;ll catch them off guard when you suddenly take a risk.  </li>
<li>When planning an escape, patience is key. Someone without training might jump at the first chance to strike, but that&apos;s exactly the wrong time because that&apos;s when your enemy&apos;s the most alert. In fact, the best time to make your move is after you&apos;ve let plenty of other opportunities go by. The other advantage of patience is it gives you a chance to find out if the situation has changed. </li>
<li>When an operation goes seriously wrong, you have to decide quickly whether to bail out, or keep pushing and try to salvage what you can. Bailing out is less risky, but when it means leaving someone behind to die, sometimes you just have to grit your teeth and roll the dice. </li>
<li>Counter-intelligence usually starts as a subtle game of cat and mouse. Your adversary pretends not to be watching you, and you pretend not to notice. But the longer it goes on, the more inevitable it becomes that you&apos;ll end up in open warfare. </li></ul>
