<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In the intelligence world, when an operation demands that you disappear, it&apos;s understood that you will disappear entirely. You can&apos;t have anything that links you to your former life. No credit history, no communication with friends, and nothing with your old name on it. That&apos;s hard enough for an intelligence professional to deal with, for a civilian, it&apos;s nearly impossible.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re on the run and planning on doing some serious international travel, you need to be prepared to put together some top-notch travel documents. Making a fake I.D. that can reliably cross a border these days isn&apos;t just a matter of getting special paper and a hologram sticker. You need some very expensive, high technology. Unfortunately, the people who sell that kind of technology tend to be very unpleasant and very well-armed.</li>
<li>One of the biggest challenges of being a fugitive is security. When you&apos;re being hunted, you have to be on your guard around the clock. If you&apos;re hiding in a safe house, that means keeping an eye out the window, having your weapon ready, and spending some quality time in front of perimeter cams. And sometimes, just as important as keeping your enemy out, is keeping your team in.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re being chased, you want to be driving something with speed, maneuverability, and stability. In other words, you want to be driving anything but a container van. If you find yourself in an under-powered vehicle with a high center of gravity and a top speed of 60, your best bet is to attack whoever&apos;s after you with everything you have. If an attack&apos;s out of the question, it&apos;s all about getting as much distance as you can between yourself and your pursuers, and bailing out.</li>
<li>If you want to scare someone into thinking their vehicle is malfunctioning, nothing is more convincing than a small explosion. The mercury fulminate in a blasting cap gives you the perfect amount of explosive to send the message loud and clear without killing the vehicle or anyone in it.</li>
<li>Industrial suction fans spin at more than 1,400 RPM and weigh as much as 500 pounds. Trying to physically stop one requires using an object heavy enough to stop it&apos;s linear momentum. And if you don&apos;t want to throw your back out, it&apos;s best to let the fan do most of the work for you.</li>
<li>The tough thing about going up against someone carrying a machine pistol is that they fire over a thousand rounds a minute. The good news is that they&apos;re notoriously inaccurate at long distances. So if you keep moving, you&apos;ve got a pretty good chance of making it out in one piece. If you stop, on the other hand, you&apos;re bound to catch a bullet.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re in the field, the goal is usually to be in complete communication with your team, to work in perfect sync at all times. But when the weight of a mission threatens to tear your team apart, there are times when you&apos;re forced to mislead even the people you&apos;re closest to. Because the toughest decisions are the ones you have to make all by yourself.</li>
<li>If you need to make a clean exit, putting an electrical transmitter between you and your enemy will help make sure there won&apos;t be a firefight. All it takes is one bullet to disrupt the sensitive electronics, and create an explosive power surge. Of course, sometimes, an explosive power surge is exactly what you need.</li></ul>
