<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>Whenever you get a fresh piece of intelligence in the field, you have to decide carefully who you&apos;re going to share it with. Because every asset you talk to, agency you work with, and resource you update brings along a new set of problems.</li>
<li>One of the most popular bases for covert operations is an abandoned building. Hotels and apartments have too many people coming and going to base a long term op. You can buy a house, but it&apos;s hard to buy something big enough discreetly, on short notice. Find a building that&apos;s been condemned however and you can move right in, as long as you can find some way to supply power and you don&apos;t mind a little dust. </li>
<li>With a running start, the average adult can jump a distance of about 10 feet. The trick to clearing bigger gaps, is raising your launch point and making your jump at full speed. It&apos;s all about maximizing your momentum, which can make the difference between a safe landing, and a date with the pavement. </li>
<li>If you&apos;re building ammunition to shatter reinforced glass, you need something harder than buckshot. If you don&apos;t have a handful of diamonds lying around, spark plugs will do. The ceramic casings are nearly as hard. Once you&apos;ve dealt with the glass you have to deal with the people behind it. A serviceable flash-bang grenade can be made from a soda can filled with aluminum shavings and gun powder. Not as stable as military issue, but it still packs one helluva kick.</li>
<li>When you give a piece of intelligence to anyone, even an ally, you never know what they&apos;re going to do with it. Because even if you completely trust that person, you run the risk of them taking that information and using it for their own purposes. </li>
<li>Locating a group of mercenaries in a third-world country isn&apos;t terribly difficult, because they are very similar to street thugs – they flaunt their presence. So if you want to find an outfit, it&apos;s as simple as asking around. The question isn&apos;t where they are, it&apos;s what you&apos;re going to do when you find them. </li>
<li>It&apos;s a popular misconception that guard duty is all about watching for people. In fact, people are usually a lower priority than vehicles. A well trained guard will focus first on keeping the road clear and monitoring suspicious cars in the vicinity, which can give you a great excuse to get up close. </li>
<li>Setting up a snatch-and-grab requires having the right pieces in place. You need a lookout up high, a driver in the get-away car and someone to create the distraction. Then you just have to wait for the target to show up. </li></ul>
