<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>In many ways being a spy is just like any other job; you get a paycheck, go to meetings, return phone calls and if your supervisor invites you to a fancy lunch without telling you why, it&apos;s either very good news or very bad. </li>
<li>Unlike criminals, spies are trained to work with their captors to negotiate their own release. In most cases, it simply requires staying calm, relaxed and being as helpful as possible. Of course it&apos;s a lot more difficult when the person standing across from you is someone you hate.</li>
<li>Selling a cover as a former convict is about the little things, the habits you learn in prison. Things like wearing shoes without laces, refusing to make direct eye contact and asking permission before doing even the most basic tasks. </li>
<li>When making an approach, solid intelligence is often just a starting point. Gauging the different reactions of your target and those around him can help you fill in the blanks. While you may already know how a man feels about his dad, keeping your eyes open can also tell you about how that mans wife really felt about her father-in-law. </li>
<li>Budget constraints force most government offices to manage their data using rigid, out of date, filing systems. The constant glitches and lack of technical support give you a great opportunity to side-step the normal rules and procedures. Of course, if you run into someone who insists on doing something by the book you better know how to bend those same rules… in your favor. </li>
<li>Explosive breaching is usually the fastest way into any building but it isn&apos;t exactly the most subtle. When a softer touch is required a compact hydraulic wedge can quickly pry a door away from its frame without waking up the neighbors or singeing off your eyebrows. </li>
<li>The mistake people make in trying to deal with a guard dog is: trying to deal with a guard dog. A well trained German Shepard can run nearly thirty miles an hour, jump about five feet vertically and bite with more than 500 pounds of pressure. Trying to distract a dog may seem like a good idea but it usually just delays getting attacked by a few seconds. The best strategy is to stay as far away as possible and, if you can, put some solid steel between you and the animal. </li>
<li>More often than not, high speed chases end with the fleeing driver in handcuffs or in a bed at the hospital. Escaping with your freedom and the ability to use both of your legs, means making a get-away the cops aren&apos;t prepared to deal with. </li>
<li>When your target draws a conclusion you&apos;re not ready for, you play along if it helps you get the job done. Sometimes it makes wrapping up a mission quick and easy, and other times it makes your job that much harder. </li></ul>
