<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Working a long-term undercover job is about learning to live with uncertainty. The uncertainty that comes with chasing something that you can never see. You&apos;re often going after a target you know little or nothing about. You don&apos;t know their plans, you don&apos;t know where they&apos;ll be, you don&apos;t know what they know about you. After a while, that uncertainty begins to gnaw at you. It affects you, no matter how well-trained you are. The real battle becomes the one within yourself to keep your doubts at bay. So that when the day comes to take your target down, you&apos;re ready. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Personal security uses a method called &quot;arm&apos;s reach&quot;. In an attack, if you&apos;re closest to the client, you shield them. If you&apos;re closest to the attacker, you focus on the threat. One man tries to defend against danger, and the other one tries to find it. Of course, if personal security has to get involved, something&apos;s already gone very wrong. A good security setup stops threats before they ever get close. With a combination of human spotters, computerized facial recognition, and electronic surveillance equipment, the goal is to find the bad guys long before they make a move. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Combat support hospitals are portable operating rooms that can be set up anywhere in an hour. If you don&apos;t have time to get your wounded to a doctor, hospitals like these can bring the doctor to you. But there are still some injuries that even immediate medical attention can&apos;t fix. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For someone who&apos;s not used to being under surveillance, knowing someone&apos;s watching can be a lot worse than being oblivious. The problem is that, when anyone could be watching you, it often feels like everyone is watching you. Whether you&apos;re a professional or a civilian, there&apos;s ultimately only one real way to find out for sure if someone&apos;s watching you. You have to go somewhere concealed, and see if they follow. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">There are a lot of reasons strip clubs have become a common meeting spot for a wide range of criminal activities. For one thing, they&apos;re open in the day, windowless, and too loud for good audio surveillance. They also provide privacy. Dark corners designed for flirting with dancers work just as well for a covert meeting. And of course, if you&apos;re doing or saying anything illegal, chances are, everyone else will be too distracted to notice. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When you have to make a cold approach, and you have to make it fast, you don&apos;t get any points for being polite. The most important thing is to get your target&apos;s attention. Because it doesn&apos;t matter if they like you, as long as they like what you have to say. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Once you sold your cover ID to your target, it&apos;s important to know your limits. The more complex and technical your cover is, the greater the danger is you&apos;ll be discovered. If you&apos;re pretending to be an expert in organic chemistry, it&apos;s a good idea to make your move as quickly as possible. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Being under surveillance is more stressful than most people realize. Even when you have no contact with the people watching you, just knowing that they&apos;re there can take a lot out of you. The problem is you begin to feel eyes on you all the time. Often it&apos;s just your imagination playing tricks on you. But sometimes, those eyes are all too real. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">There are many techniques for dealing with guards without raising alarm. They all boil down to 2 basic steps: a stunning move to stop your target from crying out, and a subduing move to keep him quiet.
</p>
</xml>
