<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>For a spy, the worst thing that can happen is to become someone else&apos;s asset. You do anything you can to avoid it, making sure there&apos;s nothing people can grab onto and use as leverage. You move through life unattached, keeping the world at a distance. It&apos;s a hard way to live, but there&apos;s a cold logic to it. Love nothing, and nothing you love can be used against you. Once you violate that rule and make that connection with someone, you&apos;ve handed your enemies the key to destroying you. </li>
<li>When operating without official cover in remote locations, you don&apos;t have resources or backup if things go wrong. So it&apos;s usually best to move fast and stay exposed for as little time as possible. It&apos;s just a matter of figuring out what you&apos;re up against, crossing your fingers, and getting in and out as quickly as you can. </li>
<li>Creating a good diversion isn&apos;t just about making noise and firing guns. It&apos;s about giving the enemy the impression that he&apos;s being attacked in a way that demands the immediate attention of all of his forces. Ideally, something big and very, very loud.</li>
<li>Information stored on a D-Ram chip was long considered impossible to steal. It&apos;s automatically erased when the chip&apos;s removed. The one way to preserve the information in a D-ram chip is by freezing it immediately after you take it out of the computer. A quick application of compressed air from your local drug store will keep the memory intact long enough to get what you need. It&apos;s possible, but far from easy. And if you don&apos;t want to get caught, it takes some practice.  </li>
<li>When you need to buy time for an operation, the key is staying relaxed. No matter how high the stakes are, you have to act like everything&apos;s fine. The key is staying natural. Giving your team as much room to operate as you can without letting on what you&apos;re doing. When you know that time is running out, you have to signal your team at the first opportunity and hope for the best. </li>
<li>In a situation where you&apos;re trying to keep someone from being captured, your best leverage is often the life of the very person you&apos;re trying to protect. The trick is convincing the bad guys that you&apos;re willing to kill their prize before you let them have it. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re surprised by an enemy who has you outgunned, your first instinct is naturally going to be to try to run. This can be a serious tactical mistake. Sometimes it&apos;s less important to get away immediately, than it is to make sure your enemies can&apos;t follow. </li>
<li>Active security systems are built to keep people out. Passive systems on the other hand, don&apos;t prevent security breaches-they help you catch the bad guy after he leaves. They&apos;re often cheaper and more effective. Plus, they let you know who your enemies are. Micro RFID tags work like anti-theft tags in department stores. Only, they&apos;re a lot smaller and stick to clothes, shoes, and even hair. Once activated, they transmit a response to a coded signal. From there, its easy for a surveillance satellite to lock on and follow a high-value target. And the best part is, the target never even knew it happened. </li>
<li>The age of satellite surveillance has made some operations easier for spies and a lot harder for others. If you need to secretly meet someone who&apos;s being tracked by a satellite, your options are pretty limited. The only move is to make sure you&apos;re some place the surveillance satellites can&apos;t see you. That usually means a cave, a tunnel, or in a pinch, a freeway overpass. </li>
<li>One of the nice things about sending a full-scale Homeland Security response after your enemies is the fact that you can get the resources of every branch of law enforcement. Which means they generally catch whoever they&apos;re after, and they don&apos;t listen to excuses. </li>
<li>For a spy, loyalty is a strange thing. Your job is to deceive, to live among your enemies, to perform dark deeds for a noble purpose. And it&apos;s that purpose that guides you through the darkness. When you lose sight of that, the darkness is all there is. </li></ul>
