<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>There are advantages to training with someone you&apos;re close to. Knowing each other&apos;s moves makes training more effective. But being involved in each other&apos;s personal lives can also make training a lot more painful.</li>
<li>Meeting a new operative is a lot like going on a blind date. You&apos;re bound to be nervous the first couple of times you do it, but live through a few and you get to be an expert. You should arrive early, prepare an exit strategy and know you could be in for an ugly surprise.</li>
<li>The cold approach is something you try to avoid in intelligence work. You wanna ease into a relationship over time. When that&apos;s impossible, you just have to turn on the charm and hope for the best. </li>
<li>A flash-bang grenade temporarily impairs hearing and vision. It makes fighting back or attempting escape futile and dangerous to civilians. So if you have to shoot blind, it&apos;s better to use a camera than a gun. </li>
<li>In a hostage situation, the same things that get you killed will extend your life. If you have money, you&apos;ll live &apos;til you pay. If you have information, you&apos;ll live &apos;til you talk. And if you have nothing, you&apos;re pretty much disposable. </li>
<li>After the adrenaline rush of an operation comes a crash. Heightened reflexes and awareness don&apos;t last. Two boring hours of driving later, even the sharpest killing machine lets down his guard. </li>
<li>When on the run, subtle things like broken branches, flattened grass and disturbed ground can give you away to an expert tracker. An inexperienced tracker may require a more obvious trail.  </li>
<li>Fanning out in a search pattern is a great way to cover a lot of area, but it also divides your forces. </li>
<li>Military units are a lot like marching bands. Take out the guy conducting the operation, and you&apos;ll throw everyone out of sync. Pretty soon, all you have left is sound and fury.</li>
<li>When fighting in the wilderness, the biggest threats are often the ones you don&apos;t see -dehydration, exhaustion and nerves. But boatloads of hostiles don&apos;t help either.</li>
<li>In battle, not even the best laid plans survive contact with the enemy. If you want to survive, you have to be willing to improvise. Of course, there&apos;s such a thing as too much improvisation. </li>
<li>Delaying tactics aren&apos;t the most glamorous part of a battle plan, but they&apos;re often the most important. Slowing the enemy down buys you time to prepare the ground ahead of him. And that, more than almost anything else, wins battles. </li>
<li>For a spy, there&apos;s no shame in retreat. When faced with a more powerful enemy, you&apos;re trained to get out of the way and keep moving. It&apos;s not about running away or giving up. The goal of any retreat is to find the right place to marshal your resources and make a stand.</li>
<li>Military history is filled with stories of small forces taking on larger ones. Whether it&apos;s David fighting Goliath or the French Resistance fighting the Nazis, the strategy is basically the same. You have to choose the right ground, deploy your resources carefully and remember that the greatest weapon in any battle is surprise.</li></ul>
