<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When a spy is killed in the field, it&apos;s often hardest on the people they were spying on. Mourning the death of someone you thought you knew is complicated enough when the spy was a trusted colleague or friend. But it&apos;s even more difficult when they were someone you loved. </li>
<li>The Cayman Islands are only home to 60,000 people. But thanks to lenient tax laws, it&apos;s the 5th largest financial center in the world. But it&apos;s not banking, like most people are used to. Bank locations tend to not offer services like online bill pay, drive-through teller windows, or even ATM&apos;s. What they lack in modern conveniences, they make up for in guaranteeing their clients complete security and anonymity. Whether you&apos;re a Wall Street executive looking for a tax shelter, or an international criminal hiding a small fortune, it&apos;s nearly impossible for government agencies to access your information when your bank of choice is nothing more than a number in a phone book, a sign on the window, and a sleazy banker with very white teeth.</li>
<li>When you want to catch a well placed and well protected spy, you can&apos;t just call local police. That kind of investigation takes high-level resources and an even higher level of operational secrecy, which means you have to start with someone connected to the very top.</li>
<li>Surviving an enemy sniper attack is about finding adequate cover while being able to stay mobile enough to escape the shooter&apos;s pre-scouted kill zone. Pulling the shifter linkage of a parked car into neutral and using it as a rolling barricade allows you to do both as long as you can get it moving.</li>
<li>As a spy, you get used to the idea that you sometimes have to ask your enemies for help. It&apos;s not an easy thing to do, but unfortunately, the best information is often in the hands of the worst people.</li>
<li>Faking someone&apos;s death is all about getting the details right. The human body contains five liters of blood. Finding half that amount spilled across the seat of an abandoned car is enough to lead any crime-scene investigator to draw the obvious conclusion. Answering the remaining questions of where the body went and how the victim was injured is as simple as a blood trail run cold, destroying any DNA that doesn&apos;t match the victim, and lots and lots of bullets.</li>
<li>If you want to incapacitate an enemy&apos;s moving car, the first thing you need is a bigger vehicle. A utility truck gives you enough horsepower to keep you from getting left in the dust, and a full-size metal bumper that can take a pounding. The trick is getting close enough to your target to precisely time an accident that keeps innocent bystanders out of harm&apos;s way and surprises your enemy with a hard impact to force them out of control. And if their wheels aren&apos;t touching the ground, they&apos;ll have no way to escape.</li></ul>
