<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>One of the reasons surveillance is done in teams, is that it&apos;s exhausting. Sitting in a car, remaining constantly alert while you watch a mailbox will knock you out like a handful of sleeping pills. Doing it in shifts is the only way to make sure you don&apos;t miss something. </li>
<li>Tailing a trained operative requires a number of time-consuming preparations. Everything from acquiring a vehicle they can&apos;t recognize or trace, to familiarizing yourself with all the local traffic patterns. Of course, since you can never be sure who&apos;s a trained op there&apos;s always the chance you&apos;ll take all those precautions just to follow a secretary back to her cubicle. </li>
<li>Covert security is designed to blend in. People you never notice until you see them in action. That means you have two choices. You can sit and wait for an incident to occur, or you can create your own incident. </li>
<li>Criminal hideouts tend to be pretty nondescript. Underground caves and spooky old mansions are dramatic, but a boathouse on the Keys is easier to find.</li>
<li>When you&apos;re looking to get somebody arrested, bad guys can&apos;t always be counted on to commit crimes on your schedule. Sometimes you have to give them a little push. Once you&apos;ve got a crime in progress, you can let the authorities take over. That assumes, of course, that the authorities are paying attention. </li>
<li>You can&apos;t stop a door alarm from going off, but you can explain it. Leave a few cigarette butts on the ground and anybody coming by will assume someone was just sneaking a smoke break. </li>
<li>24/7 surveillance on a location used to require a full team of operatives. These days, you can get by with a webcam and wireless signal booster from your local electronics store. Ideally, you&apos;d drill holes and mount it on brackets. But when time is an issue, I prefer dental putty. Easy to mix, easy to apply, and as strong as cement when it hardens. But it hardens quick, so you better aim right the first time. </li>
<li>Making yourself invisible when you need to is a crucial skill for a covert operative. It sounds exotic, but it&apos;s not like there&apos;s a super secret move they teach you at spy school that allows you to vanish into thin air. Often, it&apos;s just a matter of quick thinking, fast feet, and strong fingers. </li>
<li>Safe-cracking skills are a basic part of espionage training. Spies steal secrets, and people keep their secrets in safes. But staying current with safe-cracking is a little like staying current with computers -new model every year. Bottom line: If you wanna breach a safe, you have to practice. </li>
<li>A criminal cover ID isn&apos;t just about a new name and phone number. It&apos;s about fitting in to a culture with its own rules and hierarchies. It&apos;s a world where bank robbers are the rock stars, con artists are the snobs, car thieves are the blue collar guys and safe crackers are the artists. </li>
<li>Anytime you recommend a friend for a job, you&apos;re on the hook if things don&apos;t work out. In the retail sales business for example, make a bad referral and you might get fired. In the armed robbery business on the other hand, make a bad referral and you might get killed. So you really, really have to hope that the new guy knows what he&apos;s doing. </li>
<li>Sending messages in the middle of an operation is among the most dangerous things you can do. Sometimes you just have to drop a note and hope your backup team is paying attention. </li>
<li>A certain kind of leader insists on controlling every aspect of an operation, so that nothing can possibly go wrong. The downside to insisting on controlling everything, is that when something bad happens, people tend to think it was all part of your plan. </li>
<li>When you work in intelligence, there&apos;s no bigger slap in the face than a picture of yourself in the middle of an operation. It sends a clear message: We&apos;re one step ahead of you. We&apos;re in control. We own you. Mylar balloons and a bottle of champagne, that&apos;s just twisting the knife. </li></ul>
