<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you have to get information about an enemy position, you have a choice. You can watch from a distance, slow and safe. Or you can go inside and take a look. Quick, but potentially fatal. </li>
<li>Most people think snipers like to shoot from ledges. The fact is, the best sniper position is inside a room, through an open window. It hides the shooter, masks the report of a supersonic round and makes the muzzle flash impossible to see.</li>
<li>It&apos;s always a challenge hiding something sensitive that you might need quickly. Any hiding place involves a trade-off between security and access. Hide something in the sewer main under your floor, and it&apos;s secure, but good luck getting to it. Hide something in your sock drawer and it&apos;s easy to get to, but hardly secure. The best hiding places are easy to get to but tough to find. The do-it-yourself versions are known in the spy trade as slicks -easy to slip something in, easy to slide it out. </li>
<li>When an operative recruits someone, he lets the target make the first move. He&apos;ll dress like him, drink like him, move like him, but he won&apos;t talk to him. He&apos;ll wait to be approached.</li>
<li>When selling yourself as a traitor, you can&apos;t be too eager. A good op will walk away from a recruitment that seems too good to be true. </li>
<li>Surveillance is the leading cause of weight gain among operatives. In a job that&apos;s equal parts boredom and tension, eating is a way to pass time and calm nerves.</li>
<li>Facial recognition systems are often used to replace human guards since they&apos;re cheap, they don&apos;t sleep, and they can&apos;t be bribed. They have a big weakness though. Unlike guards, computers can&apos;t tell the difference between a photocopy of a face and a face. When you search a spy&apos;s room, you don&apos;t waste time checking the safe. You have to assume they&apos;re as creative as you are. Slicks come in all shapes and sizes. </li>
<li>There&apos;s an art to drinking without getting drunk; start with a lot of ice to dilute the alcohol. Order a new round before you&apos;re done so your half-full drink gets taken away. And of course, spill. </li>
<li>A cover I.D. that involves drinking comes with a price but the tactical advantages make the hangover worth it. </li>
<li>Operatives do a lot of bodyguard work. On any given day, the average commando is more likely to be watching a VIP walk his dog than engaging the enemy in battle. Not glamorous, but part of the job. </li>
<li>Anybody who runs a few assets knows that some crack under the pressure. You have to be tough enough to keep them in line, supportive enough to keep them stable. </li>
<li>When someone turns you into an asset, their main weapon is fear. If you fear poverty or exposure or death, that&apos;s what they use against you. Their worst nightmare, then, is an asset with no fear. </li>
<li>Blowing an operation is a delicate business. You have to convince your opponent to abandon his plans, make a case that the smart move is to just pack up and go home. Problem is, even when you do your job well, people don&apos;t always go with the smart move. </li>
<li>There&apos;s a reason they call the spy trade &quot;The Hall of Mirrors.&quot; You can never know for sure whether you&apos;re in control or you&apos;re being played, but if you do it long enough, you learn to trust your instincts. </li>
<li>Unlike cars, motorcycles don&apos;t have much of an aftermarket in stolen parts, so anti-theft measures are outdated and easy to get around. The steering lock on a smaller bike breaks fairly easily. Then it&apos;s just a matter of getting away. </li>
<li>When you&apos;re tailed by multiple vehicles, you&apos;re at a disadvantage. They can flank you, take alternate routes, box you in. It helps to have a team of your own. </li>
<li>The Electronic Stability Program was originally developed to help keep cars from sliding on icy roads. But it&apos;s a great tool for the precision driver. When you need to slide, you can simply turn it off and turn it on again when you need to maneuver. </li>
<li>A semi has about four feet of clearance under it. Sliding beneath it on a motorcycle is possible, but risky. Too low, and the pavement will grind you to a pulp. Too high, and any part of your body that hits the trailer will no longer be part of your body.</li></ul>
