<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>As a spy you get used to dealing with government bureaucracy. If you need to requisition a weapon, get an interrogation log to an analyst, or even arrange an emergency evac from a hostile territory, a bureaucrat can be your best friend. But when you need a simple answer to a straightforward question that same bureaucrat can become your worst enemy. </li>
<li>If you need to get information from a government official, it&apos;s often best to approach him outside his usual place of business. When he&apos;s not in an environment that reinforces his authority you&apos;re a lot more likely to get something out of him. Especially if you can catch him alone. </li>
<li>Whether you&apos;re trying to run someone off the road or just trying to sell that you are, it all comes down to the vehicle you use to do it. You want a light frame so you can maneuver faster than your target, and a low center of gravity so you don&apos;t flip. Choosing the right car can mean the difference between a clean stop and a nasty spill. </li>
<li>As far as cold approaches go there&apos;s nobody spies would rather deal with than sales people. They&apos;re talkative, eager to please, and most meet too many people in a year to remember them all. And, no matter what a salesman has going, on they can&apos;t bear to offend a potential customer. </li>
<li>Setting up a blackmail is about more than knocking your target out and snapping pictures of things he won&apos;t remember. It starts much earlier with all the things he will remember. You need to make sure that by the time you knock him out he&apos;s ready to actually believe that he did anything. Once it&apos;s time to spike your target&apos;s drink, the important thing is to control the dose. Mix too much sedative with alcohol and you shut down the part of the brain that controls the heart and lungs. Which means your target won&apos;t be sleeping… He&apos;ll be dead. </li>
<li>There&apos;s always a risk when using a stolen car in an operation, but there are ways to minimize that risk. Take it from an employee parking lot during mid-day and chances are it won&apos;t be missed for hours. You want an older model to avoid anti-theft devices and a common neutral color that won&apos;t attract attention. Of course it doesn&apos;t matter how carefully you choose a car if you have to drive it through a police check-point. </li>
<li>A car on fire makes a great diversion, but it takes a few minutes to get it fully engulfed. If you don&apos;t have much time to spare, you find the closest burning materials that will create the most smoke: like old newspapers and fast food bags doused in hand-sanitizer. Stuff them into rolled up rubber floor mats and you&apos;ve created a vent that will focus the flames into one area. And the more focused the flames, the faster everything burns. </li>
<li>A successful blackmail depends on the psychological state of your target. Leading with your demand can risk putting him on the defensive right from the start. But if you start by showing him how his world is about to crash down first, he&apos;ll be looking for the key to his salvation and be more likely to take it when you offer it to him. Of course no blackmail attempt can succeed if your target has no fear of being extorted. </li>
<li>The passage of time is one of the most often used tools in counter-intelligence. It allows an adversary to observe you and determine whether you&apos;ve been followed. Then, it&apos;s just a matter if they&apos;ve seen enough to make a new acquaintance or a corpse. </li>
<li>Spies feed enemies false information all the time. Sometimes though you have to give up the real thing, actual intelligence that puts innocent people in danger. It&apos;s rough rolling the dice with someone else&apos;s life; but sometimes it&apos;s the only play. </li>
<li>When you&apos;ve been driven to a meeting in a head bag, figuring out your location can be a challenge. If you know how long you were on the road, you can use the local speed limits to calculate a general area and if you can get to a window, local landmarks can narrow it down even further. It&apos;s the sort of thing you learn in the boy scouts, except boy scouts rarely do it with a gun to their back. </li>
<li>A good defensive position is known as a force multiplier. One man can hold off three others as long as he can remain well protected, while keeping up a steady stream of suppressing fire. Only problem is doing that requires a lot of ammunition and when it&apos;s all gone, your defensive position very quickly becomes a death trap. </li>
<li>Taking a hostage is only as effective as his relationship with his rescuers. The more they value his life, the more leverage you have. Of course if your hostage doesn&apos;t value his own life, all bets are off. </li></ul>
