<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><li>When you work with people, you wanna know everything about them: their history, their associates, who&apos;s contacting them. Although sometimes there are details you&apos;d rather not know. </li>
<li>If you&apos;re driving a sports coupe, you&apos;re not going to be able to lose an off-road vehicle off-road. Your best bet is to get them on the road, where you have the advantage. It&apos;s less about speed than it is about maneuverability. You need to put yourself in a position where you can do something they can&apos;t. </li>
<li>For certain kinds of criminals, partying hard serves an important management function. You can keep your eye on your employees during the off-hours and keep them spending money so they&apos;re hungry for the next score. </li>
<li>Bar fights aren&apos;t just a way to blow off steam. They&apos;re a great way to showcase your leadership skills and they&apos;re a team-building exercise. There&apos;s also no better way for someone new to get noticed. </li>
<li>Dealing with an aggressive adversary isn&apos;t always about showing strength. Sometimes it&apos;s best to show weakness. If they believe they can dominate you, they&apos;ll drop their guard. Of course, that means getting dominated. </li>
<li>When you need to distract someone without raising suspicions, it helps to play to preconceptions. Tourists are fat, old people are cranky, and girls can&apos;t drive.</li>
<li>Counterfeiting pharmaceuticals is pretty straight forward; fill some vials with your choice of beverage. The trick is to keep people from looking closer; with some compressed gas from your local farming supply store, and a few cryogenic containers, you can convince people if they get a little too curious they could loose a finger to frostbite. </li>
<li>Dealing with a trained operative is like playing chess with a master. Dealing with criminals, on the other hand, is like playing checkers with a three year-old: they like to change the rules. </li>
<li>Using a Zodiac to catch a yacht has certain advantages. It&apos;s low to the water, so it&apos;s hard to see coming. It tops out at a brisk 60 miles per hour and it&apos;s designed to turn on a dime. Of course, the one disadvantage is it can make for a bumpy ride.</li>
<li>Navy S.E.A.Ls are trained to hold their breath for three to five minutes under water. If you&apos;re an ex-Navy S.E.A.L. you probably still have the chops; but, there&apos;s only one way to find out. </li>
<li>Need the police to respond right away? Call ahead. If you&apos;ve reported a few minor crimes within a six block radius, you can be sure someone will show up when you need them. </li>
<li>Most people think that shooting the gas tank of a vehicle makes it explode. Unless a car&apos;s on fire, you&apos;ll just spill a few bucks worth of gas. An explosion requires something extra like a few bags of acetone peroxide taped to the gas tank.</li>
<li>Anyone who played soccer knows there&apos;s a long nerve that runs down the shin. Hit that nerve and people lock up in pain.</li>
<li>Arms dealers keep gunpowder handy to manufacture custom-made rounds but gunpowder doesn&apos;t need to be in a bullet to be dangerous. Even muzzle flare can set it off. So when dispersed through a room, anyone with half a brain puts his gun away. </li></ul>
