<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At <strong>Michael Westen’s </strong>meeting with <strong>Gilroy</strong>, he was introduced to <strong><em>Claude</em></strong>, <em>&quot;the best thief in the western hemisphere.&quot;</em>
 Gilroy wanted them to break into the Chilean Consulate for some 
documents supporting the “big job” that he was doing.  Back at the loft,
 <strong>Sugar</strong>, the drug dealer who used to live below M, pulled up in his moving “boom box” and said he had <em>“come in peace, bro.”</em> Sugar wanted to hire M to help his “slow” cousin get away from some gangsters. A big time robber named <strong>Lynch </strong>had targeted his cousin, <strong>Dougie</strong>,
 for some unknown reason and had beat Sugar up when he had tried to get 
Lynch to back off. M refused to help so Sugar left and, as Fiona was 
just raising her eyebrows to start ragging on him, <strong>Madeline </strong>called;
 so M jumped at the chance to leave. Madeline was getting the “take a 
bite out of crime” award from the police for reporting cars that M had 
stolen and was finished with. She wanted M to attend the chief of police
 ceremony with her and would listen to absolutely no reason. Equal to 
Madeline’s self-absorption, <strong>Fiona </strong>claimed she &quot;just 
couldn’t remember&quot; anything she had found out about Claude due to 
worrying about Sugar and Dougie. Eventually, she revealed that Claude 
was just an alias of former Australian S.I.S. member: &quot;<strong>Tomas Smalling</strong>&quot;
 and that &quot;Gilroy isn&apos;t your problem either.&quot; So… M met Sugar who 
brought what he thought M needed in the trunk of his car: guns and duct tape; and was disappointed when M said that if he wanted his help he had
 to get out of town and wait for his call.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam found out that Lynch hit everything from banks to car washes, and 
never got arrested &quot;because they never leave anyone behind. He’s a 
public health hazard.&quot; Fiona broke into Lynch’s compound and planted a 
bug in the TV remote as well as finding a room full of scuba air tanks, 
dive watches, vests and machine guns. M followed Lynch and realized that
 he and his guys were going to Sugar’s house to kill him – Sugar had not
 left town. Instead of getting out, like M warned him, Sugar ignored Ms 
instructions and shot back, which then required M to come in and haul 
him out... and to the hospital, wounded. Gilroy gave M and Claude 
synchronized watches telling them that &quot;by the end of the day our hearts
 would beat as one,&quot; and that Claude was lead on the job. Claude told M,
 &quot;just you make a diversion and I’ll do the job.&quot; Sam pretended to be 
Chuck Finley at the flower mart in order to check to see what Dougie 
knew about Lynch’s job – he was just a “helper” on the loading dock of a
 florist warehouse. Lynch gave a party, which Fiona crashed and saw them
 making fun of “the retard.” The bug revealed that Lynch had just gotten
 off the phone with a man named <strong>Bolo</strong>, who would find 
them a thief to get the last piece of hardware they needed. Barry told M
 and Sam what Bolo looked like so they could intercept the guy and plant
 M in with Lynch pretending to be the thief for Lynch’s job. They 
pretended that they had injected Bolo with a poison for which he would 
receive the antidote after helping them. Ms cover was &quot;<strong><em>D.J.</em></strong>&quot;
 a “procurement” expert and he was asked to obtain a “jaws of life,” 
which could only be obtained from emergency personnel. They could not 
figure that just dealing with flowers would make it worth such an 
effort, so Sam went back to obtain a delivery schedule from the company 
thinking that a delivery might just be a ruse to launch a heist.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Fiona found that Claude’s preferred M.O. in his past jobs was to use 
free-climbing up sides of buildings. M went to Madeline’s to get a city 
inspector’s shirt that his dad always used when he was stealing 
equipment. Madeline revealed a secret panel in the closet that M never 
knew about. She also had bought M a silly tie on clearance and when M 
told her that something had come up and he couldn’t attend her award 
ceremony &quot;because people might get hurt&quot; she sulked and played the 
martyr. M scouted the location of Claude’s future heist and dripped some
 oil on one of his future hand-holds. Then he went to a fire training 
center and got their jaw’s, pretending he was taking it for needed 
maintenance. Sam and Fiona surmised that expensive art at the Hotel 
Milano must be Lynch’s target next week; but, when M delivered the Jaws 
to Lynch he discovered that the job was on for today. Sam then realized 
that it wasn&apos;t a delivery they were after but an armored truck was due 
to pickup receipts almost immediately; so they had to wing it. Mike took
 out a guy on the roof who was going to pump gas into the air ducts… for
 which they had needed the air tanks. Fiona set an explosive in a 
garbage can to warn the armored truck away. Sam went inside to extract 
Dougie, but he wouldn’t come. Lynch began firing so Dougie tipped a rack
 over on him in order to save Sam. They both got out as Sam blasted shut
 the door lock. M turned on the gas then answered Lynch’s frantic phone 
call to his man on the roof. He told Lynch that his man was not 
available and that the cops were on the way.  He said that he &quot;hoped 
they get there before your air tanks run out.&quot; Sugar told M that he 
wondered how many times he had to get shot before he started listening 
to him.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At the heist with Claude, M caused a car to smoke for his diversion and 
Claude took to the walls. However he fell off of oily hand-hold and 
broke his ankle on the ground. That made M able to finish the job early 
and he showed up at Madeline’s award ceremony in his new tie.  That made
 her finally see reason so she let M leave. Later, Gilroy told M that 
Claude <em>“didn&apos;t survive his injuries,”</em> and that the documents were now Ms responsibility. He said <em>&quot;you should consider it a reason for living… as it were.”</em>
</p>
</xml>
