<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In <span class="new" title="Warri (page does not exist)" data-uncrawlable-url="L3dpa2kvV2Fycmk/YWN0aW9uPWVkaXQmcmVkbGluaz0x">Warri</span>, <span class="new" title="Nigeria (page does not exist)" data-uncrawlable-url="L3dpa2kvTmlnZXJpYT9hY3Rpb249ZWRpdCZyZWRsaW5rPTE=">Nigeria</span>, American covert operative <a href="/wiki/Michael_Westen" title="Michael Westen">Michael Westen</a> is waiting on a street corner, then picked up by two armed thugs and whisked to a local hotel to meet with <a href="/wiki/Boris" title="Boris">Boris</a>, a &quot;wannabe warlord&quot; whose thugs have been attacking offshore oil rigs. Boris and his thugs both address Michael as &quot;Mr. CIA.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael is the courier to deliver a bribe from the U.S. oil companies. It is just another assignment for Michael... until he calls his contact to complete the wire transfer; the man on the other end of the line tells Michael a burn notice has been issued for him, and he is blacklisted from all future contact. Michael slowly closes his phone and turns to Boris, manufacturing a sheepish laugh...
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The scene cuts to a few moments later, when Michael is curled into a ball on the floor of the hotel room with Boris&apos;s goons are beating him to a pulp, and Boris, brandishing a gun, demanding his money.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael &quot;confesses&quot; that he planned to steal Boris&apos;s money and blame someone else, promising that he knows where the money is and can return it. Boris tells two of his thugs to take Michael away. Once they are in the lobby, Michael fakes an attack of nausea and convinces the thugs to drag him into the bathroom.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In spite of his injuries, Michael overpowers his two captors, knocks them unconscious against the sink and urinals, then takes a pistol off one and executes both of them. Attempting to make a casual exit from the hotel, he is noticed by more of Boris&apos;s goons and forced to steal a motorcycle and race to the airport, with the thugs in pursuit and shooting at him.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael lures the thugs&apos; car into a crowded market, that forces the thugs to brake while Michael slips through the crowd on his motorcycle. When the thugs raise their guns to order the crowd out of the way, the crowd produce guns of their own, quickly forcing the outnumbered thugs to surrender.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Reaching the airport, Michael barely manages to stumble onto a departing plane, before he passes out.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael wakes up, battered, in a motel. To his great astonishment, he has company; his ex-girlfriend <a href="/wiki/Fiona_Glenanne" title="Fiona Glenanne">Fiona Glenanne</a>, a former <a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external text" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irish_Republican_Army">IRA</a> operative; she had been in New York, but a curious maid went through Michael&apos;s wallet and found her still listed as his emergency contact. Fiona was intrigued to get the call, explaining that if Michael really was about to die, she wouldn&apos;t let him do so without seeing him one last time - and telling him what a bastard he was.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael&apos;s worst fears are soon confirmed. Asking where he is, Fiona informs him that he has been dumped in <a href="/wiki/Miami" title="Miami">Miami</a>, his hometown. She has no idea why, she was only told that the airline was &quot;instructed&quot; by <a href="/wiki/The_Organization" title="The Organization">someone</a> to bring him there. She also mentions, with malice aforethought, that she had a &quot;lovely chat&quot; on the phone with <a href="/wiki/Madeline_Westen" title="Madeline Westen">Michael&apos;s mother</a>, and suggests he go see her while he&apos;s in town.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Fiona also adds that there&apos;s a two-man team from the FBI surveilling him. Michael pleads for her to provide a distraction, and she extracts a promise to buy her dinner.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael attempts to upgrade to a four-star hotel, but his credit card is declined. Going to the bank, Michael learns that his bank accounts have been frozen. He urgently calls his handler, <a href="/wiki/Dan_Siebels" title="Dan Siebels">Dan Siebels</a>, but the office refuses to put him through.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Keeping the feds off his tail is a challenge, though. He checks into a motel catering to teenagers on spring break, knowing the feds will have trouble blending in.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Needing to evade them completely, he bribes two skateboarding kids to tell a beat cop that the federal agent in the car tailing Michael asked them to sit on his lap. The beat cop jerks the fed out of the car, and Michael slips away.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Stuck in Miami, and broke, Michael approaches <a href="/wiki/Lucy_Chen" title="Lucy Chen">Lucy Chen</a>, an old protege of his now working in the private sector. She says she doesn&apos;t have any contacts high enough to give her any information on his burn notice, but says that if he needs some cash, she has a job he may be interested in. She also gives him some pocket cash to clean himself up and get some new clothes, remarking that he looks &quot;terrible.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In order to survive and fund his own personal investigation, Michael enlists the help of the only two &quot;friends&quot; he has: Fiona and <a href="/wiki/Sam_Axe" title="Sam Axe">Sam</a>; a washed-out ex-Navy SEAL now sponging off &quot;half the rich widows in Miami,&quot; who also does occasional grunt work for Lucy. Sam helps fix Michael up with a temporary apartment, and gives him the name of the potential client.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">An estate caretaker, <a href="/wiki/Javier" title="Javier">Javier</a>, has been accused of stealing valuable art from his employer, real estate mogul <a href="/wiki/Graham_Pyne" title="Graham Pyne">Graham Pyne</a>. All evidence points to it being an inside job and Javier, with very little money to offer ($4,600), has nowhere else to turn, fearing he&apos;ll be arrested momentarily.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Posing as a concerned friend, Michael first talks to Pyne, then to Pyne&apos;s head of security, a washed-out Army Ranger named <a href="/wiki/Vincent" title="Vincent">Vincent</a>. Pyne expresses polite concern, but Vincent says there&apos;s no doubt that Javier is guilty and it&apos;s only Pyne&apos;s soft heart that has prevented Javier from being arrested immediately. Michael&apos;s antenna go up - wherever there&apos;s money, you can bet you&apos;re not getting the whole story.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael is introduced to his new apartment by <a href="/wiki/Oleg" title="Oleg">Oleg</a>, Sam&apos;s contact, who also has former ties to Russian covert operatives, and is tickled to meet the notorious Michael Westen in person. As he is trying to make a home out of the place, Michael is stunned to take a call on his cell phone from his mother.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael tries to get out of seeing his mother, saying he won&apos;t be in town for very long, but she insists that he drive her to the doctor, despite his protests that he doesn&apos;t have a car. &quot;You&apos;ll think of something,&quot; she says cheerfully, and hangs up.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael has held up admirably thus far, but the conversation with his mother prompts him to mash a pillow into his face and scream in frustration.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael has &quot;borrowed&quot; a car and is driving <a href="/wiki/Madeline_Westen" title="Madeline Westen">Madeline</a> to the hospital. She reproaches him for missing <a href="/wiki/Frank_Westen" title="Frank Westen">his father</a>&apos;s funeral (by eight years) and she still can&apos;t understand why they didn&apos;t get along better, as they were so much alike. Exasperated, Michael tells her that he and Frank were nothing alike, and everything Michael did, good or bad, was an excuse for Frank to smack him around. Madeline appears blithely ignorant of Frank&apos;s violent behavior toward his sons (or else she&apos;s deliberately put it out of her mind). She tells him how glad she is that Michael is back home, since the whole family needs him: his brother, <a href="/wiki/Nate_Westen" title="Nate Westen">Nate</a>, is &quot;a mess,&quot; and she herself is sick with some persistent malady that no doctor has successfully diagnosed. Michael tries to explain to her that he will not be in Miami for very long, but is distracted when he notices an unmarked car behind them.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For each turn Michael makes, Madeline criticizes him for taking her further away from the hospital, while Michael is trying, without much success, to prevent her from smoking in the car since it&apos;s not his.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Managing to lose the tail car, Michael finally pulls up in front of the hospital. As Madeline gets out, he makes a call on his cell phone, trying again to reach Dan Siebels. Again, his secretary refuses to put the call through, so Michael decides on a more insistent approach.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">On his way to his new loft, Michael encounters a drug dealer squatting on the stairs, who warns him that his boss, <a href="/wiki/Sugar" title="Sugar">Sugar</a>, is in charge of the block and not to make trouble for him or his &quot;employees.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Oblivious to the loud music blasting from the club underneath his loft, Michael assembles a fake pipe bomb, garnished with fertilizer, and places it in a box addressed to Siebels.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Turning his attention to Javier&apos;s problem, Michael approaches Sam at a hotel pool and asks him to set up a meeting with <a href="/wiki/Barry_Burkowski" title="Barry Burkowski">Barry</a>.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Meeting Barry in coffee shop, Michael asks for the name of an art dealer who might know how to track the stolen artwork. Barry demurs, saying that art is a bad place to park money, since art transactions are heavily scrutinized by the I.R.S., and value can plummet without warning - &quot;some schmuck in New York says the wrong thing, you take a bath.&quot; Michael insists, and Barry gives him a name, politely asking Michael to remember who &quot;gave you love&quot; when Michael was down.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In a meeting with <a href="/wiki/Walter" title="Walter">Walter</a>, Barry&apos;s contact, Michael pretends to be interested in buying the same era and style of art that was stolen from Pyne, trying to see if any such pieces have come on the market. Walter says no, he has not heard of anything; in fact, there were several such pieces discreetly offered for sale a few months ago, but the seller was disappointed with the prices he was offered. Walter says he doesn&apos;t recall the man&apos;s name, only that he is &quot;one of these big condo developers.&quot; He apologizes for not being more helpful, but Michael says, on the contrary, he has been extremely helpful. Walter leans in and asks if Michael is interested in seeing some Greco-Roman nude wrestling sculptures. Michael, for all his long experience at reading people, is unsure whether or not Walter is coming on to him, so he manufactures a laugh, as if Walter just made a joke.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At night, Michael easily breaks into Mr. Pyne&apos;s house, removes a yogurt from the fridge (for authenticity), then locates a wall safe behind a painting.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Cracking Pyne&apos;s safe is the work of a few seconds: a lump of wax applied to the scanner lifts the fingerprint, which Michael transfers to a sheet of film and presses to the scanner, opening the safe. Inside, Michael finds financial documents of a highly interesting nature.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Exiting his apartment to visit Javier, Michael encounters Sugar himself, who is aggravated that his new neighbor doesn&apos;t seem intimidated by him. Michael calmly stares the drug dealer down, but Sugar jabs Michael in the belly, causing him to double over in pain.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael hoped to avoid fighting, but the pain causes him to retaliate with a quick move that leaves Sugar groaning on the pavement.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Visiting Javier at his home, Michael tells Javier that Pyne has framed him. The documents removed from Pyne&apos;s safe reveal that he is nearly broke, and desperately in need of quick cash. Vincent committed the robbery, at Pyne&apos;s direction, allowing him to collect the insurance money and allow Javier to take the blame. The fact that Pyne spoke up in Javier&apos;s defense only makes it that much easier for him to collect the insurance, claiming he had no idea that a &quot;trusted employee&quot; would rip him off.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Shakily, Javier asks what his options are. Michael says he could flee Miami, and stay away until the statute of limitations runs out (about ten years); he could go to court, in which case he will likely lose and be sent to prison for twenty years; or he could stay and fight back. Javier decides to fight back - or, more precisely, to have Michael do it for him. Michael says things may get ugly, and advises Javier not to return to work, and to stay with a friend until the mess blows over.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Still in his guise as Javier&apos;s concerned friend, Michael confronts Pyne with the incriminating evidence, &quot;suggesting&quot; that he drop the charges against Javier if he doesn&apos;t want his financial situation spread all over the newspapers. Pyne appears shaken, and Michael politely lets himself out. Michael has barely cleared the front door of the mansion before he hears Pyne yelling at Vincent behind him, causing him to smile. However, he knows it is too early to claim victory.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael buys a pair of cell phones from a street vendor and crafts a serviceable electronic bug.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Over dinner with Fiona, he tells her about his plan to plant the bug in Pyne&apos;s car the next day, and asks her if she&apos;d be willing to help. She agrees, and asks him if he&apos;s given any thought to re-starting their relationship, now that he has some time on his hands. Uncomfortably, Michael says he is good at many things, but relationships have never been one of them. She wryly points out that if a serious relationship is too taxing, Miami is the perfect place for him to hook up with a &quot;twenty-four year old with big, fake tits.&quot; Smiling ruefully, he admits that those types of women are &quot;too boring for him.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Taking her back to the loft, Michael is trying to think of a tactful way to avoid inviting her up, but the dilemma is solved when a thug with a gun appears with a message from Sugar; move out, or else. For Fi, it is the perfect way to cap off the evening, disarming the thug and knocking him senseless with Michael standing by and watching. Suddenly ambivalent about wanting her to go, Michael starts to ask her up, but she breezes away with a casual &quot;goodnight.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The next morning, Michael is woken by a call from <a href="/wiki/Dan_Siebels" title="Dan Siebels">Dan Siebels</a>, who has spent a few uncomfortable hours with the FBI after receiving Michael&apos;s fake bomb. He says he believes Michael&apos;s been framed, but there&apos;s nothing he can do to help him, not even showing him a copy of the burn notice. He also warns Michael that there are still people who are on his side, but another fake bomb, and Siebels won&apos;t be one of them. He tells Michael not to leave Miami, unless he wants an FBI manhunt after him.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Sam are waiting outside the office of Pyne&apos;s lawyer. While they are waiting, Michael&apos;s phone rings - it&apos;s his mother yet again. Michael silences the phone, but knows he can&apos;t avoid seeing his mother indefinitely.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As Pyne comes out, Vincent opens the car door for him, while Fiona breezes by, distracting the men as only she can do. With the help of a cab driver friend, <a href="/wiki/Pierre" title="Pierre">Pierre</a>, Sam fakes a roadside dispute that ends with Pierre punching him in the face, sending him sprawling onto the passenger seat of Pyne&apos;s car. Before Vincent yanks him out, the bug is under the seat, with no one the wiser.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">With some tools from the local hardware store, Michael measures the thickness of the wall outside Sugar&apos;s apartment with a stud finder, then uses duct tape to mark a square where the plaster is thinnest. Then he goes to the rear of the apartment, unscrews the sheet metal and cuts the plaster with a boxcutter, creating an easy entrance for himself. Once Sugar is home, Michael knocks on the door with a cheery &quot;Hi, it&apos;s your neighbor!&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Standing to the side of the door, Michael raises the gun taken from Sugar&apos;s thug, with the barrel inside a tin can as a makeshift silencer, and fires through the thin part of the wall.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Hearing nothing, Michael fires again.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">This time a scream comes from behind the door.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">While Sugar is furiously pointing a revolver at the door, Michael circles around to the rear of the apartment, breaks through the weakened plaster with a hammer, walks in through the hole and disarms Sugar, telling him he has twenty minutes to clear out, or else. Sugar quickly agrees, and Michael hands him bandages and disinfectant, telling him he should be able to limp to a hospital with enough time to get the wound treated and not limp for the rest of his life. His job done, Michael exits, leaving Sugar free to scream in pain.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Going to see his mother at home, Michael again tries to say he will not be in Miami long, but Madeline breaks down crying, begging him to stay long enough to help with his brother.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In the middle of Madeline&apos;s crying jag, Michael receives an urgent call from Sam, who has been listening to the bug, and plays a recording telling Vincent to go to Javier&apos;s home and kidnap his son, <a href="/wiki/David" title="David">David</a>, to turn the tables on the blackmailer. Michael grabs a screwdriver and some zip-ties from Madeline&apos;s garage and rushes out.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Looking for just the right car to hijack, Michael stops a 60&apos;s-era muscle car and orders the driver into the passenger side. Michael intercepts Vincent on the way to Javier&apos;s house and rams his car; Michael deliberately picked a car with no airbags, while Vincent is knocked unconscious when his deploy.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">With Vincent disabled, Michael hops out and assures the car&apos;s distressed owner that the insurance will pay for most of the damage, plus the hijacking was for a good cause. Michael picks up David from school and takes him back to his loft, calling Javier to collect him in a few hours.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael notices David crying and trying to hide it. Michael asks why, and David admits that he is being bullied at school, which is why he wishes he were a &quot;tough guy&quot; like Michael. Shaking his head ruefully, Michael lifts his shirt and displays the bruises from his beating in Nigeria. Two black belts, he tells David, and Michael still got his ass kicked - David has nothing to be ashamed of. Michael has lost as many fights as he&apos;s won, but he&apos;s an expert at winning. Michael gives David some training, including the important fact that when dealing with a gang, the best strategy is to go after the leader - it works on elementary school boys as well as it works on Afghan warlords. Michael trains David to play possum, draw the gang leader in, then knock him down and give him a few good punches.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael follows Sam to a coffee shop and sees him meeting with FBI Agents <a href="/wiki/Harris" title="Harris">Harris</a> and <a href="/wiki/Lane" title="Lane">Lane</a>. Michael casually drops into the seat next to Sam&apos;s and asks if they know why he&apos;s been burned. They say they don&apos;t, but they&apos;re simply following orders. They also warn him not to get &quot;cute,&quot; because, contrary to what he might think, he still has plenty to lose, starting with his mother and brother in Miami.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">After the agents leave, Sam shrinks into a guilty little ball, pleading that the FBI can erase his Navy pension with the touch of a button if he doesn&apos;t play along. Michael says he understands, and would prefer to have an old friend like Sam feeding the feds information than someone he doesn&apos;t know. Grateful for this understanding, Sam makes a half-hearted offer to assist Michael in the confrontation with Pyne, but Michael says he has things covered.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael prepares Javier&apos;s house for an armed assault, covering the windows, positioning a mirror to blind anyone in the hallway, and rigging Sugar&apos;s revolver with blanks and a remote-controlled igniter. He also hooks Javier&apos;s phone to a call-forwarding device.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Pyne and Vincent pull up outside Javier&apos;s house, and Vincent calls the home number to ensure Javier is there. When Javier picks up at the forwarded location, it is enough to fool Vincent.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Vincent kicks down the door, Javier is not there, just Michael. Pyne angrily demands the return of his files, but Michael casually tells Vincent his gun&apos;s safety is still on. As soon as Vincent tilts his gun to look, Michael jumps him. Suddenly gunfire erupts behind Pyne, who grabs Vincent&apos;s dropped gun in a panic. Seeing a shape come around the corner of the hallway, Pyne (half-blinded by the reflected sunlight) fires a shot in panic. Then his vision clears just enough to see Vincent on the floor with a gunshot wound to his abdomen.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">With Pyne tied up, Michael jauntily disassembles the pistol and carefully presses Pyne&apos;s fingertips all over the interior parts (causing Pyne to yelp in pain, since the recently-fired barrel is still hot). Vincent is lying on the couch, clutching the wound in his side and pleading to be taken to a hospital. Michael - treating Vincent more like a little boy with a nervous bladder than a full-grown man with a gunshot wound - tells him to stay quiet until the grown-ups have finished their chat.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael shows Pyne the trick revolver - the source of the shots that spooked Pyne - then lays out the facts: Pyne is guilty of shooting Vincent, and the weapon that fired the shot is now &quot;a crime lab&apos;s wet dream.&quot; In addition, Michael has Pyne on tape instructing Vincent to commit a kidnapping, which is a federal crime that automatically comes with a lengthy prison sentence - &quot;at your age, that&apos;s life.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Pyne breaks down and asks Michael what he wants, and Michael lays out his demands: Vincent will confess to the robbery, clearing Javier&apos;s name, and Javier will be dismissed with a generous severance package, along with a college fund for David. Pyne agrees, and nervously asks about the financial documents. Michael says he&apos;ll hang on to those, and warns that he&apos;ll be keeping an eye on Pyne to make sure he doesn&apos;t try anything else.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">After settling things with Javier, Michael drops by David&apos;s school and witnesses an altercation in the playground. Noticing Lane and Harris parked nearby, Michael walks up to the F.B.I. men and asks to borrow their binoculars: he knows they have them, but they&apos;re not using them, since he&apos;s standing right in front of them. Lane grudgingly hands them over and Michael watches with satisfaction as David knocks the bullies&apos; leader down, then jumps on him and punches him repeatedly. Michael grins.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael returns home to find his door open and the floor covered with surveillance photos. It&apos;s not the FBI, because pictures of them tailing Michael are included, but <a href="/wiki/The_Organization" title="The Organization">whoever it is</a>, they&apos;ve been tracking his every move. And they&apos;ve left a message.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><i>&quot;There&apos;s nothing worse for a spook than knowing you&apos;re being played. Someone is pulling strings. The who? Not some intelligence agency bureaucrat in a cubicle. This is someone with more - style. Not FBI either, they&apos;re not this creative and they don&apos;t do surveillance on their own guys. This is someone who knows what he&apos;s doing; someone who wants to send a message: Welcome to Miami.&quot;</i>
</p>
</xml>
