<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Still searching for why he was burned, Michael enters a local conference, brazenly enters the Security office and browses the logs for the name of some conference attendee that he feels might be able to give him information. Getting a name, he narrowly escapes the now-wise security staff.

</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael limps back to his apartment, fuming because <a href="/wiki/Fiona_Glenanne" title="Fiona Glenanne">Fiona</a> was supposed to be waiting for him with their getaway car, but drove off instead and left him to walk two miles with a twisted ankle. Fiona, who&apos;s broken into the apartment again, reminds him that the car was stolen, and she couldn&apos;t afford to wait around in full view of his FBI surveillance. She argues that Michael needs a car, and she needs a key to his apartment instead of having to break in all the time. She challenges him that he sees either of these things as a sign of commitment that he can&apos;t face. Michael argues that he doesn&apos;t have any assets with which to purchase a car, and Fiona sweetly informs him that <a href="/wiki/Madeline_Westen" title="Madeline Westen">his mother</a> is offering the use of <a href="/wiki/Frank_Westen" title="Frank Westen">his father</a>&apos;s old Dodge Charger.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">While Michael is repairing his apartment door, he is approached by his landlord, Oleg, who needs Michael to solve a problem for him. Cara Stagner, the best waitress at his nightclub, hasn&apos;t shown up for work for two weeks, apparently because someone is threatening her. Oleg offers Michael free rent for two months if he helps Cara get back to work. Michael negotiates him up to four, and agrees.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In her home, which she hasn&apos;t left for two weeks, Cara explains to Michael that she saw a pizza delivery guy accidentally rear-end another man&apos;s Lexus, then saw the Lexus driver savagely beat the pizza guy with a steering wheel lock. Now the pizza guy is in a coma. Cara called the police and gave them the Lexus driver&apos;s license plate number, but now she has been receiving death threats. After meeting Cara and her teenage daughter, Sophie, Michael agrees to help.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">As for tracking down his burn notice, Michael has identified an Egyptian spy he knows, Akhom Thabet, who is attending the conference. Akhom owes Michael a favor, for saving his life. However, he can&apos;t go back to the hotel, since the security is now on the lookout for him. So he asks Fiona to shadow Akhom and find a moment when Michael can get him alone; in exchange, he promises to ask his mother for the Charger.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Madeline is delighted to hear that Michael will accept his father&apos;s car, taking it as a sign that he&apos;s staying in Miami. Michael examines the car and finds it needs a complete overhaul and new spark plugs.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">With the Charger useless for the moment, Michael returns to the Stagners&apos; problem. <a href="/wiki/Sam_Axe" title="Sam Axe">Sam</a> helps Michael out by identifying the name of the thug threatening them, one <a href="/wiki/Alvaro_DeSantos" title="Alvaro DeSantos">Alvaro DeSantos</a>.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael&apos;s conversation with him doesn&apos;t go well, however, when he learns that DeSantos is in fact a Miami &quot;employee&quot; of a Colombian drug cartel. In fact, DeSantos says that Cara and Sophie will cease to be a problem, momentarily.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael manages to warn Fiona just in time for her to send the thugs scurrying with improvised Molotov cocktails using the liquor cabinet and a few rags. Fiona is having the time of her life, but Cara and Sophie are badly shaken, and must be moved to a safer location.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Hiding them in Madeline&apos;s garage, complete with cool tricked-out on-the-cheap spy techniques for keeping remote tabs on their security, is Michael&apos;s first idea, but the teenage Sophie is predictably miserable, especially when Michael forbids the use of her cell phone. She wants to attend her school&apos;s Spring Dance. He tells them to sit tight for the next few days, while he approaches their problem from a different angle.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">He approaches Bruce Gellman, the cartel&apos;s Miami lawyer, by spiking his tires in the middle of the lawyer&apos;s own neighborhood. Michael says that DeSantos has been a &quot;bad boy,&quot; and is risking an investigation that might upset the &quot;big boys&quot; in Columbia, who should tell DeSantos to back off. The lawyer says he doesn&apos;t discuss his client&apos;s business, but Michael asks him to think it over, promising to meet him again the next day.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">While waiting for his meeting with Gellman, Michael surprises a cartel thug trying to kill him with a car bomb. At gunpoint, the thug admits that Gellman has received orders from Colombia to &quot;kill you all&quot; - Cara, Sophie, and anyone trying to protect them.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Since he needs a new plan, he proposes sending Cara and Sophie permanently to Buffalo, New York, while having Fiona plant evidence on their computer of a trip to Salt Lake City, Utah. Sophie pitches a fit at having to leave Miami permanently.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael approaches Akhom at a dinner meeting, reminding him that he once saved his life. If that isn&apos;t enough to enlist Akhom&apos;s assistance, Michael ups the ante by threatening to expose his double-dealings to the Sudanese delegates the Egyptian is meeting with.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Akhom is not happy, particularly when Michael tells him it&apos;s a copy of the Homeland Security Directive that blacklisted him that he wants. In the middle of their meeting, Michael&apos;s cell phone rings, activated by the motion detector outside the safe house.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael rushes to the safe house and finds Cara in hysterics. Sophie sneaked out of the garage while Cara was asleep, planning to attend her school&apos;s spring formal, ignoring Michael&apos;s warnings that the bad guys are likely watching her school.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael rushes to the school and finds Sophie, who starts complaining about his over-protectiveness... until he jams the door in the nick of time against two Colombian thugs charging at her. Michael drags a now-terrified Sophie into the school and hides her in the auto shop. When the two thugs follow their trail, Michael tells Sophie to run while he stays behind, and promises to meet her behind the gym in five minutes.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Ingenuity wins the day again, as Michael booby-traps the door to the shop by heating the door knob with a blowtorch, and disarms the two attackers, escaping with Sophie and some spark plugs for the Charger.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Now resigned to the fact that she and her mother must leave Miami, Sophie sadly confides that she was really getting to like the boy she was going to the dance with. Michael tries to offer some romantic advice, confiding that he had to leave Fiona without ever saying goodbye, but they reconnected years later. Sophie asks, hopefully, whether this means that, if two people are meant to be together, they will find each other. Michael gives an unconvincing &quot;sure,&quot; but Sophie sees through him and adds with a smile, &quot;you&apos;re really bad at this.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Thanks to Sophie, the bad guys now know that Cara has not yet left Miami. Michael comes up with a new plan: turning the cartel against DeSantos. Michael videotapes DeSantos, while Sam records an innocent phone conversation with him, as Fiona checks off all the phrases they need him to say on a pad.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael then edits the tape so that it appears as though DeSantos is ratting out the cartel, and syncs it with the videotape. Sam passes the tape along to Agents <a href="/wiki/Lane" title="Lane">Lane</a> and <a href="/wiki/Harris" title="Harris">Harris</a>. The next day, Michael stops Gellman&apos;s car again in his own neighborhood. Displaying no fear, the lawyer thanks Michael for not blowing out his tires this time. Michael himself &quot;thanks&quot; the lawyer for convincing DeSantos to back off from the Stagners and testify about his bosses to the FBI, which Michael buoyantly describes as a &quot;win-win&quot; for everybody: DeSantos gets immunity for the assault charge, and Cara is off the hook.  Gellman gapes in disbelief, and Michael winks, saying he understands that Gellman doesn&apos;t talk about his clients&apos; business, but thanks him all the same.  As he walks away, he Michael stabs a knife into the rear tire, adding &quot;that&apos;s for trying to kill me.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Out of Gellman&apos;s earshot, Michael calls Sam, wagering that Gellman will be on the phone with his own contacts at the FBI &quot;before his tire goes flat&quot; and will have a copy of the incriminating tape on his desk by lunch.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Desantos is last seen being forced into the trunk of a drug cartel car by some angry thugs, under Gellman&apos;s supervision. With DeSantos no longer a factor, the cartel has stopped caring about silencing Cara or Sophie.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Cara and Sophie are grateful to be safe, and even more grateful that they don&apos;t have to leave town. Sophie apologizes for her earlier brattiness and kisses Michael on the cheek.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
Fiona gets her key as a reward, Sam gets a bit of relief from the FBI for turning over the drug cartel guy, and Michael makes his mother happy by reluctantly visiting his father&apos;s grave. He meets Akhom there and is given the copy of the burn notice; there is no information on who issued it, but there is an alpha-numeric tracking code and a special access program code name, &quot;Cold Sunshine.&quot; In Michael&apos;s words, &quot;It&apos;s not much, but it&apos;s a start.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
</xml>
