<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><strong>Fiona </strong>had “<strong>Bud</strong>,” a bail-jumper, in <strong>Michael Westen</strong>’s
 loft when he returned from a jog, hoping that they could take him in 
together and entice M into working with her instead of trying to “get 
back in” to spy-hood. They were met on the stairs by a woman with a 
badge who introduced herself as <strong>Detective Paxson</strong> and 
called Fiona by her full name as she asked if she had a bail-enforcers 
license. When Fiona didn’t, she said this was a warning for harboring a 
fugitive and took Bud away.  Paxton wanted to talk about an “incident” 
where three cars were totaled and three more were blown up – saying that
 there had sure been a lot of explosions since he moved to town. She 
yanked him in for “questioning” to harass him, which was apparently her 
style of handling cases, and smirked <em>“welcome to your worst nightmare.”</em> He spent 24 hrs. in the drunk tank. One of Fiona’s old bail-jumpers, <strong>Stevie </strong>who was doing time on forgery, referred his sister, <strong>Patricia</strong>, to obtain her son back from his divorced father. She wanted someone to knock some sense into <strong>Howard </strong>and M said they weren’t the ones to do it but Fiona said: <em>“not a problem.”</em> <strong>Sam </strong>came to tell M that his new girlfriend, <strong>Miss Reynolds</strong>, had rebuilt the entire engine and that his new detective lady was a <em>“stalker with a badge”</em>
 who had checked storage facilities on the entire Florida peninsula and 
found some video surveillance of him going into a storage unit by 
Homestead. M said he had some C-4 and detonators which needed to move 
before she got a warrant.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Fiona drug M along to go harass the father, as Sam wanted to have 
lunch for giving him the heads up, and his mother called at the last 
minute expecting him to plan a birthday party for himself. M did catch 
Howard, the father, who said that <strong>Brandon </strong>had been 
kidnapped and he didn’t want to tell his wife because she would call the
 police and get him killed. An unknown man had called and wanted 
information about diamond shipments at the place Howard worked. M told 
Howard to demand a face-to-face as well as proof that Brandon was 
unhurt. He did, then <strong>Santora</strong>, the kidnapper, beat him 
up to see if he was being watched by any cops. Santora told Howard that 
he wanted his stones within 24 hours and Sam followed him but he didn’t 
go back anywhere near the boy. M asked Sam to set up some “reverse 
interrogation,’ where you send in one of your own guys to be 
interrogated by the bad guys to see what questions they ask and thereby 
determine what they are worried about. Then when M and Fiona went to 
empty his storage shed Paxton showed up in a surprise sting but M just 
told her that he had come to give her receipts which would prove where 
he had breakfast. Sam stopped Santora in a fake cop car playing 
Detective Finley and told him that he had an informant, <strong><em>Shep</em></strong>,
 who had let slip that Santora was doing something related to a kid. For
 $2k, Sam said, he would let Santora question him first before he took 
him in to the station. <strong>Madeline </strong>flew off the handle 
when Fiona told her that M couldn’t make it to the party and ranted 
about how HE never made any effort! Santora took the bait and Sam then 
beat M up while Santora asked questions and they tap danced around 
answers finding first the name of a café that Santora used. Eventually M
 made up the fact that the guy he was working with was known at the café
 and people called him &quot;Flowers.&quot; Santora called an accomplice named 
Jimmy to go check the Seaside Diner looking for a man named “Flowers.”
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam went outside to call Fiona to go stake out the place and while 
he was gone Santora began cutting on M. Sam heard the screams and pulled
 his gun to back Santora down. Meanwhile Patricia and Howard all of a 
sudden became best buds again. They finally got Santora to reveal that 
Brandon was in a shed behind the house. Fiona got a photo of Jimmy who 
went to check the diner and sent it to Sam. Then she tailed the guy back
 to Hibiscus Island but couldn’t go all the way to the house. As Santora
 was going to call his guys to have Brandon killed, Sam suggested that 
it may be one of Santora’s own team. Then he pantomimed a description 
behind Santora&apos;s back for M to &quot;confess&quot; to meeting. Santora told M that
 the guy he just described was Jimmy and that shep had to die. Sam’s 
counter-plan was to trade guns with Santora then let him kill M out by 
the road to make it easier for him to explain down at the station. When 
Santora walked him out to the road, M flailed at him like a banshee 
until he was out cold then took his car and Sam’s gun. Going to retrieve
 his gun, Sam got the address they were heading to from Santora and 
phoned the island’s “security guard” with it. M called Fiona and 
together they rescued Brandon before Sam got there. Santora and both of 
his guys were arguing and pointing guns at each other, so Sam watching 
from outside merely shot his gun into the ground to set them off firing 
at each other. M told Howard and Patricia that they should make a fresh 
start in another town and Fiona couldn’t resist slipping into her 
manipulation about getting M to make a fresh start. He said he’d settle 
for staying out of jail and took her to the storage unit. M slipped his 
truck right past Paxton’s stake out to the back side of the unit where 
he used a water saw to cut a hole and remove all his contraband. Paxton 
showed up to taunt M saying it wasn’t over. At Madeline’s party they 
could barely swallow her “hand-baked” cake. Sam gave M a &quot;5-pack&quot; of 
imported beer then Madeline stewarded him out so Fiona could get M 
alone. She gave him a sheathed bayonet which had been used during the 
first world war for close range fighting.  M said: <em>“thanks?” </em>Then Fiona repeated what Madeline had told her – <em>“loving mike is always like trench warfare.”</em>  So, whispering in his ear <em>“I thought YOU should arm yourself.”</em>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
</xml>
