<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael started the night by saying a bunch of fancy spy stuff that would help him decode the secret messages in the Bible he found last week. He knew he had to find Simon to decode the messages. He told Sam and Fiona he was trying to get a face-to-face meeting with Simon. He called Vaughn to help get to Simon, who&apos;s locked in a secret prison somewhere. Meanwhile, there was a hurricane coming.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Vaughn met Michael at his place—he was Michael&apos;s trusted teammate on this particular project. Vaughn hedged when Michael asked for a meeting with Simon, asking instead for the Bible. Vaughn didn&apos;t want to put our biggest enemy (Simon) in the same room with our biggest asset (Michael). Michael told Vaughn that he was asking a favor, and that Vaughn should remember that he&apos;s pretty dangerous, too. Vaughn said no, so Michael kicked him out—back into the hurricane. Vaughn was not happy.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Maddy stayed home through the hurricane, which Michael didn&apos;t like. Michael told Jesse he hadn&apos;t made any progress tracking down Simon. Meanwhile, Lane and Harris, Michael&apos;s FBI friends (they&apos;re not really friends) dropped by Maddy&apos;s place asking for his help with something off the books. They told him about James Bailey, a good guy, who&apos;s wanted dead by some Turks. He took off after a confrontation with the Turks and left one of the feds with a gunshot wound in his arm. Lane and Harris were due back at headquarters and faced suspension if Baileys disappearance became known. Michael agreed to help.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael set out to find a gun dealer who might have sold the Turk&apos;s hitman the special automatic they used in the shootout. Fiona told him about a dealer named Pano. Michael and Sam went to visit him. Pano told them where he dropped the gun for the guy who bought it the previous week. It was an apartment building. Michael broke in and found himself in an awkward situation: Trying to prevent the hitman&apos;s self-made security explosive from going off just as the hitman, Cole, emerged from his bedroom closet. They chatted while Michael tried to stop the bomb from detonating.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Cole assumed Michael was another hitman on the job, so Michael played along and suggested they work together to find Bailey. Cole agreed—sort of. He kept Michael&apos;s gun and they set off to find Bailey together. Vaughn, in the meantime, went to visit Fiona.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Being held hostage, with no way to communicate with Sam, who was waiting outside, Michael tugged on Cole&apos;s car antenna for a second so that Sam knew to stay within radio communication but not come in full-force.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Vaughn asked Fiona for Simon&apos;s Bible, offering Jesse his job back and promising he&apos;d never know who burned him. Fiona said she couldn&apos;t betray Michael. Vaughn told Fiona she couldn&apos;t stop Michael from pursuing the life of danger, even though he knew how it would end. He then handed her some files and told her to let him know when and where she wanted to deliver the Bible. He promised it would stay between them.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael needed a two-way radio device and talked Cole into the idea that they needed an emergency vehicle to get to Miami Beach, because it was an evacuation zone due to the hurricane. They agreed to grab a vehicle at a city lot.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Lane and Harris came to see Sam to find out about Michael. They said they found Bailey&apos;s truck but there was no sign of him. Michael contacted Sam over the radio while pretending he was trying to hot-wire an ambulance. He had Sam get Jesse to go to Bailey&apos;s house and try to find any information on where his girlfriend might live, because that&apos;s where Cole was taking him. At the car yard, Cole did something to knock over an electrical pole and Michael yelled for him to get out of the puddle of water he was standing in. Mike helped Cole out, then punched him in the face. Cole didn&apos;t like that, pulled a gun on Michael and told him he&apos;d get a bullet if he tried something like that again.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Maddy, who came along for the ride, was upset that Jesse didn&apos;t drive faster to Bailey&apos;s place, but they got there and started searching, along with Fiona .</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">While he tried hot-wiring another car, Michael talked to Cole about his life in the Marines (he&apos;d noticed a tattoo on Cole&apos;s arm). Cole got emotional while talking about his dishonorable discharge because his squad mates were shipping drugs back to the States.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael was able to get some information about Bailey&apos;s girlfriend&apos;s house from Jesse and Sam over the radio, while pretending he was asking for a road report over the CB. But Cole was getting inpatient and told Michael to drive to the roof of a parking garage. He gave Mike some binoculars and told him to point out the house. Michael did. That&apos;s when they started getting shot at by the real other hitman, Reese, who was on a higher roof with his team of gunmen. By the time Cole realized Michael wasn&apos;t who he said he was, Michael was off and running out of the garage.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael ran straight to Bailey&apos;s house, ran through the door and rushed Bailey and his girlfriend, Joanne, into the kitchen. Cole came inside and Michael started trying to talk him down. He told Cole he wasn&apos;t a killer. After a couple minutes, with Reese outside waiting to come inside. Michael then stood face to face with Cole and told him he didn&apos;t think he was a killer. They decided to work together to stave off Reese and get Bailey and Joanne out alive.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael rigged an air conditioning unit to become a fireball while Cole baited Reese&apos;s guys into a narrow walkway where the unit was. When they passed, Michael blew up the A/C unit. Then Michael got into a hand-to-hand battle with Reese and was losing until Cole saved him.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Cole then turned his gun on Michael, thanked him and said, &quot;Looks like I&apos;m going to be able to collect a fee on this job after all&quot;. Michael couldn&apos;t believe it, but Cole said he was joking and helped him up. Michael suggested Cole head to Antigua to get to that beach he was looking for.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Michael&apos;s FBI friends came by to thank him and he said he&apos;d never forget it.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">Later, Fiona told Michael that Vaughn had come to see her and made her an offer for the Bible. She told him about the deal for Jesse. She told him she didn&apos;t take him up on the offer, but only because she has faith in Michael. He told her that if he was able to break these people down, it should be enough to get Jesse back in anyway. She handed Michael the Bible, asking him to promise her she wouldn&apos;t regret having given it to the wrong man.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">&apos;You didn&apos;t, Fi&quot;, he told her.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">She said she was supposed to meet Vaughn that afternoon, but Michael should tell him Fi couldn&apos;t make it.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">We next see Lane and Harris meeting Vaughn and telling him he could wind up on the FBI&apos;s most wanted list until he does anything Michael wants. Michael then demanded his meeting with Simon. Vaughn said he&apos;d arrange it, but Michael should know that Vaughn was only trying to help him. He warned Michael that he couldn&apos;t get into Simon&apos;s head without Simon getting into his, and I&apos;m not sure you&apos;re ready for that.</span>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif;line-height:17px;">I guess we&apos;ll find out, Michael said.</span>
</p>
</xml>
