<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><strong>Michael Weston</strong> and <strong>Jesse </strong>labored at the computer trying to crack into the data disk they retrieved from <strong>Kendra </strong>while
 voice-over explained that it was harder for a spy to crack arcane or 
out-of-date software than it was the latest technology and this was the 
former. When <strong>Fiona </strong>helped, she brought her usual 
whining about &quot;14 phone calls, 7 data recovery experts and 3 hours of 
arm twisting -- and it&apos;s still unreadable&quot; which prevented her from even
 noticing the subtle clues of a trap. M noticed that temporary signs 
were routing everyone through a single point which could be observed and
 saw Kendra watching - realizing that they would be here eventually. M 
called <strong>Sam </strong>to help try and entrap her then slowly led 
her to where Sam had left a Taser - no luck, she felt the trap and did a
 cat-burglar exit up a ladder to the roof leaving a cell phone. He 
punched the call button and she coyly bantered with him - answering that
 <em>&quot;Kendra was as good a name as any.&quot;</em> M said they should talk 
because he had something that she wanted and she retorted that she hoped
 he was ready to have some fun. <strong>Jesse </strong>called and tricked M to come over for <strong>Madeline </strong>and used the occasion to belittle Ms plan to grab Kendra, <em>&quot;it&apos;s a wonder you&apos;re still alive.&quot;</em> Madeline had a friend who had trouble with drug dealers. Exasperated, he growled at Jesse &quot;I expect this from her!&quot; <strong>Lauren</strong>, a former &quot;doctor&quot; of Madeline&apos;s, who had moved across town to work with her boyfriend, physician <strong>David </strong>in
 a community clinic, explained that heroin dealers had begun selling 
right outside the clinic. David had called the police, who were 
ineffective, and now the hood had beaten David up and told him to &quot;leave
 or die.&quot; Without even looking at M, Madeline chimed in committing <em>&quot;he&apos;ll see what he can do.&quot;</em>
 David was rude and refused to work outside the police. He said someone 
had to stand up to the thugs and he had dealt with people like this 
before in Brazil and Uganda. Finally Lauren shamed him into listening 
and M said that they would deal with the thugs from the outside so they 
didn&apos;t retaliate against the clinic or him. He resignedly agreed. Both 
Jesse and Fiona wanted to go to battle without even knowing who the 
dealers were so M had to talk reason. Fiona said: &quot;fine, just promise 
there&apos;ll be hitting at some point,&quot; and walked away.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Kendra called and used a flirty, bantering to which M responded in kind 
until Fiona gave him the &quot;witches eye.&quot; He told Kendra to meet him 
tomorrow at 4 with $50,000 for the tape. M went to scout the meeting 
place while the others &quot;climbed the drug chain&quot; using a  RFID tracking 
device on the money Jesse bought some drugs with. They tailed the runner
 to a strip club and Fiona decided to call in a favor with Sugar for 
some inside information on the boss in the sport coat. Sugar recognized,
 and was afraid of, the guy calling him a <em>&quot;psycho who gave drug dealers a bad name.&quot;</em> Vince Cutler, Sugar said, <em>&quot;came down from the Bronx and was spreading through Dade County like the plague.&quot; </em>A
 couple of years before, Cutler had shot Sugar&apos;s friend Carl, and had 
told Sugar that if he ever saw him again he&apos;d kill him, and he saw him; 
so, Sam had to divert Cutler&apos;s attention by picking a fight with the guy
 then beating him down. Sugar said that Cutler had been funded heavy by a
 Mexican cartel and now had to pay them back so was scared. As he was 
having stitches in his head, Sam said &quot;worse surveillance ever!&quot; David 
protested mightily about having them fortify his clinic. They had to 
tell him about Cutler&apos;s cartel problem and that they <em>&quot;just needed to find his supply, take it, and he&apos;ll be running from some very angry Mexican&apos;s.&quot; </em>M
 said they needed to give Cutler something else to hide so they could 
track it back to his stash, and asked for some Fentanyl (a narcotic 
analgesic).
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sugar met them at Carlito&apos;s with expectations of &quot;being on the team.&quot; 
Sugar said he &quot;owed them one… anytime… except this time.&quot; M asked him to
 have his buddies up north &quot;remember working with me&quot; and he reluctantly
 agreed. M pretended to be Kyle Barkley a <em>&quot;supplier of Fentanyl without a demander&quot;</em>
 after his buyer in DC got shot at a dog fight. He left his number and 
expected that Cutler would check him out. Back trying to snatch Kendra, 
Sam posed as a security guard to tase her for shoplifting; but, she just
 called and toyed some more and set her own date, time and place. M had 
to deal with another useless tirade from his mother about how 
incompetent his plans were, even though she was the one who had forced 
him into the mess. Cutler called for a meeting, took Ms drugs but 
resisted the attempts to get him to show his stash house. Jesse followed
 the car with the runner going to the house, but arrogantly blew it and 
barely escaped Cutler&apos;s road trap. Cutler threw a brick through the 
window at the clinic with a note saying: &quot;you&apos;re closed.&quot; David 
belligerently refused any cooperation with M which required M to 
&quot;capture&quot; him, saying &quot;you&apos;ll thank me later.&quot; They utilized a remote 
controlled airplane with a camera to scout the area Jesse was rousted in
 and found a house, with a cluster of guys, which they were sure was the
 stash house. Kendra called with another place to meet and M had to run 
to Madeline&apos;s where David thought he could handle Cutler better than M. 
Cutler had told their neighbors that he was going to hit the clinic to 
&quot;teach them a lesson.&quot; They found Cutler himself ranting and railing 
outside the clinic with no one there. When he picked up a fire bomb 
Fiona shot it and peppered all around them from hiding. David complained
 that M couldn&apos;t protect the clinic, offered no other plan except to 
complain and (surprise, surprise) both Jesse and Fiona wanted to go to 
war with Cutler. M kept saying to keep to the plan and Madeline stuck 
her nose in demanding M go talk to her &quot;right now.&quot; She had no other 
plan to offer except a story about how M had backed down the bully Todd 
for Nate when they were young. After M went to high school Nate was 
&quot;fair game&quot; and they made his life miserable until Nate solved the 
problem with a 2x4. M told her that David wasn&apos;t up against school 
bullies, &quot;these people will kill him&quot; Her only comment was &quot;I don&apos;t 
think you&apos;re going to let that happen.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Madeline was through Fiona arrogantly gave him an ultimatum &quot;either
 your with us or not, we are going to hit Cutler.&quot; M directed clearly <em>&quot;No, WE are not. David will be the one who stands up to cutler.&quot;</em>
 However, M had to do a phenomenal amount of set up to make it look like
 David was the hero. M went to Cutler, beat up and saying that David had
 beaten him up. He told Cutler that David ran with some <em>&quot;merc&apos;s or 
something. He is ex-delta force and used to run black ops with them all 
around the globe. Now he&apos;s coming after your stash.&quot;</em> M showed him a
 whole folder of newspaper clippings about David. Cutler checked with 
his &quot;corner boys&quot; and found that they had been hit. Incensed, he ran to 
his stash house to fight against David. With Fiona, Jesse, Sam and M 
already prepared around the house, David crashed the clinic&apos;s van 
through Cutlers road trap and confronted Cutler on the street. He said 
Cutler had forced his hand even though all he wanted was to live in 
peace for once. Jesse fired tear gas into the house pulling out all 
Cutlers men. Then, Fiona blew up Cutler&apos;s car. Cutler attacked David who
 acted like some kind of Gandhi saying <em>&quot;either leave town or face the consequences.&quot;</em>
 When Cutler drew his gun, Fiona shot it out of his hand. David said 
he&apos;d count to three. Cutler still did nothing, so on three Fiona blew up
 the whole house. David said his people were everywhere and they 
wouldn&apos;t kill him if he left. All the men started running and Fiona&apos;s 
gang peppered the ground behind them with bullets. As David acted the 
hero, Jesse said <em>&quot;that&apos;s how we do it people.&quot;</em> In recap the next day, the clinic was open and David said thanks. On their way out, Madeline nagged M that <em>&quot;sometimes people need to fight their own battles.&quot;</em> Annoyed, M told her <em>&quot;I got it the first time.&quot; </em> She said, <em>&quot;better to have Michael Westen than a 2 x 4.&quot; </em>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At a vulnerable boat yard, M expected Sam to cover him from an 
untenable position. He said that he was going in to get her and he had 
reinforced a briefcase with metal siding. Actually, he needed it because
 she drew him out of Sam&apos;s line of sight, then pulled a Japanese Tanto 
knife on him when he was diverted from the back-pack of payment she 
tossed at his eyes. When her knife went clear through the briefcase and 
was stuck, he hit her with it and knocked her out. As Sam helped put her
 in the trunk, he said &quot;this isn&apos;t going to be easy. She&apos;s going to make
 our life hard.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
</xml>
