<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">So, where’d we leave off? After a nice
bikini shot to open the show, Michael
sat on a park bench examining the classified document that the Pakistani spy,
Waseem, had given him last week. Most
of it had been redacted, but, as Michael
explained, it was like watching a movie
on an airplane: ”all the juicy parts are missing, but you still get the basic idea.”
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael discovered that Carla – his new handler – used ”irrigation consultant” as her cover in
Kurdistan. He thought she might be using the same cover now. Michael thought he was being
tailed by a black Lincoln Town Car, but it turned out to be his brother, Nate, whose presence
was going to be a problem.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Nate wanted Michael to help a lady friend of his who was having trouble with some Russian
mafia guys. Michael wondered what Nate’s ”angle” was, whether he wanted money from the girl
or wanted to sleep with her, but Nate said he was just trying to change his life around. The
woman, Katya, explained that her sister was being smuggled into the country, but the mob boss,
Ivan, demanded more money before giving up the girl and threatened to kill her if Katya went to the cops.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam got together with Harvey Gunderson, a bigwig in the local agriculture game, to find out
if Carla is working as an irrigation consultant in the area.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Later, Michael suggested to Sam that they interrogate Ivan and they sent Fiona out to ”bag
him.” She lured Ivan to her car in a parking lot, while Sam watched, but a scuffle ensued when
Fi pulled a Taser on Ivan. He was holding onto Fi’s leg when she got a clear chance to zap him,
and she did it, knowing full well that she’s take the shock. She did, and they both collapsed as Sam ran over.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Sam set up an elaborate interrogation area and Sam proceeded to squeeze him
for information. In order to convince Ivan that his ”cell” was real, Sam asked Michael to move in
with Ivan. That required Michael getting beaten a bit to make it look real, and Fi was happy to
oblige. Nate even got a punch in. Michael moved into the cel with Ivan and convinced him he was
Russian and got Ivan to talk about his human trafficking organization.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Ivan wasn’t budging after even more interrogation from Sam and Michael later got Ivan to tell
him that he’s the only person who knows where the safe house containing the smuggled girls is, and that his men know to kill anyone but him who goes there. They also are instructed to kill
the girls in the safe house if they haven’t heard from him by Friday. Michael hatched a plan to
help Ivan escape from the cell, hoping he’d get back to the safe house.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael’s mom pleaded with him to be kinder to Nate. She said Nate’s troubles first started
when Michael left for the spy game. Back in the cell, Michael staged an elaborate fight with Nate,
who posed as their captor. After breaking free and pretending to shoot Nate, Michael and Ivan
headed to the safe house, where a dozen, or so, girls were waiting. After convincing Ivan to trust
him to move the girls to another safe house, Michael got Ivan to run to the bosses, who weren’t
pleased to hear that Ivan had talked to the CIA. His day wasn’t going to end well. Meanwhile,
Michael, Fi and Sam took care of Ivan’s thugs and freed the captured girls.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">It turned out Carla’s cover in Miami was that she was irrigation specialist. Imagine that! All
they had was a business card that included a P.O. Box, so Michael and Fi sat and waited to see
who’d come to pick up the mail. And they waited. And they waited...
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
</xml>
