<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael is following Max&apos;s killer&apos;s money trail and he, Jesse and Sam have found a guy who&apos;s been bankrolling the effort: It&apos;s a man named Stigler, ID&apos;d as &quot;ATM to the Eastern bloc.&quot; He loaned money to a guy named Tavian, who used it to kill Max. He also ended up killing Lucien. This gets Stigler&apos;s attention. He says he&apos;ll ask around and that Sam and Jesse&apos;s lives depend on them telling the truth.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Pearce is going over the notes on Max&apos;s killing, but tells Michael she&apos;s got nothing, so far. She sends Michael to a beach town in Venezuela to extract a guy named Cheshire, who creates &quot;nasty bugs used in germ warfare for the Eastern bloc,&quot; and his wife. The CIA is sending Michael and Fi, making it easier for them to disavow any involvement if it goes bad for Michael and Fi. This isn&apos;t the kind of quality time Fi was hoping for, but it&apos;ll have to do.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Stigler meets Sam and Jesse at a restaurant and says their story about Tavian is true. He tells them when Tavian comes to pick up money. He&apos;s inside Stigler&apos;s place for about a minute and that will be the extent of their opportunity to get him. Stigler tells them if they fail, it will be bad.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Fi arrive in Venezuela and Michael works some hacking magic at the resort to find four couples have the same check-in date that Cheshire did. They head to a formal ball where all of the couples are in attendance and they work some crafty ballroom magic to do surveillance. Michael thinks he&apos;s got the couple figured out and they head to the couple&apos;s room to plant a bug. Then they have to destroy Fi&apos;s new dress to rappel down from the room&apos;s balcony in order to avoid getting caught.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">&quot;Cheshire,&quot; whose real name is Kevin Skylar, and his wife Nikki are spending most of the night arguing about how she wants a real life and doesn&apos;t want Russian bodyguards telling here where she can and can&apos;t go. Michael suggests Fi offer Nikki a bit of a break from all the structure and give her a taste of &quot;the good life.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The next day, Fi and Nikki bond over their disconnected husbands, and Fi mentions a helicopter ride over the rainforest. Later, Michael and Fi jointly try to talk Kevin and Nikki into joining. It seems unlikely at first, but Nikki talks Kevin into agreeing to go.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam and Jesse devise an explosive and plant it into a grate in preparation for disabling Tavian&apos;s car. They set it up and head off for lunch.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At dinner in Venezuela, Nikki and Kevin now say they can&apos;t go on the helicopter ride and Michael decides to lay all the cards on the table. With the couple&apos;s bodyguards sitting just a few tables away, Michael tells Kevin he knows who he isn&apos;t claiming to be, and lays out the whole process of how Kevin ended up working for the Russians, and the promise of a new life didn&apos;t pan out. Nikki exclaims, &quot;How did you know that?&quot; Michael proceeds to tell Kevin he can get him a job making twice as much as what the Russians pay and that he won&apos;t &quot;insult&quot; him by making him run around with babysitters all the time. Nikki tells Kevin to accept. With the bodyguards getting suspicious and approaching the table, Kevin says yes and Fi tells everyone to laugh loudly to throw the guards off. They do, and they toast to their new friendship.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The next day, Michael lays out the plan to escape the bodyguards and get to the helicopter.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back in Miami, Sam and Jesse are waiting for Tavian to arrive at Stigler&apos;s place, and he&apos;s 30 minutes late. Jesse goes in to see what&apos;s going on and finds Stigler dead. Outside, Tavian has a gun to Sam&apos;s neck before he can make a move. When Jesse gets no response from Sam, he runs out.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Tavian takes Sam to an isolated place and says he wants a meeting with Michael. He wants a truce and claims he has answers to &quot;the questions he doesn&apos;t even know to ask.&quot; He gives Sam a meeting place and time and says he won&apos;t wait. He drives away.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Kevin sit in a steam room waiting for Serge, Kevin&apos;s bodyguard, to show up. Michael&apos;s ready with a towel full of spa rocks and another towel twisted up. When Serge comes in, Michael hits him with the rocks, giving Kevin time to escape, then, after some hand-to-hand fighting, Michael puts a chokehold on Serge that knocks him out. Fi&apos;s exit with Nikki doesn&apos;t go as smoothly when Nikki panics and freezes just as they&apos;re about to run for it. Karina, the female guard, notices and chases while shooting at them. Fi and Nikki are forced to jump into the water rather than head for their car.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Karina is still shooting when Serge picks her up in an SUV. Fi hot wires a motorcycle and they head out. There are roadblocks in place so Fi pulls off into a warehouse-type place. She says they aren&apos;t going to go quietly.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Michael realizes something&apos;s gone wrong with Fi, he goes back and arrives just in time to knock Karina out when Fi was out of bullets. They work quite closely together, using each other&apos;s guns and ammo while shooting back to back to take out more of the Russians&apos; backups. When the shootout is over, Michael and Fi take Kevin and Nikki to a chopper, but it isn&apos;t for a sightseeing tour. The destination is CIA headquarters. Kevin resists at first, but Michael and Fi remind him the Russians aren&apos;t going to give him much of a warm reception if he tries going back to them. He gives in and gets on board, saying they won&apos;t get &quot;a word&quot; out of him. But Nikki tells him they&apos;ll get plenty out of her.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Tavian is waiting for Michael at the park he&apos;d set up as the meeting place, and Jesse has pulled out all his connections to secure the water, roads and airspace. An angry Tavian calls Sam and says he&apos;s not going to wait for Michael any longer, but Sam tells him about all the paths being blocked off, which should buy them a few hours.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Fi have a playful exchange about how they posed as being married and she tells him that next time she&apos;s his wife she wants an Asscher cut diamond.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael goes inside to drop off his bags, and Pearce. having broken in, is waiting. She&apos;s excited to tell him about a break she&apos;s made in Max&apos;s case. She says she&apos;s got security camera footage that shows some cars passing by from a nearby all-glass building&apos;s reflection. She asks him to take a look. He checks out the footage and sees his Charger. Stunned, he turns around to explain, but Pearce already has her gun pointed at him. Michael tries to explain that Sam and Jesse are following Tavian and if she just lets him make one phone call he could clear everything up. She tells him he shouldn&apos;t dare, and tosses him plastic handcuffs for him to put on himself.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">He does.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Summary from tv.com.
</p>
</xml>
