<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Michael and Fiona come home to his apartment, an attractive woman who was sent by Strickler to give Michael rejuvenating body lotion awaits them. Though the woman offers to apply it, Michael sends her away.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The next day, Michael visits Strickler to give the lotion back and to tell him that he is not interested in being Strickler&apos;s mercenary. However, Strickler offers to help Michael with his burn notice.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Soon later, Michael pays his &quot;favorite point of contact&quot; Diego a visit. He wants to know if Tom Strickler is indeed able to help him with his burn notice and asks Diego to check him out.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Fiona and Michael are on their way to Fiona&apos;s apartment, arguing about Strickler&apos;s offer because Fiona doesn&apos;t want Michael to trust Strickler. When they arrive, Michael discovers that someone broke into Fiona&apos;s apartment. They corner the housebreaker into a choke point and have to realize that a teenage boy who tried to steal one of Fiona&apos;s pistol is the culprit.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The boy tries to run away, but Michael catches up with him. The boy reveals that he needed the gun to kill his stepfather.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back in Fiona&apos;s apartment, Fiona and Michael try to talk to the boy. He reveals that his stepfather wants to take him and his brother away from their mother and Michael promises to help his family.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam is surprised that Michael is on a case of domestic disputes, but understands that Michael can relate to the boy because of his own father. Sam and Michael joins Fiona and their new client April Luna, the boy&apos;s mother. April does not believe that they can help to keep her two sons. Her abusive husband Erik is connected and his brother Quinn is a gangster.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">At Erik&apos;s golf club, Michael and Sam check the Luna brothers out. Sam found out that Quinn needs Erik&apos;s pretty face and clean record to keep the empire he built and therefor Quinn is a little protective.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In the meantime, April and her sons move in with Michael&apos;s mother Madeline. Fiona asks April about any issues between the Luna brothers that could drive them apart. April reveals that Erik has a side business his brother doesn&apos;t know about.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In Madeline&apos;s garage, Michael is building a listening device while Sam tells him about Erik&apos;s scam. Erik takes stuff that gets seized at the docks, sells it and pockets the profits. When Joey appears, Michael asks him to give him a hand and assures Joey that he can make his stepfather run.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael walks into Erik Luna&apos;s office and pretends to be an unsatisfied, angry costumer of Erik&apos;s side business. Michael claims that he bought a Lotus that was stolen back by the original owner who is now trying to kill him.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">To sell his anger - which is very real, given Erik&apos;s treatment of his stepsons - Michael throws Erik to the ground and starts kicking him around. He demands his money back, and warns Erik that the death squad will be after him, too.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><br/>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">For the next step of their plan to make Erik believe that there is a killer after him, Michael, Fiona and Sam prepare the streetlight and Erik&apos;s car. When Erik leaves his office that night, suddenly the streetlight dies, his car won&apos;t start and his phone has no reception. While he still wonders what&apos;s happening, they chase him with a car and Fiona shoots at Erik. Soon later, Michael receives a phone call from Erik who tells him they need to meet.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The next day, Michael meets with Erik. He tries to convince him that they have to run because of the psychopath who is trying to kill them, but Erik tells Michael that he can&apos;t run. He wants to team up with Michael to find out who is after them.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">After the meeting, Michael calls Sam to tell him about it and Sam suggests that they have to make Erik regret his decision to see who is after him. But first, Michael wants to find out what Diego is doing with the name Tom Strickler. He connects a network analyzer to Diego&apos;s data stream to see if he is changing his security protocol.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When he has finished his work, Erik calls. He saw the same car driving by his office several times. Michael recognizes the car and has an idea about the driver. He calls his mother and gets to know that Joey took Madeline&apos;s car.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael drives to Erik&apos;s golf club and discovers his mother&apos;s car. Between trees, he finds Joey who is armed with a shotgun, ready to shoot his stepfather. He accuses Michael of making their situation worse rather than helping his family, but Michael can take away the shotgun from him and assures Joey that his plan is working and asks for his help to scare Erik who is armed with a gun nervously pacing up and down the parking lot.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Joey speeds away in Madeline&apos;s car, Michael approaches Erik and accuses him of passing up the chance to meet their pursuer by scaring him away. Once again, Michael suggests to leave the city, but Erik replies that going away is not an option. He wants to hire someone to deal with their problem, and Michael tells him that he knows some people for that job.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael meets with Joey who apologizes for his behavior. With the help of the listening device they built earlier and which Michael hid in Erik&apos;s office, they listen to a conversation between the Luna brothers. Quinn is very angry because Erik was seen running through the parking lot with a gun. Joey is delighted to get to know that Erik is on the edge and promises Michael to stay with his mother until Michael and his team are done.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Erik meets Michael&apos;s &quot;people&quot; Sam and Fiona. They assure Erik they can find the one who&apos;s after them. Soon later, Michael meets Fiona and Sam in his apartment to prepare their last step of their plan which involves pretended gunshot wounds. When they are ready, Sam calls Erik to tell him they found the guy he was looking for.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">They take Erik to an alley where they use their bottle caps that they packed with a bit of plastic explosive to pretend Fiona, Sam and Michael are shot to death while Erik can escape. When the three get up, they are sure Erik is going to miss the custody hearing.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Nevertheless, Sam uses the listening device to monitor Erik&apos;s leaving. Unfortunately, his brother Quinn arrives while Erik is packing and prevents Erik from leaving the town. He thinks Erik acts like a lunatic and tells him that they will take his guys to find out what Erik is talking about. Sam calls Michael to tell him that Erik and Quinn are heading back to Hallendale where Erik saw them get shot. Michael reminds Sam of an operation in Moscow that could rescue their operation.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">When Erik, Quinn and Quinn&apos;s men arrive, all signs of the shooting are gone. When they enter the building where Erik believes the killer came from, they meet Michael dressed as a priest. Michael tells Quinn that he does outreach for the homeless and met Erik one day on the street. Sympathetically, he asks whether Erik is still telling the same wild story about people trying to kill him. Erik loses his temper and lunges at Michael, and Quinn and his men pull him away, fearful of attracting attention. Just then, Erik catches sight of Fiona walking casually down the street, and Sam buying fruit at a stand, and excitedly points them out as Michael&apos;s accomplices.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Quinn, seeing his brother shouting abuse at seemingly random passers-by, is now convinced his brother has gone insane and is a liability to his business, and orders his men to hustle Quinn into the car, out of sight. Michael solemnly wishes Erik the best, assuring him that he has a loving brother and will get the best care that money can buy. As a goodbye, he makes the sign of the cross.. and winks at Erik. Seeing the wink, Erik begins yelling desperately for his brother to listen to him, as he is dragged away in the car.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">After the custody hearing, April tells Fiona that she was given full custody with Erik being in a mental facility and Fiona hands her the money Erik gave them when he hired them. Michael asks Joey if he will be alright. Joey is not sure and reveals that his mother believes he is some kind of delinquent, but Michael tells him that he knows a kid like him who turned out all right. Joey knows that Michael is referring to himself.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael, Sam and Fiona meet in a restaurant and Sam tells them that with Erik gone the police is looking into Quinn&apos;s business. Michael leaves to follow up on that Strickler business. When Michael tries to remove the network analyzer, Diego threatens him with a gun. He is angry because he had to spend the last four days dealing with reporting procedures because Michael dropped the name of Strickler. Though Diego refuses to tell Michael anything about Strickler, Michael has found out what he was looking for. Knowing that Strickler is as connected as he said he is, he hands Diego the network analyzer and leaves.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael visits Strickler who knows that Michael checked his references. He offers once again to help Michael to become a respectable citizen again. In return, he asks Michael to do a job for him. Strickler doesn&apos;t give away any details about the job, but asks Michael to choose right away.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael agrees.
</p>
</xml>
