<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Previously on &apos;Burn Notice&apos;: <a href="/wiki/Michael" class="mw-redirect" title="Michael">Michael</a> made a deal to work with the CIA and take down a terrorist leader in the Dominican Republic. A man named <a href="/wiki/Dexter_Gamble" title="Dexter Gamble">Dexter Gamble</a> was trying to gather information on Michael in Miami and he took <a href="/wiki/Fiona_Glenanne" title="Fiona Glenanne">Fi</a> hostage. Michael heroically planned Fi&apos;s escape, only to have her run into <a href="/wiki/Carlos" title="Carlos">Carlos</a>&apos; arms and give Michael a farewell kiss on the cheek.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Down Range: Michael is back in the D.R. and all by himself. Left alone with just his thoughts, he digs up a picture of himself with Fi and burns it. The TV news reports a manhunt for someone who looks like Michael. He quickly shaves. He then meets up with <a href="/wiki/Randall_Burke" title="Randall Burke">Randall Burke</a> to find out about his next job. Michael is being asked to steal a truck, and he&apos;s at a bar to meet with a guy Burke wants him to work with. Michael wants to call in <a href="/wiki/Sam" class="mw-redirect" title="Sam">Sam</a> and <a href="/wiki/Jesse" class="mw-redirect" title="Jesse">Jesse</a> but Burke wants Michael to work with his guy. The guy in the bar says his price went up because the truck Burke wants him to steal belongs to a company whose building was just blown up. The guy ups his price from $5,000 to $12.5 million. He&apos;s connected the dots from the building Burke had blown up to the truck and realizes there&apos;s some serious stuff going down. The guy threatens to talk about what he knows if Burke doesn&apos;t pay him more, but Burke isn&apos;t having it. Michael quickly gets the man&apos;s knife out of his hands and Burke winds up using the knife to kill the guy in the middle of the bar. Burke then asks Michael about his guys.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael meets up with <a href="/wiki/Andrew_Strong" title="Andrew Strong">Agent Strong</a> to ask about Sam and Jesse coming in. Michael convinces Strong to let Sam and Jesse join, despite wanting to use his own CIA operatives. He tells Michael that Burke is selling the satellite equipment he&apos;s stealing to <span class="new" title="Rafael Serrano (page does not exist)" data-uncrawlable-url="L3dpa2kvUmFmYWVsX1NlcnJhbm8/YWN0aW9uPWVkaXQmcmVkbGluaz0x">Rafael Serrano</span>, a terrorist behind several big city bombings. Strong says he can&apos;t afford any mistakes. Michael assures him it&apos;ll be fine.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Meanwhile back in Miami, Sam chats up Jesse over some basketball. Jesse is actually staking out a drug dealer. Sam tells Jesse that Michael needs backup but has few details. Jesse isn&apos;t wild about jumping on a moment&apos;s notice but agrees to go with Sam.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><a href="/wiki/Madeline_Westen" title="Madeline Westen">Maddy</a> is out watching <a href="/wiki/Charlie" title="Charlie">Charlie</a> when a guy named <span class="new" title="Leo (page does not exist)" data-uncrawlable-url="L3dpa2kvTGVvP2FjdGlvbj1lZGl0JnJlZGxpbms9MQ==">Leo</span> comes up and says he knew <a href="/wiki/Nate" class="mw-redirect" title="Nate">Nate</a> ,who was a client. Leo says Nate lost &quot;a lot of money that he couldn&apos;t pay back.&quot; Leo says Maddy needs to pay him $80,000 while Leo threatens Charlie. Leo warns Maddy that if she tries to run, he&apos;ll find her. He puts a bullet in Charlie&apos;s hand as he walks away. Fi comes to see Maddy, who says she needs Fi to watch Charlie for a few days. Fi tells Maddy she can&apos;t pay this guy the money, but Maddy doesn&apos;t know what to do. She says she wishes Michael was there, but Fi says he isn&apos;t so they&apos;ll have to handle this alone. 
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Burke prepare for the arrival of Sam and Jesse, but their plans are interrupted when they hear radio traffic reporting a suspected drug plane (Sam and Jesse&apos;s plane, which is coming into the country undercover). Sam and Jesse get off the plane and have to scramble quickly to use the plane to block the road. They blow the plane up and it stops the cops from giving chase.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Jesse tells Burke they can get the truck he wants and make a smaller mess than the hack Burke was going to use. Burke says that if anything goes wrong, he wants Sam to use his sniper rifle to take out the guards. Later, Jesse and Sam tell Michael they don&apos;t want to kill any random guard, but Michael explains the stakes. He tells them that the deal he made with the CIA was to bring Burke down and if he doesn&apos;t do it, they&apos;ll all go back to those CIA holding cells they were in for good.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back in Miami, Fi comes over and asks Maddy to gather up some valuables. They&apos;re going to give Leo some things to squirrel away, but one of those items will include a GPS tracker that Fi will use to find Leo&apos;s stash. Leo comes over and is upset that Maddy only has $24,000 and maybe $8,000 worth of jewelry. When Maddy says she needs a few days, Leo mocks her and says that her &quot;loser son&quot; always needed a few days, too, and never paid up. Maddy agrees that Nate was a loser and a drunk and assures Leo she&apos;ll pay. He takes the jewelry as collateral and leaves. Fi heard this whole exchange.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and the crew make their run for the truck. They cut through an electrical fence to give Michael space to get into the yard where the truck is stored. A guard steps outside for a cigarette and follows the sound of Michael prying open the truck door. Sam reluctantly shoots the guy in the back. Michael takes the truck and breaks out of the yard with cars chasing him. Burke throws a spike strip out to knock the chasers off course and the crew rides home free.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Strong briefs some guys on the mission to take down Burke&apos;s sale of equipment to Serrano. He tells Sam and Jesse it&apos;s time for them to go home, but the pair refuse to leave. Strong agrees to let them stay to watch  emphasizing &quot;watch.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back in Miami, Fi and Maddy are staking out Leo. Maddy is feeling bad about what she said about Nate to Leo. She wonders if she could have done something different for him when he was little and she wonders whether she can do something better for Charlie. Leo leaves and isn&apos;t carrying Maddy&apos;s jewelry box, which means he stashed it. Maddy helps Fi set up the explosive that will blow out the wall where Leo&apos;s stash is hidden. Fi even lets Maddy detonate it.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In the D.R., the deal between Burke and Serrano is about to go down and the CIA has people all over it. Jesse and Sam are concerned that some exit routes have been overlooked, but Strong doesn&apos;t want to hear it. Serrano shows up and has a nice intro with Burke, chatting him up about how awesome this satellite equipment is going to be for him. He asks Burke how he wants to do the deal, but we see that Burke has grabbed a gun. Burke tells Serrano, &quot;I don&apos;t want your money.&quot; He shoots Serrano&apos;s two guards, then adds, &quot;I just want you.&quot; Michael looks stunned.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Serrano tells Burke he &quot;just made a very serious mistake.&quot; Michael cuffs Serrano while Burke tells Serrano that he has information that is valuable to the people he works for. The CIA is surprised because they thought Burke ran his own organization. Suddenly, a helicopter comes flying over and spots the snipers. The pilot reports the snipers to Burke, who punches Serrano in the face after asking how many snipers there are and not getting an answer. Serrano says he doesn&apos;t know what he&apos;s talking about. Serrano says he didn&apos;t come with snipers because Burke only gave him the location 40 minutes earlier. Burke tells Michael that Serrano has a point, then asks Michael how he missed a sniper team if he was sweeping the location. Burke makes Michael drop his gun while Michael claims that Serrano is lying. Michael moves over toward a window and talks loudly about how the snipers aren&apos;t his. Sam gets what MIchael is doing and tells a sniper to shoot at Michael. When the sniper doesn&apos;t budge, Sam takes the gun and shoots at Michael himself  obviously not hitting him, but proving enough to Burke to &quot;show&quot; that the snipers don&apos;t work for Michael. Michael then forces Serrano to call off the snipers. Serrano goes to the window and shouts for the snipers to fall back. Strong gives the order to the snipers to put their guns down. The helicopter pilot reports to Burke that the sniper teams are moving out and Burke tells the pilot to land. Michael and Burke run to the chopper and toss Serrano in the back. Sam is shaken from what he calls a &quot;long day&quot; that he was hoping would be over. Jesse says he think it&apos;s a long way from over.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">In Miami, Leo is looking stressed as he sits outside a coffee shop. Fi is about to go talk to him, but Maddy wants to do it herself. She walks over to Leo and lets him know she&apos;s the one who took his safe. She tells him he can have his client list back  she made a few extra copies for her and her important friends  but the money she took will be Charlie&apos;s college fund and Leo is to never again come near her or Charlie. He agrees to this and Maddy, turning Leo&apos;s own words around on him, squeezes Leo&apos;s cheeks and says, &quot;I own you.&quot;
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back in the D.R., Burke apologizes to Michael about having suspected him. Michael says sorry doesn&apos;t cut it. He wants to know what organization it is that Burke is working for, and whether or not he (Michael) is part of it. Burke says all will be revealed in time.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">	 Jack Coleman	 ...	
Andrew Strong
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">	 Paul Hipp	 ...	
Al Sapienza
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">	 Ricardo Chavira	 ...	
Rafael Serano
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">	 Adrian Pasdar	 ...	
Burke
</p>
</xml>
