<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"><strong>Michael Westen</strong> and <strong>Jesse </strong>asked <strong>Madeline </strong>to
 help them case the Miami Trust bank and use what she did best – 
smoking. Jesse delivered sandwiches to the security room while Madeline 
lit up down in the vault to see what the reaction would be. Jesse’s plan
 nearly got her “burned” – except the security guard felt sorry for her 
having to put her dead husband’s photo’s in the box. <em>“First thing Frank’s been good for in 30 years,”</em> she told them. Ms plans were to get into the legal office above the vault somehow and then blast their way through the floor – <em>“they’re lawyers, they have it coming!”</em> <strong>Sam </strong>and <strong>Fiona </strong>got all dressed up in formal-wear to pretend to be <strong><em>Charles </em></strong>and <strong><em>Charlotte </em></strong>who
 were going to guard a rich man’s party and prevent anyone from stealing
 a new battery. Before Fiona left the loft her passive-aggressiveness 
was blatant enough to have everyone asking M: <em>“what did you do to her?”</em> <strong>Christian Aikins&apos;</strong>
 house had &quot;more security than the bat cave”; but, the masked guys with 
machine guns weren’t there for the battery, rather for Aikins&apos; wife, <strong>Sarah</strong>. They shot up the place and Fiona had no option except to go with Sarah pretending that her husband was just as rich.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">The kidnappers disappeared like ghosts and turned out to be Mexican brothers, <strong>Jacob </strong>and <strong>Eddy</strong>,
 who were expanding their business northward. They called Aikins on his 
web cam and M began acting as hostage-negotiator. They saw Fiona blink 
“no” in Morse code, meaning they had seen the kidnapper’s faces so would
 be killed. Aikins acted like a complete buffoon the whole episode and 
disobeyed Ms instructions at every turn putting Fiona&apos;s life at 
jeopardy. Fiona even had to argue with little Princess Sarah the whole 
time she was making a bomb and stealing a phone to call M. While Fiona 
was on the phone she overheard them taking Sarah out of the building 
because her husband was the only one who paid! Their 20 hours of lead 
time had now turned into only one. Jesse had been told to watch Aikins 
but hadn’t. M told Jesse &quot;You can beat youself up about it later, and 
I&apos;ll help you.&quot;  Sam saw Fiona’s smoke signal and said <em>“where’s there’s smoke, there’s Fi.”</em>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Fiona wiled a bottle of Vodka out of Jacob and broke free from the chair she was tied to. She rigged a light bulb full of alcohol to blow 
up and called M to say that he needed to go find Sarah. Sam waited 
outside the house.  Jesse finally forced Aikins to tell where the payoff would be: his CFO 
was going to the Lighthouse at Cape Florida. Fiona stalled Jacob with 
“last requests” until the light bulb blew up and she could take down 
Jacob.  Sam came in and took out his buddy saying: <em>&quot;Honey I&apos;m home.&quot;</em>
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">M appeared at the drop and showed Eddy a photo of Jacob duct taped to a chair with Fiona’s fire-extinguisher bomb between his legs and a watch 
taped to the top. Eddy gave Sarah to M who then took their guns and shot
 their tires. M then convinced Eddy that the only way he could save his 
brother on the other side of town before the bomb went off was to call 
the police on himself in order to get them to reach Jacob in time. The 
police snapped up Jacob and grabbed Eddy at the airport after his 911 
call. Back at the loft Fiona said <em>“you should see the other guy”</em> and seemed to have forgiven M, while Jesse acted uncomfortable and left.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Madeline had washed the masks that Fiona took from the kidnappers and told Jesse that <em>&quot;maybe you and M can use them in your  bank heist.&quot;</em> She also observed to Jesse that <em>“M and Fiona love each other, and hate each other, but it’s always each other.”</em> When he said that he knew that, she told him <em>&quot;And I believe you, but you might want to work on your poker face.&quot;</em>
 Mike and Jesse were through the ceiling, into the vault and back out in
 under a minute - and found an old Bible in box 64. It was a book code 
and belonged to <strong>Simon Escher</strong> – who M told Jesse that he didn’t know.
</p>
</xml>
