<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Michael and Fiona sit on the beach watching the sunrise. Fi claims that she never thought she&apos;d see another sunrise, and she thanks Mike for not giving up on her. Mike tries to convince her to sit this case out, since he doesn&apos;t want to lose her again, but she refuses, saying that she&apos;s not leaving his side.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back at the loft, Sam breaks the bad news that his buddies at the FBI haven&apos;t found anything and are &quot;turning Atlantic City upside down.&quot; Michael and Fiona convince Sam to call Rebecca, while Michael tries to reach Maddie. Maddie doesn&apos;t answer and Michael leaves her a message. Rebecca doesn&apos;t answer the phone Sam gave her and the tracker Sam planted on her says that she&apos;s still at his girlfriend&apos;s high-rise, but it&apos;s not moving. Michael deduces that whoever killed Anson and Nate also killed her.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">They go to the hotel and find the door chained from the inside. They break in and see that Rebecca played them. She found Sam&apos;s tracker and put it on a counter with a note saying &quot;Nice try, Sam.&quot; She hacked hotel security and spliced phone lines, as well as sneaked out the back window to avoid cameras. Mike asks Sam to get the phone records from the floor they were on from his girlfriend.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam goes to meet his girlfriend, <a href="/wiki/Elsa" title="Elsa">Elsa</a>, who is angrily talking on the phone with someone. Elsa gives him the records and he asks her what&apos;s wrong. She explains that her son, Evan, whom she had cut off, called her earlier in the week begging for money, but she refused. Her housekeeper called her earlier and told her that he came to the house acting crazy and stole her $10k diamond tennis bracelet and ran off. Sam, albeit reluctantly because of the situation with Michael and Rebecca, agrees to go talk to him.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Sam and Jesse go to Evan&apos;s house. Upon arriving they see that Evan is getting ready to skip town, and Evan tells them that he stole the bracelet because he&apos;s in deep with a loan shark named Morris. He still has the bracelet and gives it back. He hears Morris and his crew pull up and tells Jesse and Sam to hide in a den. Morris comes in and is about to kill Evan for failing to get a team together for a heist. Evan exclaims that he has a team together in the den, meaning Sam and Jesse.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Back at the hotel, Fi comes in with weapons and Michael discovers that someone from their floor called a print shop at 2:30 in the morning, most likely for fake IDs. They gear up with numerous guns and lightweight Kevlar vests. Fi is about to load beanbag rounds, but Mike tells her not to, saying that &quot;When [they] shoot, [they] shoot to kill,&quot; much to her delight.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Meanwhile, Sam, Jesse, and Evan are shown a nightclub with a big rig next to it filled with $200k worth of champagne that Morris sold to the owners. He wants the truck back since the owners didn&apos;t pay him for it, and wanted them to do it because they have a few dirty cops in their pocket.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">While they are trying to find a plan to steal the truck, Sam asks Evan why Morris hired him in the first place, saying it doesn&apos;t make sense to &quot;trust a numskull to steal 200 grand worth of merchandise.&quot; Evan told them that since he couldn&apos;t afford his car anymore, he learned how to hot-wire other cars and got so good that he was known for it around South Beach. Sam starts to argue with him, but Jesse breaks it up.
</p>
<p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">Meanwhile, Mike and Fi arrive at the print shop and argue about how to get in. They convince the owner to open the door, by convincing him that they were a desperately sick couple, and tie him up to look around his stuff. They find a set of cards for Rebecca. They tell the owner to cancel all his other appointments for the day and tell her he finished early. The owner first disagrees as his clients are dangerous people with guns, but Fiona shows him that they also have guns, by taking out her handgun, and they are a lot more dangerous than his clients, by pointing her gun at his crotch. The owner calls her &quot;one sick lady,&quot; and agrees.
</p>
</xml>
