<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
<h4>Dealing with Adversarial Player Strategies in the Neural Network Game iNNk through Ensemble Learning</h4><p>Mathias Löwe, Jennifer Villareale, Evan Freed, Aleksanteri Sladek, Jichen Zhu and Sebastian Risi</p>
<h4>Leveraging Reinforcement Learning and WaveFunctionCollapse for Improved Procedural Level Generation</h4><p>Mathias Babin and Michael Katchabaw</p>
<h4>Fine-tuning GPT-2 on annotated RPG quests for NPC dialogue generation</h4><p>Judith van Stegeren and Jakub Myśliwiec</p>
<h4>A Grounded Theory of Accessible Game Development</h4><p>Jozef Kulik, Jen Beeston and Paul Cairns</p>
<h4>“Slow down and look”: Desirable aspects of failure in video games, from the perspective of players</h4><p>Charline Foch and Ben Kirman</p>
<h4>The Struggle is Spiel: On Failure and Success in Games</h4><p>Julian Frommel, Madison Klarkowski and Regan Mandryk</p>
<h4>Correlating Facial Expressions and Subjective Player Experiences in Competitive Hearthstone</h4><p>Paris Mavromoustakos-Blom, Mehmet Kosa, Sander Bakkes and Pieter Spronck</p>
<h4>Antagonistic Procedural content generation of sparse reward game</h4><p>Shaoyou Xie, Wei Zhou and Honglei Han</p>
<h4>Neurosymbolic Map Generation with VQ-VAE and WFC</h4><p>Isaac Karth, Batu Aytemiz, Ross Mawhorter and Adam M. Smith</p>
<h4>Let it Bee: A Case Study of Applying Triadic Game Design for Designing Virtual Reality Training Games for Beekeepers</h4><p>Ursina Kellerhals, Richard Wetzel and Naomi Burgess</p>
<h4>Fighting COVID-19 at Purdue University: Design and Evaluation of a Game for Teaching COVID-19 Hygienic Best Practices</h4><p>Dominic Kao, Amogh Joshi, Christos Mousas, Abhigna Peddireddy, Arjun Kramadhati Gopi, Jianyao Li, John Springer, Bethany S. McGowan and Jason B. Reed</p>
<h4>Indigenous Worldviews in Digital Games: Sámi Perspectives in Gufihtara eallu (2018) and Rievssat (2018)</h4><p>Elizabeth Nijdam</p>
<h4>Design-Driven Requirements for Computationally Co-Creative Game AI Design Tools</h4><p>Nathan Partlan, Erica Kleinman, Jim Howe, Sabbir Ahmad, Stacy Marsella and Magy Seif El-Nasr</p>
<h4>Squeezer - A Mixed-Initiative Tool for Designing Juice Effects</h4><p>Mads Johansen, Martin Pichlmair and Sebastian Risi</p>
<h4>Fractal Coordinates for Incremental Procedural Content Generation</h4><p>Peter Mawhorter</p>
<h4>Improving the Discoverability of Indie Games by Leveraging their Similarity to Top-Selling Games</h4><p>Ngoc Quang Vu and Cor-Paul Bezemer</p>
<h4>Detecting Spam Game Reviews on Steam with a Semi-Supervised Approach</h4><p>Pengze Bian, Lei Liu and Penny Sweetser</p>
<h4>#StayHome Playing LoL - Analyzing Players&apos; Activity and Social Bonds in League of Legends During Covid-19 Lockdowns</h4><p>Simone Petrosino, Enrica Loria and Johanna Pirker</p>
<h4>Common Narrative in Educational Video Games: A Design of Games to Teach Circuits</h4><p>Declan McClintock and Charles Owen</p>
<h4>The temperature of morality: a behavioral study concerning the effect of moral decisions on facial thermal variations in video games</h4><p>Gianluca Guglielmo and Michal Klincewicz</p>
<h4>Uplifting Us: A BIPOC Game Design Case Study</h4><p>Christopher Brooks, Erica Principe Cruz, Jamie Camera and Alexandra To</p>
<h4>There Is No Escape: Theatricality in Hades</h4><p>Nick Junius, Max Kreminski and Michael Mateas</p>
<h4>Orange is Sus: Among Us and Political Play</h4><p>Mel Stanfill, Anastasia Salter and Anne Sullivan</p>
<h4>The Human Fantasy: Exploring race and ethnicity through Dungeons &amp; Dragons</h4><p>Antoine Prémont and Samuel Heine</p>
<h4>Learning Through Play: A Study Investigating How Effective Video Games Can Be Regarding Keyboard Education at a Beginner Level</h4><p>Jack Brett, Christos Gatzidis, Tom Davis, Panos Amelidis, Ning Xu and Toby Gladwell</p>
<h4>A Comparison of Augmented Reality and Digital Versions of a Citizen Science Game</h4><p>Kutub Gandhi, Josh Aaron Miller, Sofia Spatharioti, Archana Apte, Borna Fatehi, Sara Wylie and Seth Cooper</p>
<h4>Teaching esports to young students with autism: Exploring pedagogical possibilities and challenges</h4><p>Rune K. L. Nielsen, Thorkild Hanghøj, Morten Boller and Peter Mollerup</p>
<h4>Meta-Learning a Solution to the Hanabi Ad-Hoc Challenge</h4><p>Aron Sarmasi, Timothy Zhang, Chu-Hung Cheng, Huyen Pham, Xuanchen Zhou, Duong Nguyen, Soumil Shekdar and Joshua McCoy</p>
<h4>Questgram [Qg]: Toward a Mixed-Initiative Quest Generation Tool</h4><p>Alberto Alvarez, Eric Grevillius, Elin Olsson and Jose Font</p>
<h4>Softlock Detection for Super Metroid with Computation Tree Logic</h4><p>Ross Mawhorter and Adam Smith</p>
<h4>Integrating Serious and Casual Game Design Approaches: A Framework for Activist-Casual Game Design</h4><p>Daniel King</p>
<h4>It&apos;s Badging Time: Permanence, Expiration, and Lifespan of Digital Badges</h4><p>Joey R. Fanfarelli and Paul M. Harden</p>
<h4>Towards explainable prediction of player frustration in video games</h4><p>Max Wolterink and Sander Bakkes</p>
<h4>Personalizing Gameful Elements in Social Exergames: An Exploratory Study</h4><p>Gerry Chan, Ali Arya, Rita Orji, Zhao Zhao and Anthony Whitehead</p>
<h4>Using Machine Learning to Predict Game Outcomes Based on Player-Champion Experience in League of Legends</h4><p>Tiffany D. Do, Seong Ioi Wang, Dylan S. Yu, Matthew G. McMillian and Ryan P. McMahan</p>
<h4>Modular Reinforcement Learning Framework for Learners and Educators</h4><p>Rachael Versaw, Samantha Schultz, Kevin Lu and Richard Zhao</p>
<h4>Ruby&apos;s Mission: An Applied Gaming Intervention for reducing Loneliness of Children with Chronic Illness</h4><p>Dionysis Alexandridis, Sander C. J. Bakkes, Sanne L. Nijhof, Elise van de Putte and Remco C. Veltkamp</p>
<h4>Increasing player engagement, retention and performance through the inclusion of educational content in a citizen science game</h4><p>Rogerio de Leon Pereira, Anthony Tan, Andrea Bunt and Olivier Tremblay-Savard</p>
<h4>Towards Disambiguating Quests as a Technical Term</h4><p>Kristen Yu, Nathan Sturtevant and Matthew Guzdial</p>
<h4>Generating and Blending Game Levels via Quality-Diversity in the Latent Space of a Variational Autoencoder</h4><p>Anurag Sarkar and Seth Cooper</p>
<h4>Modding Support of Game Engines</h4><p>Lukas Schreiner and Sebastian von Mammen</p>
<h4>Web-based Programming for Low-cost Gaming Handhelds</h4><p>Michal Moskal, Thomas Ball, Abhijith Chatra, James Devine, Peli de Halleux, Steve Hodges, Shannon Kao, Richard Knoll, Galen Nickel, Jacqueline Russell, Joey Wunderlich and Daryl Zuniga</p>
<h4>Crowning Achievements: A historioludic analysis of the achievement metagame in historical simulation games</h4><p>Kirk Lundblade</p>
<h4>Heterogeneous Effects of Software Patches in a Multiplayer Online Battle Arena Game</h4><p>Yuzi He, Christopher Tran, Julie Jiang, Keith Burghardt, Emilio Ferrara, Elena Zheleva and Kristina Lerman</p>
<h4>Investigating Match Performance Differences between Genders of League of Legends Champions</h4><p>Ivan Ramler, Choong-Soo Lee and Sarah Strong</p>
<h4>Playing between Opposite Ideologies with Focalization and Agency: A Look at Ideological Perspective in Narrative-driven Games</h4><p>Huaxin Wei and Teresa H. M. Leung</p>
<h4>Game Mechanic Alignment Theory and Discovery</h4><p>Michael Green, Ahmed Khalifa, Rodrigo Canaan, Philip Bontrager and Julian Togelius</p>
<h4>Challenging Systems of Play: Towards game design ethics for transgender allyship</h4><p>Josephine Baird and Sabine Harrer</p>
<h4>Adversarial Random Forest Classifier for Automated Game Design</h4><p>Thomas Maurer and Matthew Guzdial</p>
</xml>
